Chapter 425: Assassinate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Thoughts were swirling in both their minds. After a cold stare, both of them greeted each other warmly.

"I wonder for what’s the purpose of the Palace Head’s visit to the North FIeld?" The old man slowly descended, controlling the octopus as it quickly shrunk, from a humongous creature into a black octopus the size of a palm which rested on his shoulder.

"I was just bored, so I came out to look for some creatures which were slightly stronger for practice." Garen laughed. "I never expected to meet Tower head Endjack, what great luck I have."

"We from the Seven Nights Tower have good relations with Kovitan, why don’t you come over with me to the inner tower area for a visit, so that i can host you properly." Similarly, Endjack smiled as he said.

Garen had originally intended to get close to this person, and the other party also seemed to have similar intent when as he heard that he was from the powerful Kovitan Kingdom. Since both sides intend to build a relationship, both sides travelled with each other, chattering away about the North Field’s unique scenery.

As the other party mentioned that they were looking for a brat who stole their treasure, Garen immediately agreed to help and dispatched his own Black Fire Guard for a search and arrest.

The tens of Black Fire Guards each rode on a giant Thunderhawk and scattered across the entirety of the surrounding airspace within the snowy land.

The only elite guard left was merely there to carry miscellaneous items.

The duo walked as they chatted, and soon, two Black fire Guards have sent signals of sightings of human tracks.

Garan and old man Endjack rushed over, but they found a group of people facing the Black fire guards as though they were preparing for war

The group probably had ten or so people, each of them decked in red attire, with the strength of Form 2s, and even two Form 3s among them.

The group was also surrounding an eel-like creature’s corpse with a sad expression. The snow-covered ground was stained red by blood, corpses littered the surrounding areas.

"Sir from the Royal Alliance, this Black-tailed Eel is something we took down after hefty amount of preparation and sacrifices…" A man stood up among the red-clothed men and spoke loudly as he observed the duo approaching.

"A form 3 Black-tailed eel…" Endjack had an expression of greed for a moment.

"It’s just a form 3 Black-tailed Eel." Garen who was beside him couldn’t care less. This thing is primarily used to create leather armor and tactical scrolls, nothing much aside from that. He had the Black Fire Heavy Plate made specially by the Royal Family, and the tactical scrolls were also made by high quality black dragon skin. Those were top-tier creatures that were in the peak of form 4, these kinds of small creatures don’t even come close to comparison.

It’s just that Garen felt lazy to bring those during the usual days. Most totem users who primarily used totems during combat will pay extra attention to the tactics. Which was to say, most totem users primarily used tactics, their totem’s talents and abilities as well as their heirloom abilities for combat. But Garen was different, he didn’t need tactics to do combat at all, he used his own physical body as the fastest, most simplistic killing machine.

Adding onto Kovitan’s ability to churn out materials, the items forged from these form 3 materials can be obtained anytime. Why would he even bat an eye to these dirty raw materials. That was the reason why he was not attracted at all towards the tactics’ raw materials.

As he heard an expert of the same level say this, Endjack was shocked. He decided not to ask to take it in the end.

For the Seven Nights Tower, a form 3 Black-tailed Eel was already decent spoils, one where everything on it had a purpose.

Despite hearing this, the opposite party still didn’t loosen up.

One shouldn’t be fooled into thinking that it was easy to take down a single Black-tailed Eel. In reality, Black-tailed Eels were actually herd animals. It was an incredibly difficult task to lure and hunt a singular Eel. On top of that, they had suffered a casualty, too, if it were to be snatched by an outsider, it would be tragic.

"Let’s go, we’ll check out the other places, perhaps you can find the person you want to catch." Garen noticed the greed in the old man’s eyes.

Subsequently, the duo repeatedly encountered totem users who came to North field to hunt monsters. These totem users were mostly form 2, with a small portion of them being Form 3, but most of them came over from Kovitan’s general direction. Once they saw Garen’s Royal Alliance Uniform, they all became fearfully wary. Only a handful of people knew about Endjjack, the Tower Head, but they were most definitely respectful to Garen.

This incident had open Endjack’s eyes on the benefits of becoming a Royal Alliance member.

After a round of searches, both of them failed to find any leads, but Garen wished to help Endjack settle this issue as a friendly gesture of the Black Fire Palace.

Endjack only said he would consider, but did not reject it outright.

Garen wasn’t rushing it either, instead used his identity as the Head of Trejons Family to express his wish to obtain trade support with the Third Tower. The produce from the North Field had extremely good heat insulating properties; their animal furs were also of good quality with good aesthetics, with some exotic items on the side.

Not only did Endjack not reject it, he agreed to it on the spot. The both of them exchanged a secret communication device, then Garen returned to the kingdom.

**********************

The First Concubine’s Palace

Delouse seemed troubled as she sat on the Concubine Throne, observing the black-armored guards patrolling the surroundings through a side window of the hall. Large amounts of dark red flower patterns could be seen inscribed onto armor, which meant this person is from the Black Fire Palace.

"This is troublesome… this Nine-Headed Dragon just appeared and has his line of sight planted everywhere." A voice from a dark corner was heard; transmitted directly into First Concubine’s ears.

"That’s why you need to figure out a way. With Garen in the picture, we need an additional safeguard." Delouse’s lips moved slightly, and a soft voice was sent into the corner.

"If all else fails, we will do ‘that’!" The voice from within the corner sounded as if a decision had been made.

Suddenly, a loud noise was heard from outside the hall.

"Minister Veska has arrived!!"

Soon, an elderly man with a head full of grey hair walked into the hall under the escort of two white-armored guards.

"Greetings, Your Highness." Veska bowed out of respect. "By His Majesty’s orders, I am here to inform Your Highness that the ceremony of trust shall start tonight. I hope your highness can keep this a secret, and do the necessary preparations.

"Tonight?!" Delouse was shocked, she was caught off guard. "Why does His Majesty want to bring forward the ceremony!? I haven’t received any prior notice, this seems a bit rushed."

"These are his Majesty’s orders, we have no rights to question them." Veska turned around and left after bowing with respect.

Soon, a red skirted maid walked in; she was First Concubine’s close maid.

"Your Highness, what do we do now?" the maid asked softly after approaching the First Concubine.

"Inform everyone, make the arrangements. Though it is slightly rushed, we have finally arrived to this day. That old man Veska had most probably found out something. Do the necessary arrangements on your side and wait for orders."

"Understood"

"Alright, now get going, nowadays the Black Fire Palace are on a vigilant lookout for spies, so don’t stand out too much."

"Okay"

As the silhouette of the maid left the door, Delouse’s blue eyes turned deep again.

Nine-Headed Dragon and Garland Sword…Looks like Veska that old fart was strategizing for Avic. One was in the light while another was in darkness, and all of this happened simultaneously while getting rid of all the suspicious characters, this was truly the work of an important person.

*****************

Once Garen returned to the palace, he heard the news that the Aegis Ceremony would be held tonight.

He was slightly shocked that Avic would decide so quickly and was planning to investigate thoroughly already.

Although he had done checks for such a long time, Garen still felt that the First Concubine’s Obscuro pawns were still hiding inside the palace, and their numbers were not small. This made him uncertain.

He made a special trip to the front of the Eleventh Royal Daughter’s palace to inspect it, and kept making guesses. Avic had already sensed the First Concubine’s betrayal, but failed nonetheless, and this likely had something to do with the Eleventh Royal Daughter. Thus, he monitored the Eleventh Royal Daughter closely, not letting her out of his sight, and not allowing any outsiders to have any contact with her.

The Eleventh Palace was completely quiet, and the Eleventh Royal Daughter was focused on drawing practice and did not sense his oncoming presence.

This allowed Garen to relax slightly, and he decided to participate in the ceremonial activities this time.

Regardless whether Avic’s assassination succeeded or failed, he wanted to find as many benefits from this as possible. Of course, it would be best if it failed. The important thing, unlike the rubbish massacre previously, was that a proper professional killer was involved. Furthermore, he was also interested in the ancient Endor precious heirlooms.

Soon, after dinner, the sky darkened quickly.

Avic entered the underground palace as well, and went into the Blood Jade Palace that was below ground. He gathered Garen, Edin, Veska and the others, to participate in tonight’s secret ceremony.

******************

Inside the underground palace

The pitch-black floor was covered in black bricks as smooth as mirrors, and each piece was shaped in a large square, and could almost reflect a person’s shadow.

On top was a semi-circle shaped black ceiling, illuminated with dots of silver light. In the center, a large crystal chandelier hung downwards, and lit up the room with an unknown, faint red light.

Blood Jade Palace was roughly the same size as most palaces, except that the four walls of its interior were engraved with many gold human portraits, and all of these portraits protruded out of the walls, forming many embossments. The carvings were extremely lifelike, as if the four corners of the palace were filled with a circle of onlookers.

The ‘onlookers’ included palace officials, royal family members, children, and old people, but most of them were beautiful and flirtatious young women.

These women’s bodies were exposed, as some of them were only covered in light veils, while others were half naked, and others had exaggerated movements, and there were others that were shy and charming.

The gazes of all of the carvings were fixed at the center of Blood Jade Palace, where a blood pond was built.

Avic wore his cumbersome royal military uniform and his silver crown, and held the royal scepter in his hand, his gaze solemnly transfixed on First Concubine Delouse, who was half-kneeling in front of him.

Behind them in order stood Garen, Veska, and Edin, and some elite guards who were clad in full-bodied silver armor, holding white dual swords in their hands.

This ceremony was unusually simple, without a large aristocratic ceremony, and without notifying any foreign ministers. Meanwhile, the two Grand Dukes were also absent, and the representatives from the Elder Parliament had yet to arrive as well.

Avic had probably organized this ceremony hurriedly, and perhaps no one knew what he was thinking, or maybe First Concubine had already guessed it but currently, the conclusion was already decided, and she would have to start making her first move soon.

The faint red light shone on everyone, and cast a slightly mysterious atmosphere in the palace.

"The ceremony will begin now," Avic said solemnly.

Clang… Clang… Clang…

Melodious clock noises echoed from the palace.

Chirp chirp chirp chirp…

Suddenly, white streams of air flowed into all four corners of the palace through the windows like white ribbons, flying towards Avic and the half-kneeling First Concubine.

The white air currents were apparently made out of countless tiny pieces of yellow and white paper. They made bird-like chirping noises as they flew circles around the First Concubine.

Avic raised his right hand, before the unassuming black ring on his finger suddenly released puffs of black smoke slowly. The black smoke gathered in a circle and rose upwards, dissolving in the air slowly, before the entire palace was quickly filled with a light flowery aroma.

First Concubine Delouse bowed her head and knelt on the ground, while the white and yellow pieces of paper floated downwards and fell onto the top of her head slowly, before quickly turning into delicate flower petals.

White and yellow flower petals fell from her head and body. Like rain drops, the flower petals fell on her body, and some of them slipped off, while others changed their shape slowly, turning into white and yellow butterflies.

These butterflies flew and danced around, and some of them perched on her shoulders, while others flew everywhere.

"In the name of my ancestors, from this day onwards, I bestow you, my concubine, the final right of asylum!" Avic placed his right hand that wore the ring towards Delouse’s forehead, and said in a loud and solemn voice.

Suddenly, a cloud of black smoke wafted out of his ring and flew towards Delouse as if it were alive.

Veska, Edin, and Garen nodded lightly in respect. They were the only three close ministers that Avic had gathered here.

At this moment, in the middle of Delouse’s golden undone curls, a lock of braided black hair suddenly underwent a strange transformation.

The braid became pitch-black, and its narrow end sharpened and hardened suddenly before the entire black braid slowly turned into the shape of a scorpion’s tail.

There was a snapping noise, before the sting of the scorpion’s tail jumped up suddenly, and lit up in a dark red, and almost black glowing sheen.

Meanwhile, Avic’s perpetually raised hand now hovered over Delouse’s head, and his gaze was still fixed there as if it had never moved at all.

The moment when the ceremony was finally about to end, was when Avic had lost his final ultimate asylum pass, at that time…

First Concubine lowered her head, not allowing the coldness in her eyes to flow out.

The ring on top of her head continued to release almost-sentient black smoke, that drilled into Delouse’s head continuously, unceasingly as if it was endless.

Chapter 426: Assassinate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As time passed, the black smoke started thinning out, as though it had run out of steam.

Delouse’s scorpion tail protruded slightly, its tip aiming right at Avic, in front of her.

"Delouse, you have followed me for about 10 years, no?" Avic suddenly spoke, his voice was deep, with a hint of regret and pain.

Delouse lifted her head, and coincidentally the final trails of smoke went back into her head.

Suddenly, she was faintly aware that there was nobody around her, not even the three ministers who were standing behind her, they just vanished without her knowing.

The original guards have disappeared too, the entire Blood Jade palace was left with only her and Avic.

"Your Majesty, you….!"

Avic raised his royal staff and looked at Delouse. " I never wanted to do this…" his eyes were mixed with clashing emotions, labyrinthine thoughts, bitter betrayal, so much such that it was impossible to etch all of them on his face.

Delouse’s face turned mildly black. She also suddenly started to choke on her throat, started coughing involuntarily.

"This….this is…!?"

"I gave you a chance…" Avic lowered his staff as he saw the woman struggling in front of him.

As the staff was lowered, Delouse followed slowly, without a sound. Her eyes, nose, mouth, and ears started oozing black blood. Little black bugs started crawling out of her nostrils, and then dissipated as clouds of black smoke.

At this time, a ray of red flashed past.

Jii!!!

Avic’s pupils dilated in that instance.

************************************

Floor Palace

In the White Silver Palace, Edin was gently polishing the silver longsword on his hand.

On the longsword’s body was a silver circle, but they weren’t attached. Rather it was as if they were once the same entity.

The moon outside the hall shined bright with a hue of silver. The lights in the hall were sufficiently bright, rows upon rows of Royal Elite Guards stood quietly on the flanks of the palace.

"Then, His Majesty brought an illusion of us to the inner palace?" Edin said quietly.

In the shadows, a tall silhouette walked out slowly. It turned out to be Garen, who was donning dense, heavy armor.

He was well equipped; unlike other Black Fire armors, there were two fangs protruding on both of his pauldrons, giving off a sense of intimidation.

The armor made him look like a large monster over two meters tall. Oddly, even though he was wearing such heavy armor, Garen seemed to be walking with ease, as though this were his everyday attire, weightless and mobile.

"I had originally disagreed too, but His Majesty insisted. The choice wasn’t mine to make. Even Sir Veska cannot persuade His Majesty." Garen answered coldly.

"Just for the little bugs outside?" Edin frowned slightly.

"Those aren’t just regular bugs…" Garen frowned too. "If you carry such an underestimating attitude.."

"I don’t need you to tell me that." Edin interrupted coldly.

Garen’s expression calmed down as well. He then snickered.

"Go back to your own Black Fire Palace." Edin mocked.

Even though he felt that Edin never liked him, to use such a tone to an expert his own level, Garen felt belittled and angered, and he showed a hint of murderous intent.

"I hope you don’t disappoint His Majesty, otherwise…" Garen did not bother covering up his murderous intent anymore.

Edin did not answer, but instead, he lowered his head to continue polishing his sword.

Garen retreated into the shadow and disappeared without a trace.

The curtain nearby suddenly was drawn suddenly. A sudden gust of black wind suddenly blew past the window and quickly disappeared into the night sky.

Edin stood up from his throne. As he gazed up, he looked at the female silhouette which had been standing outside the palace for an unknown amount of time.

He extended his hand, his pale white fingertips were suddenly greeted with a white rose.

"I have been waiting for a long time." Edin walked down from the throne and walked towards that person.

*****************************************

Black Fire Palace

Garen didn’t know what kind of expert awaited Edin, but that aura had been intense and violent, it faintly felt like it was comparable to Edin, but was obviously an expert hired by Obscuro. He originally prepared to assist Edin by combining forces, but Edin brushed him off with such an attitude, which angered him and turned him away.

Tonight was the night of the assassination, but Garen felt that Edin’s behavior was odd.

He sat on that throne, gently stroking the shiny sphere on his armrest, his mind shrouded with the feeling of unease. It’s too bad that he had too little information now that the main branches strategizing had been left to Veska, while Garen only controlled territory.

Bam!!!

Suddenly, a deafening explosion was heard from outside the palace.

That direction, it was none other than White Silver Palace!

Garen shuddered.

"Edin! To think that it’s you!!" no wonder he always thought that Edin felt off. He secluded himself from communicating with anyone, always shut training in his own palace. He lacked the lust, the desire for power, even his dining etiquette was incomparable to a regular noble. Such a man with no desire should never have existed!

The White Silver Palace controlled the entire Palace Tactics; core pivot, and that was a sound was obviously of the pivot’s explosion.

"Men!"

Suddenly, Black Fire Guards rushed into the main palace like streams of black river merging into one. The rushed footsteps were oddly in sync, and there was no sense of panic.

Garen stood up.

"Four guards, follow me, the rest of you, kill all the palaces intruders!"

At this point, he did not plan to go underground to assist Avic, but instead set his sight on the Eleventh Palace opposite him.

Avic was infallible, if there were no incidents, he would never be killed. Then, the catalyst of the accident has to be...

******************************************************

Inside the Eleventh Palace

Tina bulged her eyes as she was caught speechless, looking at the underground passage’s sudden appearance.

"You….How did you avoid the underground defense array??"

Beckstone brushed off the soil off himself, pulling another bearded man out as the two men tunneled out of the ground.

"Just a little special technique, if it weren’t for Obscuro’s attack, we would never have had the chance. Alright, no more nonsense, let’s get out of here."

"But… aren’t there Black Fire Guards outside?" Tina turned around and looked outside. The Black Fire Guards had vanished without her realizing it. She was completely speechless.

"I’ve promised, I will definitely rescue you with complete preparation." Beckstone spoke calmly, "would this count as returning you the favor?"

"You’ve indeed remembered clearly." Tina can’t help but laugh.

"Since we are friends, I shall not take it that you violated by that beast without doing anything." Beckstone seemed hurt, from the look of his eyes.

"But…" Tina suddenly got nervous, "I don’t know why, but I always feel that my heart would keep pounding, things can’t be this simple…"

"No buts, let’s go, we’re running out of time!" Beckstone frowned as he said.

"Alright…."

The three people packed up, but the maids surrounding them were oddly asleep on the floor.

They were about to get into the underground tunnel and go back where they came from.

Bam!!

The deep tremor of an explosion was heard.

The tunnel’s entrance had a gush of air outwards, some black soil was mixed in the gust.

The three of them looked at each other.

Beckstone took out a small purple ball, and gently shook it next to his ears. And his expression changed.

"It’s the underground inner palace...the tunnel…..caved in from the tremor." Beckstone looked at his partners with a sobbing voice.

"To the secret passage!" Beard said decisively, leading the way and rushing towards the exit of the palace. "Right now, the Obscuro and Royal Alliance are duking it out with each other, I heard about this from the old fart, all the elites of Obscuro were dispatched, while The Royal Alliance had activated their tactical arrays. The entire palace has been covered in a layer of huge illusionary arrays. We wouldn’t make it if we delayed any further!"

Beckstone looked at his party, then carried Tina and caught up with Beard.

"It’s so late, Your Eleventh Highness, where are you heading off to?"

The cold voice of a man came suddenly.

What followed was the sound of quick, heavy footsteps, and the Eleventh Palace was suddenly surrounded by Black Fire Heavy Guards. The densely lined guards did not utter a word and completely surrounded the trio in the palace.

In front of the trio, at the palace doors, a tall armored silhouette was slowly walking out, it was indeed the handsome young man with a blood red mark between his brows.

His eyesight was locked onto Beckstone.

"I’ve said before, never appear in front of me again… looks like you took it for a joke."

Suddenly, Beckstone’s breathing became close to hyperventilating, and his eyes turned slightly bloodshot.

"Garen…!"

"Go!!" Beard suddenly pulled him and tossed him behind.

He suddenly opened his mouth wide and out came a giant python.

Tssss!

The python flew out was only as thick as an arm, but halfway through its trajectory, its diameter became bigger and it grew larger in size. By the time it reached Garen, it had already reached a diameter of over two meters. Its mouth was filled with poisonous green mist, its jaws lined to the brim with teeth. It opened its jaw wide and shot towards Garen.

The entire palace was covered with a thin layer of suffocating poison mist.

"Trying to use poison in on me?" Garen flicked his left hand. His index finger was followed by a series of afterimages, landing right on the python’s jaw.

Bam!

The python exploded immediately and turned into a cloud of black mist that was scattered in all directions. The smoke effectively disabled the vision of everyone in the palace.

Garen lifted his head and took a deep breath.

Fuuuuuuuh….!!

A large vortex appeared out of nowhere, and the cloud of smoke was sucked into Garen’s lungs like streams flowing into an ocean, and was all gone in a single suck.

The poison mist in the palace was cleared by Garen in an instant.

At this point, Beard had already taken both persons and flew out of the palace, almost landing onto a giant white bird’s back.

"Running, are we?"

Garen snickered, he extended his right arm towards the trio from afar in a grabbing motion.

Jii!!!

Suddenly, a translucent body flew towards the trio.

Suddenly, a silver ring appeared in a flash and chopped off the three blood-colored dragon heads with cold precision.

Roar!!!

In the instant the dragon head and silver ring clashed, both of them disappeared.

A silver-white silhouette flew towards Garen and blocked him from advancing.

"Move!!" Garen roared in anger, his mark turned blood-red and the Nine-Headed Dragon appeared, attacking the opponent by fluttering towards it like nine blood-red mares while letting out a deafening roar.

"Ring of the Moon."

A clear sound rang out suddenly.

A silver hemisphere suddenly appeared in front of that man, and the giant ring completely halted the advance of the nine dragon heads.

At this time, Beckstone and two other people have already arrived at the giant white bird and were ready to flee. The bird began flapping its wings.

Garen had released boundless killing intent. His irises faintly turned vertical, just like the Nine-Headed Dragon, giving off an unusually violent air.

"Edin… you’re courting death!"

"Unfortunately, you can’t do it." The man turned his round silver ring sword upright, with no changes whatsoever in his intonation.

"Then let’s try it!" the silhouette of the Nine-Headed Dragon suddenly appeared behind Garen.

Roar!!!!!

The nine dragon heads roared fiercely.

Chapter 427: Shock 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Underground Inner Palace

Within the Dark Blood Jade Palace

The many maids around the palace had suddenly disappeared, systematically rushing out of the palace hall and running to various hiding facilities.

Only Delouse and Avic were left in the Blood Jade Palace.

Delouse’s black braid was like a scorpion’s tail; the red tail pin was floating in front of Avic’s face, only a finger’s distance away from piercing into his right eye.

The two of them were in a stalemate.

What’s odd was that even though Delouse’s face was covered in blood and her facial orifices were still bleeding, her expression showed a ferocious smile.

"This absolute protection….. Really sets an expectation…" Delouse started laughing, and her voice suddenly turned deep, resembling the deep voice of a man, hoarse and gruff!

She still had her slender body, beautiful face and blonde hair, but her eyes became two black whirlpools.

Avic’s face turned pale, his body shuddered, and he could not stop his throat from shaking, almost as if he was trying to stop himself from puking.

"You….you’re God Cloud….?!!" His voice turned hoarse, carrying a sliver of hope, hoping that she gave the opposite answer.

"You guessed right." Delouse smiled. "From the beginning, I have been God Cloud. Or rather, Delouse, since the beginning, had been my clone."

Suddenly, Delouse’s expression changed and became lovable and soft again."Your majesty~~ don’t you love me anymore?" Her voice returned to that of a gentle female’s.

A usually delightful gentle voice was giving him the chills at that very moment.

"You... You!!" Avic felt sick from the inside, a strong revolting feeling was rumbling in the pit his stomach. To think that he slept with a man for so many years, he couldn’t help but shudder,

Dense layers of goosebumps appeared on his skin.

Finally

"You monster!!" Avic roared, and took a few steps back, he was surrounded by an invisible barrier, protecting him from any harm.

God Cloud had a snickering expression again.

"Your Majesty, how can you speak of me in such way? So many days and nights, have you forgotten all of them?" His voice was interchanged between a man’s and a woman’s voice.

Avic could not stand it anymore. With a pale face, he lifted his hand and pointed towards God Cloud.

"Kill him! Kill him now!!!" He shouted

In an instant, three powerful silhouettes appeared from around the palace. It was as though they came out from a void, and had been there from the beginning and never moved a muscle.

The Illusionary Arrray’s abilities had masked their presence so that nobody noticed it.

Even God Cloud was slightly surprised.

He took a glance at the three people surrounding him.

Captain Woods of the Silver Knights in the National Service?

Out of the trio, a white-haired old man holding a wooden staff smiled at him as a sign of agreeing.

"Never expected it to be Sir God Cloud coming here, being able to see the number one genius of yesteryear, is indeed my honor."

Old man Woods wore a white robe with a silver inscription, and a necklace made of white skulls was dangling over his neck. He gave less of an impression of a knight, but more of a pagan witch of an indigenous tribe.

God cloud shifted his sight to another person. This man was stern-faced, the black robe he donned was very tidy, and he was holding a blue dagger with a black hilt. A humid scent of seawater was faintly surrounding the dagger.

"So you’re here too, Veska."

Veska remained emotionless.

"Who would’ve guessed that First Concubine was God Cloud. Since you’re here, then don’t bother leaving."

God Cloud laughed and he looked over at the last person.

"King of the Stars. The head of Geometry Service is here too?"

The last one was a young man, he donned a black noble uniform, his face white and handsome, and he was fiddling with a drawing pen in his hand. Oddly, the drawing pen’s tip was flickering, as though it was an ember.

"Sir God Cloud, this time it’s you who crossed the border. This is Kovitan Empire, not your Dark Maze."

The three people formed a triangle as they surrounded God Cloud, each of them had a natural expression but placed all their attention on God Cloud.

"Looks like you intend to detain my clone. This cannot happen, my three main clones have all gone through tumultuous effort to produce." God Cloud smiled again.

With a flip of his palm, her right palm quickly bulged up and formed a sphere.

The bulging skin turned greener and greener, and the curvature of the sphere had also became bigger.

Poong…..

An immense quake spread outwards with God Cloud as the epicenter. The invisible quake surged violently onto the three men.

Tssss…..

The three men had been forcibily pushed back a few steps, under their feet were 6 streaks of marks left on the floor.

"Original Heirlooms!!!" King of the Stars had a change in expression, his expression started showing. "Hoho, who would have known that Sir God Cloud would be willing to bring out even an Original Heirloom. Distortion Pearl, hefty, indeed."

"If the clone dies here, the Distortion Pearl would be ours." Veska suddenly said.

"Since he even brought the Original Heirloom, looks like we have to go full out for this, let’s not hide our abilities, use our strongest moves straight away, otherwise the victor may not be us." The Silver Knight Captain Woods said. He was the same as Veska, even though they sounded carefree, but their eyes had a gleam of strictness.

Original Heirlooms…. Avic’s Absolute defense was also an Original Heirloom, these are the strongest heirlooms, even though Obscuro couldn’t win against RAL, but they alone could have comparable power to a single large kingdom. Unexpectedly, he dared bet on that small interval of a pinnacle form 5 expert and take the Distortion Pearl on an attack against Kovitan.

"Can we send a message out to the Department Headquarters chief?" Woods asked.

Veska smiled bitterly. "The formation we arranged ourselves has isolated all communication to the outside, we would need at least an hour to completely disable them."

Woods could only laugh bitterly.

At this time, a quake shook above Blood Jade Palace.

Roar!!!

A loud beast’s cry was heard from above them.

The entire palace vibrated slightly, which brought crumbs of debris tumbling down.

"Looks like there’re people clashing above us." Veska looked up at the ceiling.just as his gaze left God Cloud, he could hear a loud gust immediately.

"Careful!!!"

A voice shouted, by the corner of Vaska's eyes, he could see a black chain was shot towards him. Reflexively, he quickly ducked towards the right.

Pewpewpew!!

Countless chains were shot by God Cloud towards the trio.

A black giant’s silhouette appeared behind him.

*********************

The Eleventh Palace, Surface

Just as the giant white bird took off, a great sonic boom struck it down.

Its wings tilted and carved out an angled crater, and it fiercely smashed into a garden on its right side.

Bam!!

The garden was a mess, a great number of the plants were either knocked down or squashed.

The white bird laid next to a white granite platform, half of its body landed on two gardeners, and pools of blood were seen flowing out from beneath the white bird and onto the black soil.

The sharp scream of the maids was soon heard, and those white-attired maids swarmed towards the cracks to attempt escape, like frightened bee colonies.

Just as Beckstone and his friends were dizzily climbing down from the bird, dense thumps of footsteps were heard from behind him.

Tens of Black Fire Heavy Guards rushed over, their eyes shined with green lights, each of them had green liquid dripping between the crevices of their armor. As the viscous liquid made its way onto the floor, it burned through the floor, into many potholes of different sizes.

The guard in front suddenly opened its mouth wide, and out came that green viscous liquid spewing out violently, like a tide which rushed towards the trio.

Bam!!

Clang!!

The Nine-Headed Dragon in front of Garen fiercely smashed into the hemispherical moon arc blade.

The red and white light suddenly exploded, countless tiny pieces of shattered Totem lIght scattered everywhere.

Edin let out a moan, the white arc in front of him was shattered. He took a leap backward, onto a roof nearby.

"Stupid barbarian"

Bam!!

The Nine-Headed Dragon chased after him, violently crashing into the location of which he stood into smithereens. The chandelier in the corridor under the roof broke loose and fell to the ground due to the intense impact.

Clang!!

Amidst the crisp sound of broken crystal, Edin turned swiftly and avoided Nine-Headed Dragon’s attack and landed safely on the roof on his right.

The bloodied mark on Garen’s forehead got thicker. A strong, murderous intent was barraging within his heart. His eyes were slowly turning blood red as well, the horrifying Dragon’s eyes gave him an almost inhumane terror.

With a wave of his arms, the dragon heads move to the right.

Kroonggg….

The nine dragon heads were like 9 pillars tearing everything in its path towards the roof, banking right as it chased Edin.

Innumerable houses were torn down by the dragons, and more the chandeliers in the corridors beneath fell one after the other.

Pang! Pang! Pang!

The shattering of the chandeliers kept continuing, to the point of becoming deafening. The millions of crystal shards were scattered in all directions like snowflakes. The entire corridor was enveloped in a thick layer of white crystal shards.

The Nine-Headed Dragons could not keep up with Edin in the end, and the bloodied eyes of Garen only got thicker.

suddenly, his foot forcefully stomped the ground

Bam!!

Garen disappeared in an instant, the ground beneath him turned into a crater several meters wide.

Edin laughed coldly

"I was waiting for this technique"

He waved his right arm and a few roses made up a few white lines were fixed in midair.

Jii!

The white rose instantaneously exploded and became countless petals of flowers.

Garen’s afterimage had been running through the petals, but were discovered by Edin

A cold light flashed through Edin’s eyes.

"Florid Sword." A white rose appeared in his hand, as he sniffed it gently, Edin actually closed his eyes fully, without a care of the possible ambush by Garen.

Tssss!

A ray of white light shot out.

The Nine-Headed Dragon’s silhouette which encircled Garen flew up and fluttered, his left hand conjured a seemingly unstoppable gust, forming a slab of red afterimage and clashing with the white ray head-on in an instant.

The red shadow and white ray met each other halfway.

The red shadow was effortlessly slashed through. The white rose instantaneously passed through the space between Garen’s fingers and stabbed his forehead

Suddenly he could see the clear white petals of the rose, the white, without any hint of impurity, white circles of pure petals that seemed to be stacked together. There was even a dewdrop on it.

At such unfathomable speeds, yet ever so calming.

Garen couldn’t care less, his right hand struck out with speed, the auras of a long unused power had begun bubbling.

A surge of a violent, horrid aura exploded from his body.

"Ten Thousand Mammoths, Red Jade!!" his right palm brought out a clarity comparable to a red jade, his palm was rubbing the air on top of it, and ignited in an instant!

A pure, high-temperature flame ignited just by the friction in the air!

The flaming right palm was like a ferocious dragon, surrounded by nine dragon heads, and after the first attack, it hit Edin’s Round-ringed sword.

.

Boom!!!

A red fire cloud broke out directly between the two, forming a silver ring.

Chapter 428: Shock 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The surroundings were covered by a silvery-red aura, while the ground was cracked and dry, with traces of sword marks emerging endlessly.

The stone pillars had collapsed and were charred black. The embossments had burst and were now red. The decorative bronze statues in between the palace had started to melt. Some of them were bent at the waist, while others were destroyed beyond recognition, and were filled with sword marks everywhere.

The silvery-red aura had spread out throughout a distance of thirty to forty meters before it disappeared gradually.

Garen and Edin were standing off in midair, and both of them were suspended there, as if a powerful invisible force was holding both of them up and preventing them from falling.

From afar, it seemed as if the enormous Nine-Headed Dragon was charging violently towards a large white rose.

Above the royal palace, between two tall black clock towers, the thirty-meter-long body of the Nine-Headed Dragon stood taller than most of the royal buildings, making the surrounding palace buildings look like toy models in comparison. Some of the nearby buildings had collapsed completely, while others suffered considerable damage.

The outer areas had been filled with a large number of palace guards who were unaware of the current situation. They were armed with weapons but only dared to encircle the area from far away. They helped hide the royal family members, palace officials, and servants that were unable to retaliate.

At this moment, Garen’s head moved backwards slightly.

Tch!!

The white rose from earlier passed through Garen’s forehead directly, but merged into his brain like a phantom, without any movements.

"Using a will-type attack against me?" A sneer flashed across Garen’s face. His strengthened his right hand’s grip on the ring sword suddenly.

Clang clang clang clang clang!!!

A string of frenzied clashing noises rang out continuously.

Edin’s face remained unchanged while his figure moved back frantically, but his speed did not increase as frighteningly as Garen’s.

His ruby-like fingers tapped against the body of the sword frenziedly, and all of the hits were concentrated on one point on the sword.

Edin’s silhouette stopped suddenly. His figure became slanted, as his right hand drew his sword as quick as lightning.

Ching!!!

Another silver ring sword was drawn out of thin air, before the white moon colored sword marks flew towards Garen.

The fingers on Garen’s left hand shot out.

Clang!!

His fingers collided with the side of the sword.

Tch!!

Red lights flashed.

Garen disappeared instantly in place, before reappearing again, except that he now stood on a piece of ground that was over ten meters away.

The ferocity on his face had disappeared completely, as he stretched his hand out and touched the right side of his face gently, before bringing his hand down to look at it, and seeing that his hand was now covered in blood.

On the right side of his face, a horizontal wound gradually appeared, and was bleeding slowly.

"I obviously blocked it…" Garen looked at Edin who was still suspended in midair not far away. "What ability is this?"

Edin turned over and fell directly from the sky, before standing on the broken surface of a bronze statue. He looked at Garen again, with a slightly respectful look in his gaze.

His fingertips turned, before a white rose magically appeared in his hand again.

"One hundred and thirty-four."

"?"

"One hundred and thirty four opponents of the same rank, including aberrated monsters. You were the only one who could force me to use the Dislocation Sword." Edin threw out a rose that turned into a pile of white flower petals again.

The abundant flower petals resembled a stream that flowed from the bottom to the top, and flew into his right palm. They gathered together slowly, and formed into a brand new silver ring sword!

Ching!

The two silver ring swords in his hands overlapped one other to form an ‘X’, while emitting an entrancing light silver glow under the moonlight.

"It turns out that you’ve always existed in a totem and physical body state from the beginning." A look of understanding appeared on Garen’s face suddenly. The air of ferocity that surrounded his whole body had disappeared completely at once. It seemed as if the fury he felt at the beginning was just an illusion.

He was now able to make full use of the Nine-Headed Dragon’s negative emotion to enhance his own fighting abilities, and the longer the period of normal suppression, the stronger it would be during combat.

This period of time where he worked in the palace, was not something that he could waste.

Totem combination was something that Garen understood as well, but up until now, he still relied on solo main body combat, or separate Totem combat. He was unlike Edin who used combinations from start to finish.

Although Form 4 and Spiritualization were different, as the time taken to combine was much longer, very few people would use continuous combination like him.

Upon seeing Garen’s sudden transformation, Edin’s gaze finally turned somewhat serious.

"Looks like I underestimated you."

Both of his swords were still overlapped, and a fiery war challenge appeared in his eyes.

"I have four types of sword skills that take turns to overlap, and have never been defeated. If you can deflect all of them, I will not obstruct you anymore."

"Obstruct me?" A mysterious smile appeared on Garen’s face. But moments later, he could vaguely feel a strange, mysterious gas coming from Edin’s body. This gas caused his perception to become blurry.

"Bloom, new moon…" Edin closed his eyes and opened them again, and now his pupils had become fully white.

Suddenly, an unparalleled sense of danger rushed towards Garen.

With Garen as the center, within a range of a few meters in the surroundings, a white moon colored rose began to bloom in midair slowly, and the center of the rose petals, was where he currently stood.

The entire white rose wrapped him up completely, and was incomparably beautiful under the moonlight.

Garen stood upright, motionless. He could detect that his surroundings were filled with an extremely sharp presence in the air, as if countless blades had formed a white rose.

His left pointer finger moved slightly.

Tch!

A bloody wound appeared on his fingertip suddenly, as if he had been wounded by a sharp blade.

"This is my second sword skill, Imprisonment Flowers." Edin’s voice could be heard from the front, while the two ring swords that were in his hands earlier had suddenly disappeared.

Regarding the powerful Vitality that Garen was proud of, when faced with high level opponents of the same rank, although it was abnormally strong, it was still unable to produce an effect that was powerful enough.

"Right now, you are already within my Imprisonment Flowers, and all movements will lead to an attack by the countless blades, so how will you escape then?" Edin looked at Garen calmly, regarding the Lord of the Black Fire Palace that he had worked together with during this period of time, he now had a brand new understanding of him.

His body felt as if it had the toughness of the Totem Light, but strangely enough, he did not have the protection of the Totem Light. Was it possible, that he had not released his Totem Light all this while, and was merely relying on his main body to fight me?

This assumption flashed across Edin’s mind, but he pushed it away immediately.

Impossible! It was impossible for anyone lower than Form 5 to use their main bodies to fight Totem abilities!

"You’ve finally realised…" The corners of Garen’s mouth upturned slightly into a smile. "Indeed, it is as you thought, I didn’t use my Totem Light, and have been relying on my main body to fight you."

The expression on Edin’s face grew more serious, and his gaze glared at Garen, while black gas began to escape from his opponent’s body like a large amount of black smoke, and creatures began to appear in their surroundings, enveloping the empty spaces around them.

"Currently, I’ve become more interested in you…" Garen licked his lips and pushed Beckstone and the others to the back of his mind, as the combat style of Edin, who stood before his eyes, had impacted him strongly, while an inspired feeling began to float up in his mind like rain after springtime.

"If I could kill you, that would be such a wonderful thing…" Garen’s surroundings were slowly illuminated with a layer of faint red light that was the Totem Light of the Nine-Headed Dragon.

He raised his hand slowly.

Cha cha cha!!

The red Totem Light on his arm and the shapeless blades clashed violently, emitting scattered fragments of red and white light.

He was sublimating!

Garen felt that his fighting skills were undergoing subtle changes.

The relationship between Totems and Secret Techniques in Edin’s fighting techniques, used a terrifyingly rapid impact to integrate with one another.

The blood plasma-like aura dispersed silently like thick blood that submerged in the surrounding ground, and surged towards Edin.

Edin’s gaze changed slightly, as he took a few steps back to avoid the spread of the plasma.

"What is this?!"

"If you survive, I’ll tell… You!!"

Before he could finish speaking, Garen’s entire body exploded into dots of light suddenly, as those were the countless fragments that were formed when the shapeless blades and Totem Light rubbed together violently.

The red and white dots rained down like fireworks.

A red afterimage appeared beside Edin instantly. Unlike its previous speed, its current speed seemed beyond his line of sight and beyond his nerves.

Before Edin could even open his blinking eyes, he felt a hot sensation collide against his chest violently.

He heard the sound of his own Totem Light tearing, as a terrifying surge of power rushed in through the crack, corroding his body.

When he opened his eyes, he could only see a burning red flame in front of him.

"The third sword… Fantasy Flower…" Edin could not move, and just voiced his command in a low mumble.

The flame disappeared instantly.

"Eh?" Garen said softly, he felt that he had suddenly been transported to an area a few meters away from Edin, as if his feet had made him run there, while the meter-long distance between them was something that he was unable to reduce.

The burning Red Jade Palm in his hands could never seem to get closer to Edin. It was merely a short meter-long distance, but it seemed so far away.

He kept rushing forward, but the ground beneath his feet seemed as if it had been stretched, and was constantly being pulled longer.

"Cough cough…" Edin began to cough violently, while he looked at the Totem Light in front of him that had almost been torn to shreds, flashing across his eyes suddenly. That speed that surpassed his nerves, senses, and even sound. If his Totem Light had held on for a slightly shorter amount of time, he would have been killed!!

Looking at Garen who had stopped not far away, he began to calm his emotions, before opening his mouth slowly.

"It’s useless, the Fantasy Flowers are a sword technique that possess unlimited extension. No one has been able to touch me with this technique."

"Fantasy Flowers… What a mysterious sword technique," praised Garen while he stood on the spot and felt his surroundings twisting slightly, he did not know if the space around him was twisting, or if his thoughts themselves were merely twisting, but this strange sensation was the first time he truly felt the powers of ultimate Form 4, and even Form 5 levels.

"I’ve never met a Form 4 Totem User like you…" Edin shook his head slightly. "Your main body is so powerful that even I fear it. I initially thought that anyone below Form 5 in this world was not worthy of being feared by myself."

Garen’s eyes narrowed slightly.

"Dislocation Sword, Imprisonment Sword, Fantasy Sword, I’m very curious as to what the last sword technique may be?"

"Hahaha…" A rare smile appeared on Edin’s face. "You’ll see it soon enough… The Fantasy Flowers can only bloom for ninety-nine heartbeats. And my last technique is preparing to end…"

He had just finished speaking when the surrounding areas that were twisted earlier now returned to their original calm states.

Without a moment of hesitation, Garen turned into a red shadow and dashed towards Edin.

"White New Moon Sword!!"

Edin growled softly as the two swords clashed, before the body of the sword melted instantly.

Whoosh!!

A terrifying, ten meter long white sword appeared in his hands, and the body of the sword had a large silver ring that turned circles like a clock.

The effect of the Fantasy Flowers finally disappeared completely, while at the same time, Edin raised the large sword, and waved it gently.

Chapter 429: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!!

Inside the underground palace, four rays of multicolored light exploded suddenly and intertwined continuously. The black chains were suspended in midair by a force field and did not move at all.

Veska’s entire body was enveloped by dark blue seawater whirlpool, and the dagger in his hand was soaking in seawater. His surroundings were filled with the echoes of crashing ocean wave noises. His eyes were like deep sea whirlpools that were almost bottomless.

"Choking Blade…" First Concubine, Her Excellency Delouse, or God Cloud, was currently smiling while looking at the dagger in Veska’s hand. "Ocean Ultimate Technique Whirlpool Blade. Legend says that it is a terrifying weapon that can silently cause the death of others, and today is the first time I’ve seen it properly."

She looked at the light blue halos that circled her surroundings, as her eyes blinked in awe.

"You already know my strongest Ultimate Technique, but you’re still brave enough to show off?" Veska spat coldly. "However, I’m not your most important opponent today."

Standing on the sidelines, the captain of the Silver Knights, Woods and the King of the Stars from the Geometry Service both smiled simultaneously and took a step forward together.

"With Lord Veska possession of the distortive power of the Original Heirlooms, the next step will depend on us."

Woods leaned on his wooden staff, as a cloud of black smoke circled the top of the staff and formed a whirlpool there, the center of the whirlpool seemed to have a terrifying gaze looking outwards.

He raised his wooden staff and pointed it towards God Cloud suddenly.

A hissing noise could be heard as a cloud of black smoke spurted out suddenly, and flew towards God Cloud. The black smoke was accompanied by an inexplicable heartbeat noise that pumped continuously, causing mysterious sound waves.

"Oh? Fragile Eye? An Ultimate Totem ability that allows one to mold their opponents?" God Cloud’s hands were placed together and then separated, before a dark green ball floated at the center of his palms suddenly, emitting a strange green light.

The circle floated in the middle of God Cloud’s chest, as thin transparent distortions began floating out of it, and landing on the empty spaces in the surroundings.

"Second activation, distortion!"

God Cloud said the Precious Heirloom’s activation commands.

The empty spaces near him suddenly began shaking slowly.

Both Woods’ black smoke and Veska’s Choking Blade halos were suddenly shaken up by the strange distortive powers.

Bang!!

Both powers collided with one another directly, before extinguishing themselves in a clearing nearby.

The moment the powers collided, the distortive waves from the distortive beads quickly stopped suddenly as well.

King of the Stars held a paintbrush, and the dancing flame on the burning paintbrush began to burn brighter.

"Dimensions of drawn destruction!"

His shadow spread out in a flash suddenly, as the tip of the paintbrush began shooting out black flames.

Shh…!

The paintbrush that King of the Stars held began to etch black drawings in the air, enveloping God Cloud’s surroundings. These drawings floated towards God Cloud like pieces of black ribbon, and also like countless black snakes.

Hiss!

The strands of black ribbon began weaving inside when the distortions stopped, and the place they flew towards was coincidentally the back of God Cloud’s head.

****************

A few thousand kilometers away, at an important checkpoint at the West Farm defense line.

The night sky was filled with stars, and the dots of blue light were like diamond fragments that embellished a black curtain, and were densely packed, as they drifted off far away quietly.

Under the starlight, the guards at the bright, lamp-lit checkpoints yawned a few times and were about to drift off to sleep.

Woo~~!!

Suddenly, an ear-piercing warning siren suddenly rang out from one of the checkpoints that were further away.

Bang!!

A large cloud of yellow fireworks exploded in the sky, resembling a yellow flower.

The guards were almost frightened to the point where they fell on the floor, as they wiped the saliva on the corners of their mouths frantically, and carefully deciphered the faraway warning signals. Next, they rushed towards the fence frantically and peered downwards.

Vaguely, they could see that the black checkpoint wall had collapsed, and was also faintly dotted with countless green and red spots of light, which were actually the eyes of numerous monsters.

The guards began to shiver and did not hesitate any longer.

Woo!!!!

The checkpoint sounded its ear-piercing alarm immediately.

***********

The sound of frantic footsteps.

Inside the Kovitan defense line’s main command room.

Throughout the corridor, a group of silhouettes in full-bodied black cloaks walked towards the main command room quickly.

The man at the front had a face that was ghostly pale, and his blinking eyelids were purple, while his lips were pitch-black. His collarbones on both sides were now connected to biochemical tube-like tracts, and the tracts were translucent and light yellow, while light yellow fluids flowed throughout them constantly, causing a large number of air bubbles to form occasionally. It gave off a strange quality.

The Totem Users and workers on the surrounding corridors would leave quickly with their heads downcast and bow the first moment they saw him. All of their eyes were filled with looks of horror and a touch of fear.

Bang!

The man pushed opened the metal door at the end of the corridor quickly and brought the others into the main command room.

Inside the command room, a middle-aged man in a white coat stood in front of a large map of the kingdom with his eyebrows knitted tightly. His surroundings were densely packed with office desks filled with over a hundred workers who were seated there and collected large amounts of information from the outside world.

When he saw that the main door had been pushed open, the middle-aged man furrowed his eyebrows and looked over.

"How’s the situation?" The man in black had a feminine voice that resembled a woman’s, but he did not have a woman’s gentleness, as he gave off a fierce, demon-like air instead.

"The situation is terrible! There were a total of forty-two checkpoints in the defense line that released reports at the same time!" The middle-aged man shook his head. "I’ve already passed the message to the kingdom, but I’m afraid that they have yet to respond until now."

"Don’t wait for them anymore, since the situation at the kingdom remains unchanged, I offer my services as the chief for life, and I will step forward to accept the guarding tasks of the entire defense line." The man in black’s tone was unquestionable.

"Vice chief, this matter is the responsibility of the National Service."

"It is not your responsibility anymore." The man in black reached his hand out, exposing his five slender fingers that were painted in a layer of purple nail polish, while a black bracelet embedded with diamonds was worn on his wrist, causing bell-like jingle noises when he moved.

"This is what the chief of the Geometry Service intended, as he is busy getting rid of the nests of the newly aberrated monsters, and as the situation on the surface is still not optimistic, I have volunteered myself to come here for a visit."

The man in white narrowed his eyes and glared at the other man. He knew that although the situation was urgent, once he gave in, it would troublesome for him if he wanted to regain total command from his opponent ever again.

"Idiot!! Why are you hesitating? What’s the use if the defense line was defeated by a stronger power?!" The vice chief snorted coldly. "According to the Secret Service‘s reports, currently outside the defense line, the five highly dangerous nests that were initially noticed are now moving quickly towards our direction, and our time is running out!"

"Highly dangerous nests?!!" The middle-aged man’s body shuddered. "Fine! I’ll give you transfer the system control rights to you immediately!"

He turned around.

"Martha!"

"Captain Colossus, sir," said a gentle woman’s voice within earshot of the men. "Martha number 2 at your service."

"Transfer my highest control rights to Lord Yesha, the vice chief of the Geometry Service!"

Bang!!!

Suddenly, a loud roar shook the ground. The quakes made it almost impossible for the command room to remain standing.

"The defense line… has been broken!!!"

The two highest commanders glanced at each other and saw a trace of fear in each other’s eyes.

"How is this possible?! The final defense contains twelve Spiritualized Totem Users, and is guarded by two Form 4 generals!! How could they not have released even one message?!"

Some of the staff officers stood up suddenly.

A large and powerful reaction is coming closer to us quickly!!" yelled one of the staff officers frantically, while he stared at the arching, translucent screen floating in front of him, as a large cluster of red dots rushed towards a blue area rapidly. One of the red dots was abnormally huge and took up half of the screen.

Both of the commanders shivered and rushed towards the screen that the man was monitoring.

"This… This is…!!??"

"Giant Stone Sculpture…!!!" The Vice Chief of the Geometry Service’s voice rang out bitterly. "Ender’s Giant Stone Sculpture…"

**********************

Plop…

A drop of fresh red blood dripped on the floor.

It dropped on the large pile of black ruins and rubble in between the palace.

The left side of Garen’s body had been expanded by a meter, as the ten meters long, large white sword cut a deep gash there, while the blade had almost sliced off one-third of his body.

On the border of the red wound, pools of fresh thick blood circled around constantly, trying to flow back into the wound, as a layer of thin flesh began growing at the corners quickly, attempting to heal the wound once again.

"Hee… Hee hee…" Garen laughed quietly.

Plop!!

He held the large sword in one hand and took a heavy step forward.

Boom!

A tearing sound could be heard, as the blade tore his long wound open again. The immense pain pierced Garen’s nerves constantly.

He ignored it and took a step forward again.

Bang!

The hand that Edin used to hold the hilt was sliced open suddenly, as fresh blood began to drip down the hilt slowly as before.

"It’s over…" He looked at Garen who was inching closer, and said softly.

The ring on the large silver ring sword stopped turning suddenly.

Garen’s footsteps halted suddenly as well, as the expression on his face began to froze.

Tch tch tch!

In that moment, endless amounts of blood began spraying out of Garen’s body.

There was a ‘bang’ before his entire body immediately exploded into a cloud of dark red blood mist.

Within the blood mist, countless white rose petals sliced him like blades continuously, strangling him, as if the blood mist was being sliced into even smaller pieces.

But Edin remained motionless, as he clenched the hilt tightly, while his gaze glared at the blood mist nearby.

"Ready?"

"Of course." The shadow of a girl who wore a crown of white roses appeared behind him slowly, except that her image only included her upper body, while she was holding a long white sword in her hand as well. "Such strong vitality!"

A shocked look appeared in the girl’s eyes as she looked at Garen’s blood mist.

"My White New Moon sword causes every opponent that touches the sword itself to be strangled by unending flower petals, and regardless of the strength of their vitality, they all die eventually." Edin closed his eyes as he was somewhat mentally tired by now.

"Let’s begin then." The girl nodded. "What a shame, another genius died at the mercy of your sword again."

"This is inevitable." Edin opened his eyes slowly with both hands still holding the hilt.

The girl stood behind him and held the hilt of his sword as well.

"End of the fantasy…"

"End of the fantasy!"

Their voices chorused with one another, as they raised their long swords at the same time.

"Silver Flowers!"

They placed their swords together suddenly, as the shadows of Edin and the girl became one as well, while four hands held the hilt of the sword tightly, and dashed towards the blood mist quickly.

Chapter 430: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Whoosh!!

Moon-white bands of light floated around Edin quickly, forming a large white ring.

The blood mist was covered by the ring. Inside, the sound of countless blades piercing and rubbing against each other could be heard.

It seemed as if countless blades were continuously piercing through the blood mist at every second inside the bands of light.

"Inside my halo of Silver Flowers, at every second, there are a thousand knives piercing through, equivalent to my maximum attack strength." Edin murmured, as he watched the blood mist become thinner the more it was sliced.

"Goodbye then… Nine-Headed Dragon Garen."

Tch!!

A bloody arm stabbed through his chest suddenly.

Edin’s pupils widened instantly.

The air seemed to have stopped moving…

His surroundings stopped moving as well.

Startled, Edin bowed his head, and watched the arm poking out of his chest, and noticed that the blood on the arm was as warm as his body.

His hand loosened its grip on the large sword immediately.

Crash!

"Edin!!!" The shadow of the girl behind him screamed immediately, and outstretched her arms to catch his body, but disappeared quickly instead.

A bloodied figure stood behind Edin, with three bloody glowing birthmarks on his forehead, and an armor-clad body that was dripping with a thick layer of blood.

Garen’s arm poked through Edin’s chest slowly, causing a large pool of blood to form. The armor and flesh rubbed against each other, and let out a horrifying squeaking sound.

Silently, the two large swords and the white moon halo exploded completely on their own, and turned into countless white rose petals, before being blown by the wind, and dancing around Edin and Garen endlessly.

The ruins seemed to be immersed in a shower of flowers for a brief moment.

Edin’s vision became blurry, but he could still see the hole in his own chest, and the color of the blood that flowed out.

It was a bright red color, tinged with glistening black accents. He could smell the weird scent that wafted from his blood, and although it was not a fishy smell, it was a strange stench that contained undertones of rotting.

"It seems that… I was poisoned from the beginning…" said Edin as a bittersweet smile appeared on his face.

"Five lives!" Garen’s voice rang out behind him. "You destroyed five of my lives. During the battle at Snowy Peak in the beginning, even God Cloud hadn’t killed me so many times…"

He paused, and continued speaking in a more solemn tone.

"Unfortunately, you only paid attention to my Nine Lives, and forgot that the Nine-Headed Dragon was actually a terrifying, toxic ancient creature."

"I never expected that… after serving Ivycius my whole life, that I would die in a place like this…" Edin raised his head painstakingly, and looked towards the moon in the sky, with a feeling of loss caused by his sudden epiphany.

"Dead?" A strange expression appeared on Garen’s face. "For a strong individual like yourself, I wasted lots of time and energy to hurt you, not just so I could kill you so quickly."

Edin was slightly shocked, and was about to open his mouth.

Suddenly, he felt a sinister icy foreign matter pouring out of his chest.

When the watery foreign matter touched his flesh, it melted and seeped into his internal organs rapidly.

He felt as if his life force was being frantically sucked out by this foreign matter, as his reasoning became weaker, while his awareness become blurrier.

Pfoo.

Edin knelt on the floor immediately, as his whole body was completely out of energy.

Garen stood where he was, clad in his black armor, as he looked at the messy palace in his surroundings, and noticed that the initially magnificent palace had completely turned into a rubbish dump, filled with rubble and residue.

The night wind blew over, and the air was still filled with traces of flowery parfum.

"Ivycius… I should have known earlier, that this bastard was actually the White Rose Juggernaut Ivycius."

Actually, the last thing that he said to Ivycius, was not true.

The Nine-Headed Dragon’s poison was not mainly used to kill one’s opponent, as the main purpose, was actually related to Secret Techniques.

After witnessing the moment when Edin strengthened his sword techniques, Garen had finally understood the parts that he could not see clearly before.

Secret Techniques could aid the evolution of Totems and could unearth the body’s inner blood flow, meanwhile for Totem evolution, it would form natural Secret Technique Roadmap exercises.

However, this was only one of the uses of Secret Techniques.

In this world, and the previous world, most of them were not blood flow Secret Techniques, but were rather life transforming, life evolving Secret Techniques!

Ivycius presented unprecedented sword techniques that seemed to be able to defeat Rose Totems, by integrating sword skills and Totem abilities, to achieve an incomparably powerful, yet new and different sword techniques.

"If it weren’t for that sudden breakthrough, perhaps this fight would have become a prolonged battle." Garen exhaled. "Wouldn’t you say so? Ivycius."

Ivycius’ corpse blinked mysteriously. His skin and body had blackened slightly, and he had apparently stood up again.

"No matter the reason, a win is a win, and a loss is a loss." He smiled bitterly and shook his head. "I lost, thinking I would die by your hands, but I never expected to lose my freedom instead."

"It’s always better to have hope."

"That’s true." Ivycius nodded seriously.

Garen walked around Ivycius.

This was his sole Demon Dragon quota.

Because his evolved Nine-Headed Demon Dragon was incomplete, because his ancient Nine-Headed Dragon lacked blood, he was only able to forge one with Demon Dragon abilities.

The Demon Dragon was actually a parasitic life form, because after it killed its enemy, it would preserve a large part of its opponent’s corpse, and within fifteen minutes, it would place its parasitic seeds into its opponents flesh to reanimate it, and turn it into the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon’s war tool.

As for the Demon Dragon’s self-beautifying exterior, that was merely an additional characteristic. Moreover, the beautifying aspect was something that was slowly perfected over time, and not something that could be achieved quickly.

Of course, Garen was not hoping that the beautifying would have any additional effects. He definitely did not harbor any longing for the ancient Nine-Headed Demon Dragon’s aesthetics, and as long as it maintained its current state, he would already be very satisfied.

Looking at Ivycius in front of him, Garen felt that they had some blood relations, as if they were close brothers, and moreover, he could now control his opponent’s body the same way he controlled Silver Totems.

"Do you feel anything?"

Ivycius shook his head.

"Looks like you’re using this type of ability for the first time as well."

"Of course. The Nine-Headed Demon Dragon has possessed this ancient parasitic Demon Dragon ability since ancient times." Garen looked at his opponent with a pitiful gaze. "I have two kinds of news that I’m about to tell you, one is good, while the other is bad, so which one would you like to hear first?"

Instantly, Ivycius realized that something was not right.

"Tell me the good news first, being happy under a burdenless situation is not a bad feeling."

Garen shook his head.

"The good news is, the current state of your body is much stronger than before, especially your regenerative abilities, one of the special abilities that I possess as the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon, Swallowed Lives, is something that you can share as well."

"I understand, the strength that you gain from consuming flesh, can also be used to revive me?"

Garen nodded certainly.

"The bad news is that your body will be changed by the Demon Dragon parasites, and I’ve heard that it will make you more beautiful… Of course, this version of beauty is defined by the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon… Don’t look at me, I don’t know the aesthetic values of the Nine-Headed Dragon either."

Ivycius’ face twitched, beauty in the eyes of the Nine-Headed Dragon…

During ancient eras, God knows what kind of beauty standards the Nine-Headed Dragon would hold. In the rare chance that it was a large backside or extra chest hair… What if he suddenly noticed an extra mouth growing below his penis, that would truly be bisexual reproduction.

Ivycius’ strong associating abilities clicked suddenly, and chills spread through his entire body.

"If that day really comes… I will kill you, before killing myself!!" he said, grinding his teeth.

To him, who loved vanity more than he loved his life, it was definitely more agonizing than death.

Garen was speechless.

"Try being more honest with yourself." He lifted Ivycius in one go. "Still trying to resist even after being captured by me? Looks like you’re not awake yet. Currently, your Totem is heavily damaged and your body is seriously injured, and you’re not much stronger than a little chick."

"Release me!!"

"If you shut up I might help you think of a plan later, if you keep talking, I’m just going to ignore you!"

Ivycius became honest suddenly.

At this moment, the flower garden on the side became messy as well.

When Garen carried Ivycius and brought him over, the entire flower garden had turned into a pile of wreckage after being burned by the large fire.

The corpses of more than twenty Black Fire Guards lay on the ground, while the Beckstone trio was nowhere to be seen. There were only traces of pools of almost dried up blood on the floor.

"Here!!" Garen looked over at the desolate and quiet ruins of the flower garden and roared loudly.

After waiting for a few minutes, frantic footsteps could be heard vaguely from far away.

A group of Black Fire Guards ran over from the borders of the ruins and bowed respectfully before Garen.

There were almost two hundred guards at first, but all that was left were the forty guards that stood before him.

Garen suddenly understood the tragedy of the current war, which involved him and Edin as well.

All of these elite guards were ranked at peak Form 2, and their scariest ability was self-explosion, and this self-explosion could be overlaid, and under the command of the Form 3 guards, was apparently strong enough to take appropriate revenge on the Beckstone trio, and was truly amazing.

"You’re probably very proud by now," Ivycius interjected suddenly. "Beckstone has two Form 4 professionals with him, and although you had to protect the Eleventh Royal Daughter, it must have been an amazing record to have been able to hurt them."

"Two Form 4? Does this mean that Beckstone has finally entered Form 4 already?" Garen asked quietly.

"Yes. Although I’m not familiar with them, as they were always lurking in the palace, I’ve heard that they were geniuses that have been cultivated from the society during these past years. However, I was always trying to break through to Form 5, and never had any intentions to return. But this time, someone came looking for me and wanted me to obstruct you for awhile, and since we were members of the same society, I grudgingly agreed."

"The person who came looking for you was a woman, right?" Garen interrupted.

Ivycius blushed, and stopped speaking.

"Breaking through Form 5? Well did you find any opportunities?"

"Before the battle with you, it would probably take at least a year or so. But after this fight, I have started to feel this threshold loosening?" Ivycius said proudly.

"Form 5… Perhaps, I’ve seen a sliver of hope…" Garen’s gaze drifted towards his Attribute Pane unconsciously.

In the Attribute Pane at the bottom of his vision, there were now Earth-shattering changes.

A clear blood-red symbol appeared at a far back position in the Attribute Pane. The Colour Changing Butterfly Totem that he had almost forgotten about had now disappeared completely, while the Neon Butterfly that he had gotten from Teacher Emin, which he later evolved into a Totem, was now completely nowhere to be seen.

Meanwhile, strange changes had occurred in Garen’s Attribute Pane.

‘Strength 14. Agility 10. Vitality 10. Intelligence 10. Potential 22117%. Obtained Luminarist qualifications.’

Secret Technique --

Myriad Water Jasper Technique: Hallucination Toxins have been strengthened to the next level (Originates from the Color Changing Butterfly Totem)’

"Apparently… It’s exactly as I guessed…" A bout of sudden realization flashed in Garen’s eyes.

Chapter 431: Pursue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

If mining type Secret Techniques regarded the vertices of blood vessels as their endpoints, then evolving Secret Techniques in the foundations of blood vessels would be able to take a step forward and improve the body, in order to create a method for new life methods.

Certainly, the Myriad Water Jasper Technique was an evolving Secret Technique like that.

It would swallow and absorb Totem abilities to reach its goal of evolving itself. For an ancient martial art like this to exist in this world, only a stepping stone would be required.

Garen concentrated and felt the powers of the Myriad Water Jasper Technique for a moment.

This set of Secret Techniques possessed its own set of attack methods but was obviously impractical in the Luminarist world. Garen used cloud exercises, and his own Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills to attack. But the Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills were a form of martial arts that used the Divine Statue Technique as its core, thus, using the Myriad Water Jasper Technique with it felt wrong, as its power would be insufficient.

"If I was able to train my New Moon Sword Skills to the highest level, I would definitely break through Form 5," said Ivycius quietly, as he stood on the sidelines.

"New Moon Sword Skills?" Garen was slightly shocked.

"I named it myself," Ivycius nodded. "I obtained this set of sword skills from some relics, and they were once used to practice strengthening one’s body, but I never expected that, once I combined it with a Form 4 Totem, there would be an immensely strong effect."

"Could you let me see it?" Garen’s heart trembled.

"Originally, I had destroyed it, but I could relay the information to you verbally," Ivycius nodded, because for Garen, he was instinctively unable to reject him from the depths of his heart. Although he was slightly surprised at first, he immediately understood that this was probably the consequences of the Demon Dragon.

Both of them told all of the Black Fire Guards to fall back, before they began to pursue Beckstone and the others by following the tracks that they left behind, while Ivycius told him about the origins of the sword skill practices.

The more he listened, the more frightened Garen felt.

If all the normal people of this world were practicing a normal, auraless Secret Techniques, then the sword skills that Ivycius possessed, were obviously exercises that closely resembled high level Secret Techniques.

Except that he was unlike himself, without the ability to absorb Totems, in order to strengthen the effects of his original Secret Technique exercises.

Or perhaps this fusion upgrade, was originally just an effect of Garen’s abilities.

Sudden realisation flashed through Garen’s mind, if it was like the previous world, superimposed strength like this would be able to allow him to start off at a lower starting point, and upgrade to a higher level quickly.

When comparing the Myriad Water Jasper Technique and Ivycius’ New Moon Sword Skills, Garen shockingly realised that the former was not as complicated as the New Moon Sword Skills.

Regardless if he was looking from the description of the Secret Technique, or the difficulty to practice it, the New Moon Sword Skills exceeded the former greatly. Of course, the most likely probability was that the level of the New Moon Sword Skills was higher than the Myriad Water Jasper Technique.

"Looks like this world is also filled with high levelled Secret Techniques." Excitement began to bubble up slowly inside Garen’s heart.

"Have you passed these sword skills to anyone else?" He looked at Ivycius.

"Only one previous disciple," Ivycius shook his head. "Unfortunately, I don’t know his whereabouts anymore. However, it is not only myself but many other Ultimate Form 5 strong individuals, that possess their own types of attack methods. The Form 5 level is the level where the Totem and main bodies fuse, and the Totem User themselves will be affected by the Totem, and while some of them use it to get rid or suppress these effects, others use them to strengthen the effects, Thus, these ancient attack methods that were obtained from the relics became more popular to this day."

"You’re saying, that there are people in Form 5 who have these kind of Secret Techniques?"

"Secret Techniques? This phrase is quite suitable. That is true, from my knowledge, there are some people in Form 5 who have these Secret Techniques," Ivycius nodded. "Secret Techniques were truly the best method for us to unleash our abilities."

The two men spoke as they walked through the palace quickly.

Inside the black palace, the Beckstone trio left a rotting bloody stench along the way, that kept appearing throughout the ruins.

Under the large Magic Array that covered the palace, they were apparently unable to exit the palace grounds.

After they left the ruins caused by the fierce battles, Garen and Ivycius led the Black Fire Guards to pursue the path that carried the bloody scent.

Beckstone and the others had obviously suffered serious injuries, and along the way, they would often see palace guards that had been shot dead. However, although the situation was such, every time they moved, the smell of blood from the three people would become stronger.

Fortunately, Avic had dispersed a large amount of the palace’s Tactical Defense Formations before he took action so that each palace had a specific Tactical Defense Formation, and although it was not extremely powerful, it was enough to deflect some of the effects of the fierce battle. Thus, most of the royal family hid in the deeper parts of the palace.

The palace grounds were completely quiet; those who wanted to hide were hidden already, while only a few of them remained outside.

Garen and Ivycius ran over, and noticed that the corpses of the guards and maids had decreased.

The palace area was at the back of the royal palace and was connected to mountains and cliffs. The area was full of slopes and led towards the Yellow-Eyed Black Crow’s nest.

Going up the sloping grounds, Garen suddenly caught wind of their plan.

"They’re trying to ride the Yellow-Eyed Black Crow to escape!"

On top on one of the palace walls, Garen crouched down and reached his hand out to reach for a trace of blood on the ground gently.

He placed it in front of his nose and sniffed.

"It’s right in front." He stood up, as his eyes looked towards a black palace in the top right corner of his vision. "This is the women’s quarters, they left no longer than two minutes ago."

"What are you planning to do?" Ivycius asked quietly. "Kill them?"

"For publicly kidnapping the Eleven Royalties and the royal family members, regardless of who they are, they are doomed to die," said Garen sternly.

He looked around his surroundings and noticed that the Yellow-Eyed Black Crow’s grey nest was in a faraway area front of him.

"Let’s go. The Magic Array is still untouched, a sign that they haven’t found a way to escape yet, so as long as they remain within the Magic Array, everything can go as planned."

Both of them walked towards the middle of the palace slowly, one in front of the other, and began rushing when they reached the stone steps. Every step seemed to be excruciatingly slow, but in reality, they were both crossing great distances, at a frightening speed.

At every moment, Garen would pay attention to the movements in his surroundings, to see if the three people were hiding inside the palace grounds.

Suddenly, a ray of silver light burst out of the ground on his right, and from the corner of his vision, Garen could see it shooting towards him, as if it was about to pierce through the back of his head.

Tch! Bang!!

Garen raised his fingers and clasped the silver light gently, before realising that it was a thin, sharp silver needle.

He increased the force applied by his fingers, and slapped them together, causing the silver needle to break suddenly. It fell on the ground.

Garen realised suddenly that a large black shadow had appeared right in front of him.

The black shadow covered him completely, and the last sliver of moonlight from the night sky was concealed as well.

In a nearby area in front of him, a large grey stone man burst out of the ground suddenly.

The body of the stone man was entirely grey, and his body was made up of countless huge rocks, as it many grey stone balls had been glued together. Its large body was at least ten meters tall.

Roar!!!

The stone man turned towards Garen and let out a fierce roar suddenly, and although it was silent, its large black mouth kept spitting out strong winds.

"Giant Stone Formation? Looks like the person on Beckstone’s side is a formation professional," Ivycius sighed behind him.

"Giant Stone Formation?" Garen sneered.

The stone man raised his right fist suddenly, and the giant right fist, with a diameter of five to six meters, suddenly came crashing down near Garen, as if it were trying to crush him into meat sauce all at once.

At the same time, Garen brandished his right fist as well, and waved it openly.

Bang!!!!

The ground was reverberated with strong quakes, as the floor beneath Garen’s feet split down the middle, spreading large unruly cracks everywhere.

Roar!!

The stone man’s loud painful roars sounded again, as his entire right arm broke into fragments instantly.

Banging sounds were heard twice, as he took two steps back, while his entire body shivered continuously, as if something was shaking him continuously.

There was a crash, and the stone man collapsed instantly. A large number of boulders came crashing down, smashing the ground, and overturning a large pile of rubble and dust.

Garen sighed and brought his right hand back, while most of the heavy black armor on his body had cracked already. His entire body had been shaken up, so his armor flew off suddenly and fell to the ground in the distance.

While only wearing a layer of black tights on the inside, Garen walked past the stone man’s body and rushed over towards the Yellow-Eyed Black Crow’s cliff again.

Ivycius followed closely behind, and glanced at the stone man on the ground, and although this was not his first time seeing it, he was still shocked by Garen’s frighteningly powerful strength.

In between the black palace area, two people who were dressed in black and white respectively, were like two small dots who were rapidly passing through the palace, and they passed the plaza, forest, and statue garden without stopping at all as they rushed towards the Yellow-Eyed Black Crow’s nest on the cliff hurriedly.

Lots of stone men appeared endlessly, and each time they were obliterated with one of Garen’s punches. This was only able to delay Garen momentarily.

*********

On top of the cliff

The Beckstone trio surrounded a gigantic Yellow-Eyed Black Crow. The exterior of the Black Crow was covered by a thin layer of golden light that resembled a piece of protective film.

Beard heard the dull ramming noises that were constantly coming from below, and his eyelids jumped around madly. Whenever the sound echoed over, it meant that one of his Giant Stone Formations were being violently destroyed.

"Here! They’re here already! They must have realised our intentions by now! We need to hurry up and resolve the Magic Array screen!!" He turned his head and looked towards Beckstone frantically.

This young genius’ face was now becoming pale, and his chest was rising and falling violently.

"Don’t panic… Don’t panic! You absolutely cannot panic!!" he seemed to be murmuring to himself, while he took deep breaths continuously. "There is definitely a way… This golden screen is also part of the Magic Array’s cover, and I remember seeing it someway before… I remember…!"

Beard could hear that the exploding noises from below were getting nearer, and it wasn’t just him; the Eleventh Royal Daughter had been frightened ‘til her face turned white.

"All of you need to get on the Black Crow King’s back now!!!" Beckstone yelled loudly.

"Brother Stone!" yelled the Eleventh Royal Daughter tearfully. She was swooped up by Beard in one swift movement, as he dashed towards the empty slot on the back of the Black Crow.

Beckstone did not hear anything, and his eyes were illuminated by flashes of silver light continuously, as if countless messages were flowing in rapid calculation.

From the beginning when the White Bird was obstructed, and unable to fly out of the palace, he had already begun to hurriedly search for a way to get rid of the giant Magic Array above the palace. Until now, he was still unable to locate the thinnest part of it.

Upon hearing that the explosions from below were getting nearer, Beckstone’s mind grew more panicked.

"Don’t panic! We will definitely find a way, surely!!"

"Eleventh Highness, please don’t be tricked by those two treacherous villains, their goal is to capture you to coerce His Highness into becoming Terraflor Society’s bargaining chip! In this world, His Highness is your only relative, and the person who has truly treated you the best," said a man’s voice in an unusually sincere voice, and while his tone was cordial, for some unknown reason, he gave off a cold, snake-like, terrifying feeling.

"Come back… Your body is already covered with protective Spritualized Tactics, and once you stimulate it, I will protect you immediately!"

Upon hearing the voice, Tina widened her eyes, and felt chills throughout her whole body while she was locked tightly in Beard’s grasp.

"To think that a genius like that would actually be placed under the command of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists!" Beard’s face was pale, as he smashed his fist against the Black Crow King’s feathers, but was steadily blocked by the golden halo. "He’s relying on Spirit Light to determine our location!"

Although Tina had seen Garen many times, the other man was always smiling and welcoming, and his actions were always polite and warm, he also had a handsome appearance, gentle attitude and manners, and powerful strength. All of these were enough to capture the heart of an average girl. But nobody knew why, every time Tina saw Garen, she could feel a cold, terrifying, and suffocating feeling coming from him.

She knew that this was part of her royal bloodline, as she had inherited premonitions and talents that would lead to warnings.

"He can’t find us now! The Yellow-Eyed Black Crow King has four heads in total, and each head has been designated to four different areas of the cliff, making it the bird with the fastest speed. Even if he were to use the fastest way to get here, it would take him five minutes at least!" Beard said quickly. "Stone!"

Beckstone stood beside the Black Crow King, as the silver in his eyes had increased, and had almost accumulated into one pile.

Tch!

Blood spurted out of both his eyes.

Woo!

He closed both of his eyes tightly, as his figure staggered backwards.

Suddenly.

"I’ve thought of it!!" A joyful look appeared on his face, and he could not help but yell loudly.

************

On the ground below the mountain, Garen raised his head suddenly and looked towards a cave at the extreme right corner. His bright red eyeballs were like terrifying dragon’s eyes.

"Found you… Hehe."

There was a hissing noise, as he turned into a black shadow instantly, and dashed towards the cave.

Ivycius stood at his original spot without following him, pursed his lips, and smiled bitterly.

"What terrifying five senses… President, this time I really cannot help you anymore…"

Chapter 432: Pursue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Within the cave.

Beckstone jumped onto the Black Crow's back while holding onto Eleven's smaller hand.

"Eleven, everything depends on you now! As long as you find the connecting point in the Magic Array, Uncle and I will be able to burst out if we combine our strengths!"

Eleven's little face was deathly pale, and her face showed that she was completely at a loss.

"Calm yourself and come! I believe that you can do it." Although Beckstone was panicking, he tried to relax his tone.

He knew that he and his uncle had received heavy injuries from the self-destruction of the Black Fire Guards. In this state, he definitely could not face the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon as his opponent. However, he determinedly made sure that his appearance was not too worried.

Eleven's eyes were filled with tears, but she nodded determinedly.

She closed her eyes and began to detect the weakest parts of the Magic Array's joining points. Strong warnings of danger ravaged through her and disrupted her concentration, as she tried to perform her premonitions.

"I can do it… Can definitely do it… Definitely…" Eleven chanted it repeatedly in her mind.

Crash!!

Another loud noise rang out, and the source of this noise was much closer as compared to the others.

The expressions of the trio changed.

At this moment, Eleven's eyes shot open suddenly, and she grabbed Stone's hand and pointed to the front.

"I felt it! It's there!!" she yelled loudly while in tears.

"Your Highness, I went through so much trouble to find you…" echoed the man's cold voice from outside the hole suddenly; he was close!!

"Go!!"

Beckstone roared loudly. The bodies of the three people suddenly exploded in blinding golden halos.

Crash!!!

The golden halo around the Black Crow King's body collapsed suddenly. The gigantic Black Crow opened both of its eyes, abruptly spread its wings and flew towards the cave in front at lightning speed.

Countless golden lines appeared in the air suddenly and wrapped around the Black Crow King tightly, but were immediately broken by Beckstone whose eyes were still bleeding.

Caw!!

The Black Crow King blurred into a black long straight line as it flew towards the cave platform.

Crash!!

Copious amounts of black smoke lingered, as the black figure shot into the cave.

"Trying to run?!"

Garen's right fist clawed at the Black Crow King.

Nine blood-colored dragon heads circled around and flew out of his arm, before intercepting the Black Crow.

Tch!

Unexpectedly, the Black Crow King pumped its wings and in a burst of speed, barely evaded the claws of the Nine-Headed Dragon. It rushed out of the cave, entered the platform, and shot towards the night sky.

A few black feathers drifted in the air slowly.

Garen followed closely behind, and his feet exploded suddenly, as the great reactionary force pushed him forth like an arrow fired at the Black Crow King.

At this moment, a giant black stone man stood up right in front of him suddenly and blocked the path in front of him.

"Get lost!"

The giant stone man's chest was punched by Garen. But his speed had been drastically reduced.

The Black Crow King took the opportunity to finally fly off the platform, leaving the cliff for good.

"Today's revenge will be remembered by us at Terraflor Society!!" Beard's voice echoed angrily from the sky.

Garen rushed towards the platform cave, and both of his eyes were bloodshot. Suddenly, he puffed his chest out. His entire chest was so puffed up, it seemed as though it was about to explode. The Nine-Headed Dragon's shadow floated out behind him steadily.

Suddenly, his mouth gaped open.

Roar!!!!

A cloud of terrifying black smoke accompanied the loud roars that echoed out of the entrance of the cave suddenly.

The black smoke turned into a replica of the Nine-Headed Dragon before it flew at the Black Crow King in the sky.

Caw!!

The Black Crow King roared in frustration and had barely passed through a layer of golden light film in the sky, before gliding down and falling in a faraway area unsteadily.

Behind it, the Nine-Headed Dragon that was releasing black smoke was obstructed by the golden light film and howled angrily in the sky.

Garen grasped the sides of the cave with both of his hands, as his bloodshot eyes glared at the Black Crow King in the sky angrily, while a dragon's shadow flashed across his face.

*****************

Underground Blood Jade Palace

There was a ringing crash as God Cloud's right arm fell on the floor and shattered into countless pieces, like a cracked clay container.

He held his broken arm tightly while a green ball of flesh floated in front of him slowly, emitting a faint tragic green light.

"Your decision to enter the Blood Jade Palace alone was your greatest mistake," said Avic coldly while he stood at far away. "I had initially thought that my arrangements were already set, but I never expected that a conclusion like this would happen in the end." He looked at the ruined surroundings of the palace and took a deep breath.

The staff that had belonged to the captain of the Silver Knights, Woods, had broken, and he was now crawling on the ground while a blood pooled around his body; he was on the brink of death.

The Geometry Service's King of the Stars held a paintbrush with an extinguished flame, while droplets of blood continuously trickled from his wrist and dripped between the slits of his fingers. His forehead was covered in sweat.

The only perfect one was Veska, who held the Choking Blade in his hand while his surroundings were wrapped in a large dark blue sea water illusion that imprisoned God Cloud tightly.

He glared at God Cloud's chest where there was a wound, a very strange wound indeed.

It resembled a painting that had been partially erased as if there was an additional broken layer on God Cloud's chest, and between the top and bottom halves of his body, it seemed like a block had been removed, causing him to lack a large chunk of flesh.

The strangest part was that although his face was pale, he continued to move like normal.

"Drawn Removal… Not surprising that it's King of the Stars' strongest ultimate move!" God Cloud bowed his head and looked at the wound on his chest. "Too bad you can't move, if not, even if it was me, we would only be able to fail and return."

"Right now you're gravely injured, as long as I continue to pin you down with the Distortive Beads, to keep you here, you will die sooner or later!" said Veska coldly.

But no one expected God Cloud to smile mysteriously.

"Actually… From the beginning, victory and defeat were already determined…"

Puff!!!

Something fell down right after he spoke.

Not far away, Avic clutched his chest suddenly as he hacked, and fresh blood spurted out of his mouth.

A look of disbelief appeared in his eyes while he glared at God Cloud. He wanted to open his mouth, but was unable to make a sound.

Everyone had been stunned by the abrupt changes that occurred almost instantaneously.

Avic's blood splattered on the palace floor, causing a large pile of broken bricks to be dyed red.

"Your Highness!!"

Veska finally came to his senses and yelled loudly while trying to turn around and rush over.

"Don't!!" Avic finally roared at the cost of coughing up another mouthful of blood. "Stop him! Kill him!!"

Veska's pupils widened. All this time he'd assumed that everything was under his control, yet today, twice in a row, he'd completely misjudged the situation...

If His Highness Avic died…

He was too afraid to think of the consequences that would follow, Obscuro Society had already arranged everything, and definitely would not have any oversights in the end!

"God Cloud!!!" He spun around abruptly, the murderous intentions in his eyes revealing how close he was to killing him.

A calm smile appeared on God Cloud's face.

"From the very beginning, I had begun to meddle with His Highness's food and drink, putting in a medicine that could not be considered poison, as a flavor enhancer. But it wasn't His Highness that was the only one eating it, I ate it with him as well."

He seemed like he was reliving certain memories.

"This medicine does not have negative side effects, but it will benefit the body instead… Except that, no one knew. Once you consume too much of this medicine, the benefits will become excessive. For the average person, these benefits do not pose any danger. Of course, as long as His Highness did not use Original Heirlooms, there would be no danger at all. Even if he did use Heirlooms, there are only minimal repercussions, and any high-leveled Totem User would be able to calmly resist and even become immune to them."

"But… But unfortunately, His Highness is a normal person…" The smile on God Cloud's face became even more serene. "For a Totem User, there would only be minor repercussions. But for a normal person, it can be fatal."

King of the Stars stepped backward, and clutched the wall tightly without a sound, while his eyes coldly surveyed the scene that was playing out before him.

"The overall situation has been set, this encounter has been a great loss…"

He studied God Cloud carefully while he murmured.

"This time, we lost a round. God Cloud of Obscuro Society… Next time, it will not be this simple..."

Without a sound, his body melded into the black stone wall behind him. Less than a few seconds later, his entire body had disappeared completely into the stone wall, without a trace.

Woo!!!!

Suddenly, a deafening siren echoed throughout the air from the Kingdom.

The smile on God Cloud's face became more obvious.

"My plan has finally come into action on all fronts!"

Both Veska and Avic's faces had become abnormally ugly.

The warning siren of the Kingdom was only sounded when the Kingdom faced extremely dangerous threats, and this time it had been raised at once.

"Veska! Don't die!!" Avic choked out his last words painfully, and without hesitation, he turned around and staggered towards the outside of the palace to escape.

"Still trying to struggle? How funny." God Cloud had no restraints, as he had also been gravely injured, was pinned down strongly by Veska, and was unable to move.

******************

The front of the Kingdom, at the blue waterfall large canyon

On the dark yellow ground, the canyons seemed like an inflamed black wound that divided the plains into two parts.

The canyons near the Kovitan Empire were on one side, and the endless pale blue light screen seemed to reach towards the edges of the horizon.

The light screen stretched up high into the clouds, forming a large broad physical screen, that emitted bright blue glowing lights.

On the left side of the light screen, there was an ocean of multicolored monsters. There were countless Black Flying Dragons, White Bats, and Dead Babies howling and screaming.

A huge number of Dual-Headed White Wolves raised their heads towards the sky and howled, while their entire bodies were burning with white flames. They looked like little white mushrooms in the monster herds.

In the sky, a few Giant Angel Stone Sculptures circled around.

Each Angel Sculpture had pearl grey stone wings growing out of their backs and were holding Dual Stone Swords in their hands, while their eyes resembled deep black whirlpools.

They were at least fifty meters tall and their bodies were pale grey, and they stood as the largest monsters in the sea of monsters. When they came down, they landed on the ground with one foot and would end up stomping and killing countless smaller monsters that were unable to dodge in time.

Looking at the sea of monsters that stretched towards the ends of the horizon, it seemed as though their numbers were limitless.

The thin blue light screen seemed like it would break when touched, and looked extremely weak.

The number of Totem Users behind the light screen, when compared to the monsters, were completely overwhelmed; they did not have even ten thousand in numbers, while some of them had been assigned to guard the entire back of the light screen as well.

The faces of the Totem Users were as dull as the ground, and some of them had already fled in secret.

"It won't be able to withstand any longer…"

At the headquarters of the light screen, the Captain of the Colossus Corps of the National Service stood in the command room quietly and looked outside the ring-shaped glass window at the enormous Giant Angel Stone Sculptures on the opposite side.

He crossed his arms and stood there, with an unspeakably calm expression on his face.

"Perhaps there is another way, as long as we persevere until we get support from the Kingdom…" the Vice Chief of the Geometry Service said quietly beside him.

"We can't make it…" the Colossus Captain said plainly, "This Four-Headed Giant Angel Stone Sculpture can't even be held back by the defense line. We don't even need to mention the King of the Nest behind."

He turned around.

"I brought up the defense line plan, and the Three Departments offered an abundance of manpower and financial resources. I originally hoped that it would be able to become mankind's final barrier. How unfortunate."

"What are you planning to do?"

"Life is full of ups and downs." the Colossus Captain reached his hand out and looked at the wrinkles that had already formed on his skin, while an unspeakable calmness appeared on his face. "This life of mine has already been very exciting."

He put on his white cloak meticulously and pinned a golden button on his left shoulder.

"A person's life will always have some things that require perseverance!"

Vice Chief's face expression changed slightly.

"You're mad! Do you know how many monsters there are outside? Ten million, twenty million, one hundred million? Two hundred million!!"

"I'm the strongest wall in the Kingdom," said the Colossus Captain plainly. "I once swore to His Highness, that on every day I existed, both the Empire and the Kingdom would never fall! This was my promise, and was also my resolve."

He took a big step out of the command room, while countless silver lines formed on his hands slowly, forming the outline of a pure silver triangular shield.

"Madman!! Georbas, you've lost your mind!!" The Vice Chief's chest puffed up immediately.

Boom!!!

The large blue screen suddenly tore and a gap appeared, as Giant Angel Stone Sculptures raised their enormous swords, and began to squeeze through the gap. Countless smaller-sized monsters escaped from the outer parts of the gap, like a flood bursting through.

The Totem Users who had been guarding the area turned around and fled quickly, none of them attempting to quell the torrent of monsters. They were like ants on a bursting dam that were facing the floods but could not resist it at all.

"Giant Sculpture! Giant Sculpture! Giant Sculpture!!"

A deafening roar echoed from the top of the command room.

A white human-like figure appeared in the sky and was closely followed by more than a hundred other white silhouettes, and all of them held triangular silver shields and flew directly towards the sea of monsters.

In an instant, countless silver lines appeared on the shields of the flying battalion and connected together, weaving an incomparably large triangular silver shield. It collided with the gap furiously.

The several hundred meters long giant shield was illuminated with silver lights as it collided with the Giant Angel Stone Sculpture violently.

Boom!!!

At that moment, it was as though the world had been purged of sound.

Chapter 433: Crisis 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black cloud in the sky was suddenly rent apart.

A huge silver triangular shield descended and merged together with the blue light wall.

It looked as though the Light Wall had an additional silver shield from afar.

The entire Light Wall was completely covered by it.

When the totem users who had been running for their lives noticed this scene, they started cheering. Suddenly.

Boom!!

There was a loud boom and another section of the Light Wall was destroyed by the Giant Angel Stone Sculpture, and a huge amount of creatures came flooding through the gap.

Roar~~~!!!

A wolf's howl echoed from the other side of the barrier, sounding as if it originated from the sky.

With the combination of heavy footsteps, what appeared walking towards the Light Wall was a white giant wolf standing at nearly thirty meters tall. Its rear was something similar to an anaconda slithering on the floor. White flames were flickering on its body, yet this illusive fire didn't seem to be burning anything at all.

The giant wolf was walking through the sea of creatures, similar to a large creature walking over the ants; every step it took would flatten multiple smaller creatures. As it set its gaze onto the silver triangular shield in front of it, its pace gradually hastened and it started racing towards it.

In the end, it went wild and leaped towards the triangular shield.

Kaboom!!!

The giant wolf collided with the triangular shield.

*************

Garen observed Beckstone and his teammates who'd managed to burst through the golden veil, on the Black Crow King which was slowly gliding down far away while black smoke circled around its body.

"The Black Crow King is definitely something. It didn't fall immediately after being poisoned by mine and its own poisonous smoke." Garen muttered.

How did they find the flaw in this Magic Array? He didn't understand how they did it. Although this Magic Array wasn't strong, it wasn't something that could be broken within a short amount of time. He didn't expect Beckstone and his teammates to dispel it in such a short amount of time.

As the thought of the Kingdom in danger flashed through his mind, Garen felt that this incident might very well be related towards the Eleven Royalties.

Ivycius was still waiting where he'd been after he came down from the precipice. Although he was halfway through a full recovery, his totem was still heavily damaged so he didn't really have any strength. He could do nothing but be a bystander.

"What should I do now?" Ivycius asked himself. As a demon dragon, his life force was directly linked to Garen.

"Idea?" Garen was emotionless. "Beckstone and his two teammates have been poisoned by my poison smoke and as totem users, they are able to resist the poison and return towards the Terraflor Society. However, as commoners, the Eleven Royalties would have no chance to withstand it and would definitely go to where they could possible dispel the poison in the shortest time."

"The place where could possible detox?"

"Do you know who is the best at dispelling poison in the Terraflor Society?"

Ivycius shook his head. "However, I do know that the Terraflor Society and Obscuro Society have temporarily allied together."

Garen suddenly smiled.

"Let's go, I will help you and recover your injuries!"

"Do you know who is it going to be?" Ivicius was slightly stunned.

"You'll know when the time comes." Garen turned around and headed towards the Palace. "Let's go help His Majesty!"

It didn't matter to him if Avic was dead or alive. His main objective was to obtain the Original Heirloom that was in Avic's possession! It was what Garen really wanted.

He'd done everything he could to the best of his abilities. If history were to remain the same…

***************

Avic had arrived in a secluded area within the Palace as he stumbled with blood trickling out from his mouth.

Just as he entered the main hall, countless purple bats flew over his head and completely blocked the entrance of the main hall.

He turned his head around and glanced at them before he walked directly to the throne and slammed on the hand rest with his right hand.

Buzz!

He immediately sank to the underground at a very fast pace. After he disappeared, a new identical throne resurfaced and everything appeared normal once again.

Avic was sitting alone on the throne as he went downwards via a cylindrical tube-like tunnel.

"Your Majesty Avic, the third layer of defense of the West Farm has been breached. The third layer of defense of the West Farm has been…"

A mechanical female voice could be heard inside the tube.

"Aisha, tell Georbas… to return immediately. We need to focus our strength and defend the Kingdom's main city! Gah!" Avic wiped off the blood beside his lips with extreme difficulty. As he spoke too fast, he immediately vomited a mouthful of blood again and dyed his royal clothes red.

"Unable to contact General Georbas." The girl immediately responded.

Avic was stunned as he felt hopeless.

"I knew it… Georbas… I didn't expect you leave me…"

The throne soon brought him into a small secret room deep in the underground.

The secret room was completely empty without any sorts of decoration at all and it looked like a natural cave.

A stone pillar resembling a black hourglass was at the center of the cave, and on top of it was a small black glass ball levitating on it.

Avic's face was completely pale at this point as he mustered all his strength to get down from the throne and walked towards the spherical glass.

"Did you hope to annihilate the Royal Household of the Kovitan Empire? Did you think it would be that easy?!!" He started to laugh like a maniac.

As he reached the side of the black glass ball, he grabbed ahold of it with his hand.

This fist-sized ball was levitating up and down on his hand.

"Although there was no successful prototype, perhaps it's enough…" He looked at this item that he'd been obsessed with for the past decade. His face was filled with emotions such as remorse, conflict, despair, and comfort.

"It's very unfortunate… If only I had another year…"

Clank!!

The spherical glass was shattered into millions of pieces as it was thrown fiercely onto the ground.

A cloud of black-purple smoke spread out from the glass ball and turned into lights as it spread everywhere silently.

Avic tried to laugh as he opened his mouth wide but he didn't utter any sound as blood started to flow out of his mouth. He stopped moving and breathing on the spot and at the same time, one of his rings on his hand started to lose its light.

***********

Inside the Blood Jade Palace.

A blue gas suddenly spread about in all directions like flowing water.

The Choking Blade in Veska's hand broke and it was as if he suddenly aged by a decade. What was originally a sixty-plus-year-old man suddenly looked like he was in his nineties as his face paled.

With both of his hands completely chopped off, God Cloud rushed out of the palace in the direction which Avic escaped.

The whole Blood Jade Palace behind him exploded and started to shake and was completely toppled down within a matter of minutes.

God Cloud was here not just to assassinate but to obtain the Original Heirloom as well.

As he followed Avic's scent, he didn't slow down her pace at all and soon arrived at the secluded area of the palace.

The groups of bats at the door shot towards her like raindrops. However, all the bats were bent to behind her back as a green light flashed in the air.

Without any hesitation, God Cloud rushed into the secluded palace.

At the moment he entered the palace.

The Defense Tactic of the whole Kingdom started to turn red. What was originally a colorless and transparent Defense Tactic Formation was dyed in layers of red halos.

Without any warning, two luxurious looking buildings in the city fired two rays of light, one white and the other yellow, directly at the palace.

The current palace had used up all of its formations before the two lights landed on the palace. The light rays turned into two white-haired old men the moment they touched the floor.

One of them was thin, tall and had very thin eyebrows as if he was malnutrition.

The other man was fat and was in a yellow robe. He had a square yellow crystal placed onto his chest. The crystal was crystal clear and strangely, it seemed to have countless of faces flashing by at all times inside it.

The expression of these two men was very stern as they looked at each other in the eye.

As they landed on the floor, a strong tremble came from below the palace.

The ground kept shaking as if there was something big rushing out from the ground.

The main hall started to tremble and the pebbles from above kept falling to the ground.

Cracks started to appear on the ground of the already deserted palace and propagated into multiple cracks.

"His Majesty is in trouble!!" One of the two old men voiced out and rushed into the entrance which led to the underground of the hall at the same time.

Cracks could be seen everywhere along the way, revealing countless corpses from the Royal Guard and Black Fire Guard and it was then that both of them started to panic.

Voices could be heard outside the area as all the remaining forces of the Kingdom arrived.

In some buildings of the palace which were completely unharmed, the female guards who were in hiding came out as they protected the princes and princesses, who were all terrified.

Princess Liv was the first one to walk out of the palace with all the guards protecting her from all directions. She was ecstatic as she saw two men passing by with great speed.

"Two Lords, please wait up!!"

Unfortunately, none of them responded to her and these two old men immediately disappeared, leaving their afterimages behind and gradually disappeared.

The Princess was stunned as her royal instinct told her that Kovitan was in serious trouble.

She stood still as she started thinking.

"Sister Night, sister Ning. Please contact the three feudal lords and it would be good if you could get ahold of Palace Master Garen as well!"

The two women by her side heeded the order and disappeared immediately. Spiritualized light glowed on their bodies as they left. Surprisingly, both of them were Spiritualized Elites.

The princess promptly decided that she would send out two of her strongest elites out in hope that they could get in contact with the powerful individuals that she had relation with.

She then stared at where the two Grand Dukes had vanished.

"Let's go! Let's go to the MingJi Temple!" The princess shouted.

"Her Highness, shouldn't we go to see how His Majesty is doing?" A middle-aged man asked softly.

"We are not qualified for that." Princess was unexpectedly calm. "It doesn't matter who wins or lose. What we should do now is wait and react accordingly."

**************

As both of the grand dukes arrived the palace, two figures appeared behind the palace temple as well.

Three individuals in heavy white armor gathered beside the two men.

Ivycius had a white cloak on him. He looked energetic as totem light flowed through his body. He had recovered all of his strength within a short amount of time.

Garen stood beside him as he smiled wryly.

In order to recover Ivycius's true strength, he had used all of the energy that he had been accumulating for the past few days and he only managed to recover half of Ivycius strength. This made him understood how beneficial the Dragon's Heart was.

If it was solely based on the strength of absorbing life force, It would be an astronomical value for him to recover himself.

One had to realize that the amount of life force he had given to Ivycius was enough to fully heal himself thrice!

As he was healing Ivycius, Garen had replenished the five life forces that he had exhausted earlier. Those five life forces had cost him at least a hundred potential points to replenish. The accumulation of more than two hundred worth of potential points had become about a hundred points or so. This made Garen realized how fast the consumption of potential points was.

Not only had Ivycius not supplied him with any potential points during their uphill battles, he made him lose them instead.

However, these losses were worth it as Garen glanced at Ivycius, who was currently giving orders to the Silver Palace's subordinates.

It was different from his Black Fire Palace as the Silver Palace had three more elites excluding Ivycius.

These three people's nicknames were Lily, Narcissus and Rose respectively and they were all totem users elites who were taught and nurtured by Ivycius himself. They were the true disciples of Ivycius.

Among the three of them, two of them were women and the remaining one was a man. They were all very young as well, where the guy was the youngest, aged at 19 years old and the oldest among the two girls was 23 years old. They were all gifted elites of the Silver Palace.

"Teacher, are you sure you're fine?" Lily and Narcissus were both attentive girls as they immediately noticed the small details from Ivycius's attire.

"I'm fine. As long as the Black Fire Palace Master is around, I will be fine even when I'm heavily injured so don't worry about me." Ivycius explained clearly. "The Black Fire Palace Master and I are old friends and we didn't manage to recognize each other all this time. We unexpectedly reconciled this time. If I am not around, you guys can find Palace Master Garen to settle the problems for you."

"Alright teacher." Three of them were very respectful towards Ivycius and they had reached the peak of form three. They would be able to enter Spiritualization state when the opportunity arrived. They were all different from the typical form three users as they were all very experienced and had already battle against Spiritualization elites. Aside from Rose who was slightly weaker, the remaining two were able to defend for themselves against the spiritualization elites and once they evolved, their strength would definitely be much greater than the typical spiritualization totem users.

Chapter 434: Crisis 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Three of them immediately treated and greeted Garen as the same position as their teacher after Ivycius explained everything to them.

Although the trio didn't possess Beckstone's gifted rapid growth, all of them were more advantageous than the typical totem users.

They had the ability of Crowd Control.

They could only inherit Ivycius's extraordinary Sword Art if they possessed such a gift. They would be able to control countless Petal Totems and attack the enemies simultaneously.

Compared to Garen, who had been a mere commoner without any gift, he was incompetent as compared to these gifted totem users. If not for his Secret Techniques and his memories from the previous world, he would probably still be working his way into form 2.

"What is the status of the current situation?" Ivycius asked.

The trio was stunned and then understood that the relationship between Garen and their master was beyond their comprehension, as they noticed that their master didn't intend to betray Garen. Then, they no longer held back and reported everything they knew.

"There is still no news underneath the palace temple. However, multiple high magnitude earthquakes have occurred and the Defense Tactic Formation in the sky had turned red. We still have no idea who had activated the Kingdom's Defense System." Lily responded immediately. "My sister and I had gone inside to investigate and found out that both Grand Dukes had arrived before us. After we had picked up the corpse of the subordinates inside, we planned to seek for you."

"Change of plans. I will go and meet both of the Grand Dukes in person. You should stay here Ivy." Garen voiced out.

"I will go with you."

"Your injuries haven't recovered yet. If you come with me you'll be in my way." Garen's straightforwardness had caused the trio to feel unhappy.

"Alright then. Be careful." The trio was stunned as they didn't expect their master Ivycius to not refute Garen's intention and merely nod his head.

The arrogant and proud Ivycius, the White Rose Sword Sage who had been famous for the past centuries as one of the three most gifted people in the Royal Alliance, didn't even defend himself or hesitate when Garen said that he would only be in his way.

It was obvious that there was only one reason for this -- That was that Palace Master Garen's strength had far surpassed or was at the same level as their teacher.

Garen pondered for a while.

"You should take this opportunity to capture Beckstone and his men. They had been poisoned by my poisonous smoke so they shouldn't have escaped far from here."

"No problem." Ivycius nodded his head. As they were on their way here, Garen had already told him where Beckstone would most likely head towards to.

After Garen had given his orders, he stared at the central region of the palace from afar and in a blink of an eye, he disappeared without making any noise.

His terrifying speed was revealed and this stunned the three disciples. It was then they knew how terrifyingly powerful the rumored and famed Ninehead Demon Dragon was.

As he was getting close to the temple palace, an ominous presence appeared quickly from below.

Boom!!!

A stream of black chain burst out from the ground and flew towards the sky.

The came the second one, a third one, a fourth one!!

In a blink of an eye, dozens of black chains soared towards the sky and some of then even pierced through the palace temples. There were people who didn't manage to evade in time and was split into half by the chains.

Screams of horror could be heard everywhere.

Boom!!

A man covered in black gas came out of the ground. Without the interference of the Magic Array, he directly went towards the west side of the Kingdom.

"Stop!!"

The deep tone of an old man came from the Palace.

A line of white thread was shot up into the sky, heading towards the human figure.

The human figured let out a sigh and blocked the white thread as he avoided it around his body. Then, a mushroom-like cloud appeared in the middle of the sky.

Countless of black chains soared into the sky as they went after this person. All of the chains disappeared as they entered her body.

As she was about to escape, four yellow light formations in the shape of a shield appeared around her body. The formation was densely filled with Tactic symbols, so dense that it couldn't be read properly as they moved about in the shields.

Then, these four yellow shield started to rotate rapidly around her.

"Greater Imprisonment Tactic!? It's you, Cody!" The woman in the sky shouted. Blood started to flow out of the skin on her entire body, caused by the bursting of capillaries under the skin when exposed to intense high pressure.

Before she had managed to finish her sentence, her body glowed green and she escaped the light shield in an instance, soaring away immediately.

"The Distorted Beads? The Original Heirloom!?" You're God Cloud!" Two surprised tones could be heard from below.

Garen, who originally planned to check on the status of His Majestic Avic was stunned as he heard the word Original Heirloom.

"How dare you assassinate His Majesty Avic! God Cloud, you're literally seeking death!!" He roared as he flew into the sky towards God Cloud, as a black formation flashed underneath his feet.

"I will kill you in place of the Geometry Department!!"

Garen shouted as he tailed God Wind closely from behind.

God Cloud was once in the Geometry Department and eventually betrayed them and joined the Hellgate, so it wasn't wrong for him to say such a statement. It was just rather strange that he would go after him the moment the word Original Heirloom was stated out.

Both of them flew far away and she could still faintly hear Garen's voice.

"God Cloud you bitch, don't run away from me. We will fight fair and square and God will decide who's the victor!!"

Garen's shamelessness had risen to another level as the Grand Dukes watched from below.

Both of them were not used to the style of not letting their enemy escape and survive.

At this point in time, God Cloud was already heavily injured beyond comprehension. Even if he had the Distorted Beads, he would most likely not stand a chance against Garen, who was at the peak of form four. If he were to fight him "fair and square" there wouldn't be any chance of letting God deciding the fate of their battle…

Both of them hesitated but they didn't expect Garen to be the first one to chase after him and felt rather angry towards him. This was the best chance to obtain the Original Heirloom Distorted Beads.

Without any hesitation, both of them showcased their strength as both of them stepped onto an invisible single eyed creature and flew towards Garen and God Cloud.

The Royal Household was only one of the noble households in the Kingdom. However, whoever managed to obtain the Original Heirloom Distorted Beads could possibly be crowned as the next generation of the Royal Household.

In this situation, no one would care whether Avic was still alive underground and three of them tailed behind God Cloud.

Avic's loyal experts fought God Cloud and both parties were heavily injured. Hence this was the crucial moment for them to secure a victory.

A few thousand kilometers had passed while the four of them were in their pursuit.

As they flew across the Kingdom, four distinct lines could be seen in the sky. There were two streaks of black lines, a white one and a yellow one each and all of them possessed immense, unrestricted pressure.

Garen was barely able to catch up due to the impulse force that he'd created originally but as the distance grew further, his disadvantage started to become more and more obvious.

Without any specialized flying equipment and by relying upon only the Black Light Formation Ring from the Secret Service, he would not be able to tail her without his strong force.

On the other hand, both of the Grand Dukes caught up to him and surpassed him in an instant.

Garen once had a unique Black Crow Formation Heirloom but it had broken, resulting in him not being able to fight properly in the sky.

During this pursuit, he was only relying on his body's strength and speed. No matter how strong his body was, he couldn't compare with a flying equipment in terms of endurance.

He could only rely on his strength to fly in the sky and would occasionally descend. His path was literally parabolic.

The remaining three, however, were flying in a straight line and it took no time for them to surpass him.

"God Cloud! Is the Marshall of the Obscuro Society good at running away!!" As he knew that he couldn't catch up with him, Garen immediately shouted at him.

God Cloud heard him and started to laugh. Her pursuers were three form four totem users. It would still be manageable if her original body was here but the current body was a heavily injured substitute. In addition to that, she also had the Obscuro Society's Original Heirloom and would be in great trouble if she were to lose it.

Although she didn't obtain Avic's Original Heirloom, she had already completed half of the plan. Once Avic died Kovitan would have no elites supporting their defense lines, as she had lured the elites away from the Kingdom. Once the overall setup was complete, no matter how strong the RAL was they would need years to recover back to their original strength.

Furthermore, it would be too difficult to produce another Avic.

Within a short amount of time, if the three plans towards the three major countries in the Eastern Continent were to be a success, it would be too late to control the situation even if the Elder Parliament were to find out.

Up in front was where the creatures resided and God Cloud didn't dare to go there alone as these creatures would attack anyone on sight. She turned left and flew towards another direction.

"God Cloud, hand over the Distorted Beads and we would let go of your substitute body today." Grand Duke Benoc shouted.

"There's only one Distorted Beads, who should I pass it to?" God Cloud laughed.

"You still dare to fool around!" Cody smiled coyly as he pointed her with his fat finger.

Four yellow shields appeared in the sky once again and started to surround God Cloud as they rotated.

The Distorted Beads activated once more and a green light flashed. God Cloud continued flying away but her skin started to turn red as if it was scrapped off by a metal brush.

Garen glared fiercely.

As he looked at the three of them getting further and further away from him, he knew that he could no longer catch up with them. He now knew how useful a flying heirloom was.

Even with the Blackcrow King, he might not be able to match with their speed as well.

An heirloom could increase a totem user's speed based on the original strength of the totem user. If only he had an heirloom.

"It's unfortunate…" under this hopeless situation, he turned around and went back to the Kingdom.

In the history, this countless attack from the creatures would break the defensive line so he had to quickly go back and help out his relatives.

Although he couldn't change the history this time, he had obtained countless resources from Avic as the Black Fire Palace Master. The Black Fire Guards could even heavily injure two form four totem users and this was considered a powerful strength. Within the form four totem users, excluding the type which had incredible recovery skills like him and the unique ones who stood at the top of the form four, the rest would consider making a move towards the Black Fire Guards.

Garen had learned how to resupply the Black Fire Guards from Avic. Garen was the only one who stood on top of the command chain for the Black Fire Guards due to the Green Vine Sphere.

After a few upgrades from the Royal Alliance's technology, the technology towards the Green Vine Sphere was very matured.

As he battled with Ivycius and had the opportunity to witness the strength of a form five, he had no regret even though he couldn't change the history.

As he returned, he wondered if he could obtain other good items from Avic as he had provided a great amount of assistance.

Chapter 435: Endgame 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He quickly rushed back towards the Kingdom, but the entire Kingdom was already under siege.

The sky above the Kingdom was pitch black and the bell kept ringing in sets of three peals.

Garen blended into the crowd of lower form totem users' outposts and disappeared immediately.

What made him surprised was that the defense routes of the Kingdom were not the usual ones. Although the setup was strict, there wasn't enough manpower and there were only a few form two totem users.

As the Kingdom's bell rang twice, it unexpectedly rang for the third time.

Garen's expression immediately changed.

"Three groups of bells ringing and nine times in total??!! Could it be?"

It was the bell of someone's death! When the bell rang nine times, it meant that it was a state funeral.

Garen was shocked as he quickly rushed towards the city area of the Kingdom at the top of the hill.

The surrounding totem user guards could only see a black wind billowing past and couldn't even react in time.

If Avic was dead!

Garen's thought flow was incredibly fast, the effects of ten points put into intelligence. By putting just a little bit of thought, he could determine the most important item in the entire Kingdom.

"Caeserton! Ultimate Shelter! If these Ancient Endor Heirlooms were taken away by God Cloud, she wouldn't be injured by Cody. This meant that these items are most likely still inside the Kingdom and have yet to be snatched away!"

A series of possible positions flashed through Garen's mind.

If the Ultimate Heirloom's imitation heirloom, the Blackcrow Formation, was comparable to a form four godly weapon, then the Original Heirloom would allow totem users to display their maximum strength at the same grade and it was definitely possible that it could surpass the current rank as well.

Furthermore, the Original Heirloom was an item that could allow anyone, including commoners, to output a consistent amount of power.

The Original Heirloom's strength had been constant from the very start. The only difference was whether one could muster how much strength from it. Avic, as a commoner, was unbeatable when he obtained the Caeserton. What if it was a totem user who had obtained it? Wouldn't that mean that he would have an absolute defense and would be unbeatable?!

Garen's heart pounded with excitement.

Once someone had obtained the Caeserton, no matter who it was, it meant that he would definitely not die! Even a commoner could become the ultimate guard!

He recalled that God Cloud was able to escape from and heavily injured three master elites with the Distorted Beads. One had to realize that these three master elites stood at the peak of form four and had countless of experience. Each and every one of their strength was on par with Ivycius.

If it were him, he might not possibly win against Veska, and he couldn't even imagine fighting against all three.

Since His Majesty had passed away, then the Caeserton would most like appear at the Palace, the funeral, or among the Royal Nobles…

In the original history, who had obtained the Original Heirloom?

Garen tried his best to recall but he couldn't recall it clearly as the content was very blurry.

He could only see a small black figure inside his mind.

Now that he thought about it, everyone's attention must have focussed on the Original Heirloom. Although this item was powerful, it was definitely eye-catching. What if that old creature appeared….

He knew that deep within the palace, there was a super strong old creature who had the strength of a form five totem user!

As he thought of this, he had already arrived at the City area's giant black wall. There even were a few guards patrolling at the top of it.

A formation flashed underneath Garen's feet and he immediately changed his destination from the funeral to the palace's vault.

He'd once went there with the Black Storm Doves and his every growing memory showed him the path towards it.

He might as well obtain an Heirloom that was suitable for him in the vault, instead of competing to obtain the Caeserton which might fall into another's hands!

Garen tampered down his greed and rushed directly towards the Palace's vault.

After commuting in the Kingdom for half an hour, Garen pushed the crowds away with his black wind.

Everyone in the Kingdom was in the state of panic and there were very few officials out here to control the crowd. Most of the noble officers were prioritizing securing resources with their authority.

Some of the totem users even started to brawl on the street, inflicting injuries to bystanders in the crowd.

Some of the streets were filled with corpses and were completely deserted. Some of the streets were filled with gangsters that would attack anyone they saw. There were even streets where patrols fought with one another over who was supposed to keep the streets safe.

Those who held grudges against each other in the past were fighting to their deaths and no one was stopping them at all.

The houses of beautiful commoners had their doors broke down and pleas for mercy could be constantly heard from within the room. Many merchant shops had been dashed into pieces and some merchant guards could be seen fighting against the troublemakers on the streets as well.

The entire Kingdom was a mess. Garen killed anyone whom he wasn't happy with along the way. Those who had committed rape, murder, robbery and all the gangsters he had seen along the way were killed by his simple Secret Techniques.

Anyone who had Garen's aura inserted into them would stiffen and fall to the ground immediately.

Although there were no changes in other locations, the place Garen passed through had their orders restored and the citizens had gathered together to fend for themselves.

"Captain! Where are you?" Suddenly the Secret Service's communication devices was activated and the old man's voice came out from it. "The Kingdom is in total chaos and a lot of the private soldiers from the noble households are fighting against each other."

"Where are the General Director and the others?"

"The Headquarter ordered us to leave Kovitan Empire immediately!"

"Huh!?" Garen's face turned cold.

The Old Man immediately explained the situation when he realized Garen was unsatisfied with the response.

"There is chaos in the underground as well and high-level creatures have attacked the Administration. The form five totem users from the Headquarters have already gone to the underground to assist. We can only retreat as we don't have any form five elites. We would be tortured to death just by the sheer quantity of these creatures.!"

"Where are the people from the National Service!"

"They have all gone to the front lines! Captain, you should come back immediately! We are about to board the boat! It's located at the Northern region's empty port!" The Old Man urged him.

"I'm not leaving. If you guys still see me as your captain, get off the boat immediately!" Garen said coldly. "I will wait for you guys at the Palace!"

He switched off the communication device immediately.

He couldn't help himself but smile coldly as he switched off the communication device.

"I didn't expect the Three Departments to now know about the old creature inside the palace. This is interesting. Looks like this is Kovitan's final trump card…"

He would have been the first one to leave the Kingdom he didn't know about the existence of this creature.

However, since he knew that the Kingdom would be fine, he naturally stopped panicking.

"The two main forces in charge of maintaining the safety of the Kingdom, the Safety Department and the Inspection Guard, contains combatants ranging from commoners to totem users to maintain the order of the city. These two forces were under the direct control of the royal household and Grand Duke Cody. Since the safety department is a total mess and the Inspection Guards are nowhere to be seen, it's obvious that they have been mobilized to occupy the resources."

Garen pondered as he rushed towards the Palace's Vault with great haste. He was thinking of what he should do to obtain the most authority as Avic had passed away. No matter how absurd he was, he still treated Garen pretty well.

He would help him in any way he could.

Garen was determined.

************

The Palace's Vault was the entire eastern region of the city zone and the entrance was located at the top of a cliff. The black door which spanned a few meters tall was at the opposite side of the cliff and two everlasting Eternal Fire burned on both sides.

There were two parties at the entrance of the vault about to unsheath their swords at any moment.

"Masha, Erina! Leave this place immediately! I am responsible to protect this vault. If you continue to loiter here, I will attack you!" A middle-aged man in a black shirt shouted as he blocked the vault's entrance.

The two men and woman who were facing a group of people started to smile coldly.

"Gujjad, if you don't step aside, don't blame me for stepping on my cousin brother's pride. I will definitely open this vault!" the handsome male leader shouted.

Then, a ray of red light rained from the sky and landed directly on the vault's door.

Buzz buzz….

A black sealing tactic formation suddenly appeared onto the door and it had weakened the red light.

"Veska's tactic formation sure is something!" A cold voice came from the sky.

The two parties suddenly felt a shiver down their spine and a stronger red light that resembled a red cylinder came down once more before they could react.

Boom!!!

The red light kept shooting onto the door and canceled out with the Black Sealing Halo.

"Rheins?" A man blurted out a sentence with suspicion.

A man in black robe suddenly appeared at the entrance of the vault. His raised both his hands up and his gaze were cold from his long, narrow eyes.

The man raised his head up and looked at the source of the red light.

A giant bird with red feathers came down from the sky. Countless red lava spheres were revolving around his body and the source of the red light was none other than these spheres.

The eyes of the giant bird were like burning firestones and after staring at the man in the black robe underneath him, it revealed a sign of fear and surprise as it spoke like a human.

"Muen? Didn't you go after the Caeserton? Why are you here?"

"There's a lot of people searching for the Caeserton. I won't be able to do anything if I were there. So I changed my destination here in hope that I can obtain something more beneficial." The man in the black robe, Muen smiled as he stared at the giant red bird landing at the entrance of the vault as they kept a distance between each other.

As the human and bird were having their conversation, the remaining people slowly backed off as they were afraid to catch their attention.

"You people from the Geometry Department has yet to fully retreat? What a surprise." Although the man in the black robe, Muen smiled, he still gave off a cold and emotionless vibe.

"Aren't you from the War Guild the same. After the disappearance of the night assassin, half of Kovitan's underworld is in your palm, right?" The red giant bird, Rheins scoffed. "Looks like you and I have the same objective today."

"50 50?"

"50 50." The red bird nodded. The bird, which stood at least three meters tall, kept its wings, stood up and walked like a human.

Boom!!

Suddenly, noise reverberated from afar. A tall, strong, muscular man with red eyes and a body covered with black hair walked towards the vault.

The form two totem abilities which tried to restrain him felt like nothing but an itch to him and they were completely powerless. With his strong suppression due to his rank and his terrifying resistance towards everything, it was as if there was no one there even though there was a crowd.

Chapter 436: Endgame 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Roar!!!" the black haired man roared and his body largened substantially.

A few yellow-shirted men appeared behind him and it was obvious that these people were targeting the vault.

They hesitated when they saw a man and a bird standing at the entrance of the vault, and they started to surround the black hairy man.

Soon a group of strong totem users arrived, in which each and every one of them was at least a form two totem user.

More and more people gathered and the largening group was starting to become eye-catching. Everyone was staring at the bird and the man, as every person could feel their exposed power.

This group of people gathered together and split into three smaller groups.

One group had gathered near the black hairy man and one could faintly hear someone calling him the Bear man. He was a strong spiritualized totem user.

The other group was led by a girl in a red shirt. Its leader Aier was a middle-aged woman who was riding on a white bear. Her face was average and was rather skinny. She was in a red shirt and had a white feathered round hat on top of her head. The force field around her was impressive as she stood at the pinnacle of form three.

The last group was lead by two poets who had one violin each in their arms. Their grey shirts were ragged and they even had baggage on them. The man and woman's eyes resembled those of beasts as their pupils were black and narrow.

There were tumors spawning on their bodies and their force field would spike from strong to weak and kept fluctuating unnaturally. It was obvious that some sort of totem user had merged with them.

"You all don't even know you're on death's doorstep!" The red giant bird glared at the crowd coldly. "This place is completely owned by me and the ward guild."

Its voice was neutral and no one could make out if it was a female or male.

At the same time, it brushed its wing across the ground.

Whoosh!!

A red line appeared in front of the entrance of the vault.

"Don't blame me for eating whoever who dares to cross this line!!"

The bear man started to smile coldly.

"Lord Fire Spirit, we have so many comrades here. Isn't it absurd to tell us to give up based on your one measly order?"

"That's right." The woman in red shirt responded. "Although we're no match for the two of you, we are still able to create some havoc."

As a totem user who was already in the front line, she was always on high alert. She knew exactly how strong these two were.

Fire Spirit Rheins was a well-known form four elite in the Kingdom. It was also the guardian of the Kingdom's defense tactic formation. It was originally a human but an accident occurred and he had merged together with his core totem. His original body was burnt and he became a core totem fire spirit bird.

Muen, on the hand, was something else entirely. He was the only form four elite in Kovitan's War Guild and was one of its three leaders.

Whoever dared to rob the Royal's Vault at this time, be it a villain, would hesitate from such a threat. Since they had decided to rob, they would have already considered the consequences.

No matter how powerful these two were in Kovitan, it wasn't possible for them to obtain everything for themselves as there would be flaws in everything.

"I meant it when I say no." The Fire Spirit Rheins smiled coldly and raised its right wing.

A transparent man who was hiding at the side of the vault's entrance was blown into the sky by the wind.

His body was immediately cut in half at the waist as he screamed. The transparent force field around his body started to react strongly.

Boom!!

This man self-destructed and it was obvious that his totem had the ability to self-destruct, as it formed an invisible concussion ball that expanded rapidly.

As the concussion ball was about to expand further, the fire spirit shuffled its wings again.

A layer of red light engulfed the entire concussion ball as it formed into a huge sphere levitating in the sky. After a while, the red ball dispersed and everything was in peace with nothing left in the sky.

It was as though that guy had never come to this place.

"Is there anyone else?!" The Red Spirit stared coldly at the remaining people.

Suddenly, a black wind blew from afar and the people who stood in its way were blown to the side and fell to the ground.

The totem users with vision totem ability could faintly see a person inside the black wind. Perhaps one should say there was a man's after image moving in the black wind at high speed.

"Turning a deaf ear on me!!?" The Fire Spirit raged as it raised both of its wings.

The Fire Spirit's expression changed immediately as soon as the red beam made contact with the opponent.

"Alright alright!!! I admit I have…"

"Get lost!!"

A deep roar could be heard and broke off the Fire Spirit's speech. A fiery red beam collided with the Fire Spirit's red beam and immediately melted the latter before it landed onto the Fire Spirit.

Boom!!!

The Fire Spirit was viciously pushed off the cliff as it embarrassedly tried to maintain its balance mid-air.

As it was about to turn around and rage, Muen was already slammed deep into the stone wall on the right of the opponent and his face was totally pale.

A tall golden-haired man in black armor was standing in front of the vault's entrance.

"Veska's Tactic Formation?"

Eight red dragon heads appeared behind him and collided with the door without any restraint.

Roar!!!

Eight of the dragon shadows crash onto the stone door at lightning speed.

The red light and black light intertwined with each other as the buzzing sound could be constantly heard.

Kaboom!!

A huge hole was created onto the vault's entrance.

The man hmpf-ed and walked into it.

Muen and the Fire Spirit didn't even dare to breathe behind him.

Although both of them were form four totem users, they were able to become form four due to the external strength and were just at the initial and unstable stage of form four. The difference in strength between them and the man who crashed into them was day and night.

Furthermore, this man was the Black Fire Palace Master, who was a recently notorious man who could even stop a child from crying. They didn't even dare to utter a word.

"Should we go in?" Muen asked as he suddenly appeared behind the Fire Spirit as he showed an intention of working together.

The Fire Spirit glanced at him and noticed that one of the top totem users of the War Guild was heavily injured by his casual attack.

"That guy is the Black Fire Palace Master. He's the kind of guy who would kill anyone who doesn't agree with him. You're welcome to go on your own."

Muen was in a dilemma as he recalled the two combo attack earlier.

The Fire Spirit and he were pushed away by the opponent like a fly. Finally, he had to suppress his greed.

"I know another first-class vault but the guards there are a little bit troublesome. Do you want to team up?" He finally gave up on the Royal Vault.

The Fire Spirit nodded his head in frustration.

Those who couldn't suppress their greed cast all sorts of camouflaging abilities and entered the vault in hope to loot some leftovers.

The three totem user leaders didn't hesitate at all.

After some obvious struggle from the Bear man, he decided to leave.

"Let's go!"

He turned around and left the scene.

As for the other two, the middle age woman gritted her teeth and covered herself with a layer of grey-white membrane and entered the vault.

"We will just be collecting the items near the entrance…" These group of people quietly entered the cave with this intention in mind.

Even the wandering poets entered together as well...

**************

Garen trotted inside the vault.

The inner side of the vault was a pitch black main hall.

The wall, ground, metal racks and everything else were completely black.

There were Heirlooms on two metal racks that were glowing in different shades of color.

Each Heirloom was protected by two unique layers of tactical formations.

The first layer was to prevent others from using the Heirloom and the second layer was to prevent others from taking the Heirloom away. Once the first layer was forcefully removed, the second layer would activate and destroy the Heirlooms.

At the front of the vault were all valuable medicine. Valuable totems were placed at the center but these totems were all silver made primitive totems.

There were complete sets of inherited, Nurtured Totems.

Garen wanted them so badly but he didn't dare to simply break the Tactical Formation.

Aside from protection, the first layer also had the effect of anchoring the totems in place. Hence it would be impossible to bring these totems home and unlock them slowly.

Garen didn't care about the medicine as he now has superhuman recovery and was immune to hundreds of poisons. Furthermore, his totem was almost merged with his actual body and didn't require multiple resources like those low-grade totem users.

Although the Cherish Totem was strong, without a strong background in totem maintenance it would be usable but not maintainable. It would be completely broken if it's damaged even a little bit since it couldn't be fixed.

After some consideration, Garen took a few Silver Medicines that were used for repairing totems. These medicines which were fused with Silver were very rare. It could heal the damages of a primitive totem but only light damage.

It's valuable just because only big noble households were able to get their hands on these. The remaining typical totem users could only find a forger to fix their totems.

These items could be used by Garen or sold it for money as the quantity was very minute.

Garen glanced at the inherited totems and the strongest he saw was but of a Spiritualized grade, which was meaningless to him. He simply took the inherited Magical Eye and left the place.

This inheritance was the least among the others, from which Garen could easily acquire thirty to forty thick books.

The Magical Eye only had five books so it was considered to be very little.

Next was the deepest part of the vault.

Kovitan's Royal Household wasn't the best in researching totem but in fabricating Heirlooms.

The reason Garen rushed to this place was that he wanted to obtain an imitated Heirloom that suited him.

In the original history, the Caeserton off the annals of history without a trace, and there had to be a peculiar reason for it.

It would be better for him to obtain heirlooms that he could most likely obtain than to try and obtain an unlikely heirloom.

The elites who wanted to obtain the original heirloom had gone to the funeral and only the side characters would come to the vault.

However, Garen was different. He obtained intel from the third princess that Avic once fabricated the ultimate heirloom Caeserton which has immense power. Very little people knew about this as it was fabricated within the Royal Household. The item never came to light ever again after completion and its whereabouts was unknown.

Garen's objective was an item in this vault.

Chapter 437: Rewards 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There was an opened door in the tall black wall deep within the vault.

It was pitch black inside and a bone-chilling wind could be felt coming out from it.

Garen looked left and right and his surroundings was an empty space.

There was a layer of snow on the ground, suggesting that the temperature inside was extremely low.

His heart and throat started to vibrate as he produced a small vibration outside of humans' audible range. The vibration could penetrate through everything and the distance it could travel was astonishingly far.

"Ivycius, I'm currently at the Royal's Vault. Please send some men over."

This was a unique way of communication between Garen and the Demon Dragon. Although the range was limited, it was not a problem if it was within the Kingdom.

He soon received a response.

"Alright. My disciple is on the way there along with fifteen totem users. You should have enough support and they should arrive in twenty minutes."

Garen stopped his vibration. As he was about to enter the door, he suddenly heard whispers of joy from behind. It seemed that some outsiders had entered and felt ecstatic when they obtained the Heirlooms.

His face went cold and flicked his finger towards his back.

Pew pew pew!

Three streams of poisonous black fog trickled from behind him and disappeared into the darkness.

Those were the Nine-Headed Dragon's poison secreted by Garen himself. It could spread within the vault and kill all living beings silently.

This would last for fifteen minutes or so and Ivycius's disciple would arrive soon after that. Those who were able to leave the place with the Heirloom would be considered lucky.

He walked into the black door with large strides.

Garen's vision quickly adapted to the pitch black environment in front of him.

Underneath his feet was a long black passageway which extended into the pitch black darkness in front of him.

The endless pits were on both side of the passageway and gushes of cold wind kept blasting up from it.

Garen moved forward slowly as he maintained great caution of his surroundings.

He could faintly hear something buzzing at the bottom of the pit. It sounded like a cry or a soft laughter but he couldn't hear anything afterward when he tried to listen closer.

He looked down to the pit from both sides but it was pitch black.

Garen's eyes glowed as he gazed down.

The Eye of Isaiah was activated but the pit was completely quiet.

Garen frowned, canceled the tactic and pondered for a moment before he kept moving forward.

The black passageway seemed to be endless as it kept stretching forward. There were no rail guards on both sides and he would have fallen had he been a commoner.

He gradually increased his speed as the layers of snow underneath his legs became thicker and harder.

Bam!

Suddenly the passageway in front of him broke apart.

A red dot was lit up in the pitch black pit.

The red light grew larger and flew up at incredible speed as it buzzed. Then, the red light lit up the surrounding area.

Surprisingly, the entire area was a massive wide black cage with uneven stone walls and pillars everywhere.

The red light in the pit became larger, dying the stone walls bright red as well. The cold air was gone, replaced by scorching heat.

Garen took a few steps back and the layer of ice underneath his feet melted immediately under the red light, similar to lava flowing down into the pit from both sides.

Boom!!

A fireball of more than ten meters in radius appeared in front of him.

The fireball cracked open, revealing a black square door and the door had a handle and a keyhole.

There was a fiery red human face made of red lines carved onto the door. Lava seemed to be flowing under the face and the overall look was elegant.

Ember motes floated in the air due to the high temperature. The ice on the passageway had completely evaporated into steam.

"So this is the real entrance huh?" Garen squinted his eyes.

He walked towards it while resisting the scorching hot temperature and touched the stone door handle at the center of the fireball.

"Please state the password." A clear voice of a woman could be heard. She seemed emotionless just like the computers on Earth.

Garen hesitated for a moment.

"I, as the Black Fire Palace Master of the Kingdom, should have the right to record in the central totem system, right?" He asked unsurely.

"Checking for rights… Result states you do not have the right to enter. Please leave immediately." The female voice immediately found the answer.

Garen's expression changed slightly and pulled the handle fiercely.

"Invader!! Invader!!" The female voice sharpened.

Kachak!

It was as if some glass had broken.

Countless of black cracks resembling spider webs came at Garen from all directions. The cracks propagated in the air, it was as if space itself was shattering.

Boom!!

Garen's landed his right fist on the stone door instantly.

As his palm crashed into the stone door, the whole cave suddenly trembled. Garen used the recoil as a supportive force to push himself to the far back, avoiding the black cracks at the same time.

The gigantic fireball had started to descend into the pit.

Garen rushed towards it and felt that the temperature had increased dramatically. Compared to the temperature previously which was just scorching hot, the current temperature was on the verge of being able to cook a person and it was still rising.

However, this was all meaningless to him; he had 10 vitality points hence he could withstand up to hundreds of degrees of temperature without sustaining any injury. Furthermore, he also had totem light to protect him.

As he got closer to the stone door in the fireball, multiple black cracks approached him from both sides.

These cracks gave him a sense of danger.

Garen's eye flashed and he immediately clapped his hands, countless auras forming complex and mysterious lines on his body.

Ten Thousand Mammoth Sky Encirclement!!!

He roared as fires were produced from the friction between his hand and the air. He then placed them at the center.

Boom!!

A shockwave spread across the area and stunned the black cracks.

Garen then took this opportunity to land a quick punch onto the stone door.

However, there was no effect.

The dragon's shadow flashed on Garen's face. He opened his mouth and roared like the dragon.

Copious white gas, similar to a cloud, gathered at his right fist, forming a white cloud ball.

The feeling of battling against Ivycius filled his heart.

The violent desire of destruction flowed out of his heart and with the nine-headed demon dragon's totem light, the two of them formed into a single being.

"Ah!!!!" Garen shouted violently.

Nine dragon shadows darted out as they wrapped around his right hand. The dragons' eyes glowed red and collided with the stone door.

Crack!

Cracks started expanding on the stone door's surface and this formed more and more cracks until it had covered the whole stone door.

Crush!!

The stone door collapsed.

Garen immediately flew into the door as countless spider web-shaped dimensional cracks grazed his back, leaving an injury.

He stood at the entrance as he tried to calm himself down. His heartbeat was extremely erratic.

That had been one of the skills he'd created when he had encountered Ivycius. It involved multiple Secret Techniques merging with the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon Totem Light.

One could also say that this was the accumulation of his techniques from the martial art world. All the strength and pace Secret Techniques had been placed into it.

"This move should be called Sky Dragon's Crisscross!" Garen opened his mouth and a stream of black gas which looked like an arrow flew out.

Garen felt empty as he invented the Sky Dragon's Crisscross as if he had poured out all of his accumulated inspiration all at once.

He stood still until his heartbeat returned to its normal rate before he opened his eyes.

If the Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills was his complete martial art essence as a commoner, then this newly invented technique would be his first step in merging himself with his totem.

The strength of the Dragon's Heart might be fully utilized with this technique.

With the support of the Troll Grip, he wondered how strong he could be.

As he put away his thoughts, Garen analyzed the surrounding environment.

Inside the fireball was a small square stone room.

The stone walls were glossy and black in color and the fiery red tactical lines were glowing on it, giving off a fantasy vibe.

There were three black metal racks placed inside the stone room.

Each rack had different items placed on top of it.

On the left rack, there were daggers, long swords, and armors placed on top of it. These items were carved with shining Tactical symbols. Its interior looked beautiful and delicate patterns were carved everywhere.

Garen walked towards it and picked up a white armor. It was thin and carved with flowery patterns. It was warm and its base material was rather soft.

He gently rattled the armor.

Buzz!!

A circle of white halo spread out from the armor and shone onto Garen's body. Suddenly, his injury on his back had fully recovered.

"Non-activated healing effect?" Garen placed down the armor. With such an incredible healing effect, it would mean that he would have many lives during a battle and could be considered a priceless item to anybody.

One would typically need at least ten minutes to heal such a heavy injury. In addition, the main difference was that it would exhaust a person's potential to heal themselves. This would result in a reduction in lifespan if one were to keep healing themselves.

However, this item relied on external resources to heal the injury and would not injure the body's potential. No wonder it had been placed in this vault.

When Garen had been grazed by the black crack, the Nine-Headed Dragon's Totem Light was instantly shattered, heavily injuring one of the dragon heads and almost losing one of its lives.

He observed the Dragon Head within the black dimension and saw that the injured dragon head was wilting fast as if all of its water content had been absorbed away.

Although his body had been healed, the totem's injury wasn't healed at all.

Garen placed down the armor and picked up the dagger.

The dagger was yellow in color and its base material resembled a jade, which gave off a half transparent vibe. The end of the dagger was curved, forming a J shape. What was interesting was that there was a yellow diamond-shaped gemstone placed on the edge of the knife at a fixed distance.

This dagger, which was the most eye-catching one, was placed at the very top of the rack.

As Garen picked up the dagger, he felt that he was holding onto a living being. It was as if he was holding onto a living being rather than of a weapon.

He gently waved the dagger.

Fling!

Suddenly, a yellow arc of electricity flickered in the air.

A yellow snake-like creature appeared faintly around the dagger. This living being resembled a snake but it had ears and a pair of transparent cicada wings.

As it appeared again once more, Garen could clearly see that this living being only had one eye and was filled with yellow electricity inside of it.

Chapter 438: Reward 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Good stuff!" He tied the dagger to his waist decisively.

Checking it on the weapons rack again, the rest were at most the same level as the chest armor, not particularly peak class, but still rather excellent. It was just that after he obtained the dagger, Garen couldn't quite appreciate the rest.

His fighting style was always bare-handed, he only took the dagger because he felt this thing was more mysterious, and he didn't know where that flashing creature came from.

Leaving the weapons rack, he walked up to the rack in the center.

There were a few items sparsely scattered on this rack. They were all unbelievably precious peak-level minerals and jewels.

There were six items in total, divided into three types.

Garen recognized two types, the three Evolution Crystals and two Night Crystals. The last was something like a blood-red pearl, he didn't know what it was.

Although most nobles had Evolution Crystals, he really hadn't seen a crystal like the one in front of him before, crystal clear and as large as a watermelon. Or at least, Garen hadn't seen one like this in Vanderman's estate storehouse.

Most totems could only use an Evolution Crystal once, the more these things were used, the more efficient they became. At the same time, they were absolutely necessary ingredients for fixing most powerful totems after they were utterly destroyed.

They had always been military-required materials, and weren't allowed in open private transactions. Most people found it impressive to use a walnut-sized one once. All three in front of him were as large as watermelons.

Garen took off his coat directly, putting the three crystals inside and tying them up tightly. These three crystals exceeded entire cities in worth.

As expected of the Royal Treasury!

With admiration in his heart, he also stuffed the other two items together and tied them up.

Night Crystals were a treasure that could temporarily boost a totem's potential, and temporarily strengthen them significantly. It was just that they also had significant side effects, and required a forger to make them into a potion before those side effects could be reduced.

As for that last Blood Pearl, he had no idea what it was, but Garen put it into his waist pouch.

After that was the third rack.

There was a mess of everything there, many items overall, more than ten types, but they were all strange and unknown.

There was a lush green plant seed shining with green light, an old scroll torn in half, a wilted black flower in a flower vase, an unknown creature's banana-shaped skull, and a blue-purple spherical object like a fish egg.

Garen didn't recognize many of these items, but he vaguely felt as though these things had something in common.

That was, they all emitted an aura of age. As though they had existed for many, many years.

Garen glanced at these items one by one, when suddenly his gaze fell on a dried-up black eyeball.

This item had the exact same feeling he got from the Eye of Isaiah back then!

He couldn't help but reach out to pick up the dried-up black eyeball.

The Eye of Isaiah was a grey-white stone eye, and the one in front of him was a true creature's eye.

Vaguely, he felt an intense heat coming from his War Chain, as though something was resonating inside, beating.

He pulled up his sleeve and looked at it, on the very tip of the diamond-shaped white-silver chain, the embedded grey-white stone ball was slowly trembling, beating like a heart.

The War Chain was embedded into his body, and Eye of Isaiah was naturally also a Solidifying Tactic etched into his body. This was actually already equivalent to an organ transplant, the entire War Chain similar to a man-made organ transplanted onto the human body. Not long after the transplant, it would be utterly assimilated into the totem user, becoming part of their body.

It was just that, right then, the Eye of Isaiah that had already been assimilated into Garen was resonating with the eyeball in his hand.

"Could it be?! All these are…?"

Garen suddenly thought of a possibility, his heart giving a little jolt.

He took the black eyeball in his hand and pressed it lightly against the War Chain.

Psst!

The eyeball actually melted away, turning into a black liquid and flowing into where the Eye of Isaiah's grey-white stone ball was, completely wrapping it up.

Suddenly, an intense, burning pain came from his left arm.

Garen frowned slightly, thinking this intense pain slightly odd.

It was as though two burning hot snakes of fire were rapidly extending down his left arm, flowing past his shoulder, heading up his neck, and darting into his eyes with a whoosh.

He had no intention of stopping it, after all the worst case scenario would be that he died once. He had the Nine-Life Talent, so he wasn't afraid of any accidents at all.

As for the pain, he had experienced countless battles since he started training his secret techniques, and which injury hadn't come with pain. Some of the training methods were even more painful than the injuries. If he didn't have that much determination, no matter how strong his natural talent was, he couldn't possibly have become King of the Century.

The black liquid kept enveloping the Eye of Isaiah, and after more than ten seconds, it finally slowed down, seeping directly into the Eye of Isaiah.

The whole stone ball became faintly black from its original grey-white, emitting an unnamed sense of eeriness.

Garen looked straight at his attribute pane, and as expected, the Eye of Isaiah on the War Chain had changed.

'Original Eye: originating from the mysterious Ancient Endor civilization's tactics, this tactic will make the user's eyes completely transparent, they can see inhuman mysterious powers. Formed by the Eye of Isaiah absorbing the Original Eyeball. The Eye of Isaiah was originally forged by a forger known as Isaiah. The forgery was the Original Eye, excavated from the ruins.

Ability:

Ray of Terror -- the strange eyes can induce the terrifying shadows in the enemy's heart, directly causing a powerful emotional impact.

The totem user will obtain the ability to use Ray of Terror once a day, source of attack: eyes.

Effect: can cause death, serious injury, loss of consciousness, weakness. The stronger the opponent's will, the weaker the effect.'

"So it's this thing!" Garen suddenly remembered, when he was with Windling from Obscuro, he heard him mention this. Windling just didn't know that Garen had an Eye of Isaiah.

And now he dug the information about this special ability directly from his memory, everything becoming instantly clear to him.

"I just don't know how powerful it is."

He continued looking at the other things, and now Garen was certain, these things in front of him were all different Solidifying Tactics. These Solidifying Tactics were all different, and looked like all sorts of things.

Just take any one of these out, and the totem users outside will break their backs fighting over them.

Garen carefully identified the effect waves of these Solidifying Tactics.

For tactic effects, it was always quantity over quality.

He chose a seed with a mix of red and green, the seed emitting waves similar to that of the Healing Breastplate.

After embedding it into the War Chain, another Life Vine tactic ability appeared as expected. This was also a tactic ability he knew.

Summoning the surrounding plants into becoming a prison of vines, it wrapped around the patient, healing and protecting at the same time, while the vines themselves had certain protective power. It was a tactic with rather high survival power. It could be used once a day. It could heal all injuries below Spiritualization, but the number of usages needed could differ.

After the War Chain was upgraded, it had eight available tactic spaces.

After Garen took one Life Vine to increase his survival power, he started looking at the remaining tactics.

The War Chain was meant to gather his subordinates' and companions' power and survival abilities, while at the same time it was a good way to increase his own power and gathering ability, so it wasn't for his use only.

Therefore, the Life Vine was going to be his service to others, as a Solidifying Tactic kept by the royal family, its effects would naturally be decent.

After that, Garem began choosing his offensive tactics.

He believed that the best defense was to kill off the opponent, so offense was key.

He could gather power in his Solidifying Tactics, and use them once every day, which made it perfectly possible for him to match them up to create a mixed effect.

Garen felt the force fields between these tactics closely. After considering them carefully, he realized that his Myriad Water Jasper Technique probably wasn't the only one among Form Five fighters.

These Form Five elite fighters all shared a secret, which was that they all had their own Secret Technique. If he hadn't learned this secret from Ivycius, Garen would still be clueless about this.

They used Secret Techniques to assimilate the totems into their bodies, merging the two into one, achieving an extreme and terrifying evolution effect. Lower-level totem users think they themselves were stronger than totems, and that was why they didn't release their totems, but the truth was that they had assimilated their totems totally.

They no longer had totems to release.

Although Ivycius understood that, he had deep feelings for his own totem, and wasn't willing to take that path. Otherwise, he would have entered Form Five a long time ago.

The Solidifying Totems on the rack had heating forces, cooling forces, material forces, and other complicated forces that he didn't know.

Garen felt them for a while, and finally decided to add a tactic with the same type of force into his six remaining tactic spaces.

He didn't choose different combinations, because he didn't know any of these. So he decided to take six wilting black flowers with cooling forces.

There were eight of these flowers in total, and they looked like they withered a long time ago, the vase they were put in was actually made of pitch-black ice. The forces emitted by each flower were slightly weaker than their fewer counterparts, but not by much.

Garen pressed the six flowers into the War Chain, one after the other.

Slowly, his elemental pane changed again, a new tactic effect slowly appearing.

'Black Wilted Flowers (unnamed): source unknown.

Effect: Passive Spirit Light, lowers the temperature within ten meters by ten degrees. Slows down the enemy's movement speed and efficiency by a certain degree.'

"It's actually a precious non-consumptive Passive Spirit Light." Garen was slightly surprised, this type of tactic didn't need a continuous source of power, and could be used whenever and wherever. To a normal low-level totem user, to be able to obtain the effect of Spiritualization beforehand was already very impressive, as they could understand the true quality of such an effect in advance and increase the chances of their totem evolutions being Spiritualized, but to Garen, this was a little underwhelming.

He had only met a few Spiritualized high-level totem users, all the peak-level fighters gathered and compressed their powers, never using them wastefully.

They even only used their Spirit Light when they needed a large-scale effect.

These black flowers actually only lowered the temperature by ten degrees, Garen had pressed all the flowers into the War Chain, so the six black flowers stacked up reduced the temperature by sixty degrees. The area of effect was sixty meters. The effect on the enemy was the same, without an objective value.

There was still some effect to speak of. To a normal person that was already extremely terrifying, but to a totem user, it was only so-so.

After all, it was non-consumptive, so it was much better than those extremely powerful but at the same time extremely consumptive tactics. It was also more valuable than those Solidifying Tactics that had limited daily uses. Or so it was to Garen himself.

Solidifying Tactics were only for support, in the end he still had to rely on himself.

Chapter 439: Chaos 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Black Wilted Flowers, minerals such as the Evolution Crystals, the mysterious dagger, and the legacy of the Illusory Demon Eye.

Garen thought about it, and tried his best wrap all the Solidifying Tactics into his clothes and put on the Healing Breastplate, it was a bit small, but after a bit of adjustment it fit his figure nicely.

He had stuffed away more than a half of the things on the three racks, his pockets bulging and threatening to overflow. Only then did Garen retreat towards the door, satisfied.

Outside the door, those countless dense black cracks had disappeared, the darkness was empty and utterly motionless.

Garen narrowed his eyes slightly, one hand holding the package made from his clothes as he put one foot on the doorframe.

Bam!

With one dash step, he rushed out of the doorframe, his figure like a shot of lightning as he burst out of the room.

Ker-chak!!

Many black cracks appeared all around him in the blink of an eye, madly extending towards him.

He had no idea what these things were, but they seemed to ignore his defenses altogether, Garen’s Totem Light acting like tofu in front of it, unable to withstand even one hit.

Before he could think too much of it, many black cracks chased closely behind Garen, as he dashed straight out of the black tunnel, shooting back into the treasury hall with a whoosh.

With a bang, he somersaulted in the air, a black light formation lighting up under Garen’s feet, and he landed lightly on the floor of the treasury hall.

His back was already covered with many wounds and cracks, many wounds deep enough to see bone, a mess of blood and flesh.

Garen’s buckets of sweat flowed down both of his temples.

"What a terrifying defense system!" He looked at the Nine-Headed Dragon totem in the black space, two consecutive heads had utterly withered, evidently completely killed by these black cracks.

Two dragon heads equaled forty potential points, Garen felt his heart ache as he watched the forty potential points get deducted, and the Nine-Headed Dragon returned to its Nine Life state.

But in his attribute pane, the potential points pane was left with only seventy-odd points.

He had always been losing without any gain, who knew how long it would take for his Secret Technique to reach the second level.

Smack!

Suddenly there was a sound from between Garen’s fingers. That Black Light Formation Ring issued by the Secret Service finally broke completely. It had probably been touched by the black cracks just now, this was a common heirloom, a tool to borrow some momentum. After being used for so long, after enduring so many battles, it finally shattered completely.

This was actually already a sign of its incredible endurability and high quality. To have lasted this long, it truly inspired admiration in the endurability of the three departments’ skills.

Garen frowned.

"This sort of tool to borrow momentum isn’t very precious, but it’s still not something just anyone can make. I need to find another suitable flying apparatus." After getting used to being able to move by borrowing momentum whenever he wanted, Garen was really not used to suddenly losing the Light Formation Ring.

Taking the things as he walked out, he saw some bodies strewn all over the Treasury, each of them with faces turning purple, grasping their throats tightly, their death masks horrific.

These were all totem users who gave in to their greed and came here looking for good stuff, there were even some normal strong fighters.

The poisonous gas that Garen had released earlier was now completely gone, and he was beginning to hear some voices come from the front half of the Treasury.

"...It’s the Royal Treasury! It’s the royal family’s, our forbidden area, what do you think this means, Dill?" A woman’s voice, suppressing anger, could be heard.

"It means whatever you think it means." A deep man’s voice replied calmly. "I don’t know anything about any Royal Treasury, I only came here on my teacher’s orders, I don’t know anything else."

"You guys are committing daylight robbery! Aren’t you worried about Her First Highness investigating this?" another cold man’s voice said.

The other side seemed lazy to reply, and simply fell silent.

Carrying his things, Garen walked out boldly.

There were two groups facing off in the first half of the Treasury, one side was obviously the First Princess’ grey-clothed underlings, whereas on the other side was one of Ivycius’ disciples, that nineteen-year-old boy Rose.

There were still seven or eight people behind Rose, each of them aggressive and not particularly kind-looking. As soon as he saw Garen come out, Rose immediately took a step out.

"Teacher Garen." His arrogance from before completely gone, he said humbly and respectfully.

"You guys are here?" Garen nodded, ignoring the grey-clothed female leader whose eyes looked ready to spit fire. "The country is in crisis right now, in order to secure the safety of the Royal Treasury, I took the initiative to hide some of the heirlooms, to prevent some lowly characters from taking advantage of the situation. I’m thinking of the larger picture for the royal family here. You guys don’t have any objection to that, do you?"

He looked at the woman in grey calmly.

Beside him, Rose and the others were already looking fierce, their Totem Light threatening to come to life. Evidently they were planning to silence the witnesses once and for all.

The woman in grey gave a shudder, and hurriedly was all smiles.

"No… none. Your Excellency the Black Fire Palace Master is here, and since it’s the Palace Master who’s here, naturally there’s nothing for us to say. We’ll take our leave now."

Garen watched the group of people in grey retreat outside in orderly haste, but had no intention of attacking them.

There was no way he could hide the fact that he had gone into the Treasury, and everyone had openly declared war already anyway. With Avic’s death, nothing else had to be hidden anymore.

After these people had left completely, Garen finally looked at Rose.

"Get your people to take as many things out of the Treasury as possible, I want half of everything, got it?"

"Got it!" Rose nodded obediently.

"Make sure you maintain a balance." Garen nodded.

"I understand." Rose gave a smile, meaning ‘we all get it’. "Oh, yeah, Teacher Garen, the two Grand Dukes are back, and right now they’re gathering all the middle-class and above nobility into the palace meeting hall. Now that the three departments have left and abandoned Kovistan, we cannot just sit here and await death. The two Grand Dukes are probably planning to gather everyone’s power. They even invited Teacher, and you, sir."

"I got it." Garen mused. He had planned to go look at his cousin and the others, although he had told them long ago to go to Prynne’s grandfather’s at the first sign of trouble, and he believed Prynne would take good care of them, it was still safer for him to go and see.

And then he needed to summon all of his family’s members.

Garen gave the package in his hand straight to Rose.

"Give these things to your teacher for safekeeping, make sure not a single one is missing, remember."

Rose was nearly crushed under the weight of the package, and almost lost his grip on it. He hadn’t expected this package, wrapped in clothes, to be this heavy.

Hearing Garen’s words, he nodded hard.

"Please leave it to me!"

In the entire Kingdom, even if he dared to lust over Teacher’s things, he would never dare to touch the Black Fire Palace’s things. Compared to the cool and calm of the Silver Palace, news of the Black Fire Palace Master’s cruelty and horror had already spread throughout the Kingdom.

In these chaotic times, such a terrifying reputation was the most effective.

Garen hurried straight towards his family estate.

Under these circumstances, he had long since told everyone to gather back at the Blue Bay estate.

Using about a dozen whole minutes, Garen rushed back at full speed, noticing how the streets on the way were getting emptier and emptier, most of the citizens having hidden into their homes and leaving the place a lot clearer. It didn’t affect his speed, in any case.

Hurriedly he returned to the suburbs where the estate was.

Garen could already see two people waiting at the estate’s main entrance, and one of them was the knight Edney.

This old woman had been working for the Trejons family for so long, and now she was pacing back and forth, seeming rather anxious.

Seeing Garen’s figure appear on the road outside the estate, Edney’s face relaxed instantly. She came up to greet him.

"Chief! You’re finally back!!" She finally released the breath she’d been holding, "Come in, quick, our people are all in here."

Garen nodded, walking past the wide-open estate doors.

The front hall inside was filled with a large crowd of people.

They were divided into two groups, one of them comprised of the family’s few remaining totem users, surrounding Maxilan.

The other group was made of the Black Fire Palace Guards, they sat quietly at the side, saying not a word but giving off an impression of sternness.

There were also two kids, a girl and a boy, next to Maxilan, they were totally black from head to toe, and so thin they were basically skin and bones, wearing clean, newly-changed clothes. They were both practically toddlers, their little hands gripping Maxilan’s clothes tightly, evidently treating him as their only source of comfort.

Seeing that Garen had noticed the two children, Maxilan smiled slightly awkwardly.

"Chief, these are the couple of kids I found on the road, their parents were both killed in the chaos, and I thought they were pretty pitiful, so… You don’t mind, do you?"

After Garen inherited the position, he and Edney were both assimilated into the Trejons family line. At first the two of them were just normal citizens, but once they entered the family, they were now truly members of the family. That was why they both called him Chief.

With a sweep of his eyes, the two kids’ full body conditions immediately appeared in his vision, completely unobscured. He was using the Secret Technique aura flow to sense the intricate parts of these living bodies’ conditions.

"It’s okay." After checking that the two of them weren’t spies sent by the other powers, Garen decided to leave them be.

The two children, however, were terrified into hiding behind Maxilan.

Just then, all the people in charge came up to Garen one by one, to give in their reports.

"Chief, I’m Leian, in charge of the chain stores. Right now the stores aren’t in very good condition, they seriously need people to help in defense, we could only gather all our hired power to gather everything from the warehouses up and defend those. But even now we’re barely holding in under Chief’s name, it probably won’t last long."

The one who spoke was a fatty.

"Guard One, take two people to help with defense, help organize the defense for all the shops." Garen said calmly.

Beside him, three people stood from the Black Fire Palace. They walked up to the fatty wordlessly. Taking two guards with him, the fatty rushed out of the estate, and returned to defend their family stores.

"Chief, more than half of our farms were taken over by hooligans."

"Send two Black Fire Palace guards over to subdue them, execute all the hooligans." Garen waved his hand, sending out two regular Black Fire Palace guards. Even regular Black Fire Palace guards would be in a completely different league from these warring farmers.

"Many of the houses and about a dozen shop lots around the auction house have been emptied out, Chief, I suggest we immediately expand our territory, and claim all that land!" A thin person said in a deep voice.

"Guard Two, you take two people over." Garen sent out one of the four most elite Black Fire Palace guards.

One by one, the people in charge came up and gave their reports, while Garen sent out the Black Fire Palace guards one by one to solve their problems.

It wasn’t just that the family fortune took a hit, unexpectedly, the family property expanded as well. It wasn’t expansion through power, taking advantage of the situation to expand, but rather two small families came to find them of their own accord, intending to become Trejons family branches.

"Branches? Interesting." Garen touched the stubble on his chin. "Where are they?"

"I arranged for them to rest at the back." Edney replied softly. "I asked about their situation, both families couldn’t afford to protect themselves in the chaos, and after hearing of your… reputation, they came here to seek us out as their last hope."

"As the family’s branch, that means all their family property will be assimilated into the main family, and they’re still willing?" Garen asked with interest.

"They have no other choice." Edney explained, "The chiefs of both families aren’t nobles with land, one’s a viscount and the other’s a baron, their general situation is…" She was interrupted by Garen with a wave before she could begin.

"That’s enough, I have no interest in their affairs, you just take some people to settle their matters, if we bring in their property, what do we need to do in return?" Garen asked the key question directly. If there wasn’t some danger approaching, there was no way that these nobles would be willing to join another family, and hand over everything they had.

"They’re two middle-sized families, they hope they can use this money to earn your protection over these two families."

"There will probably be a lot more of these things, you handle it directly, Big Sister Edney. I’ll give you some people."

Garen waved his hand, sending Guard Three and five Black Fire Palace guards to stand behind Edney.

By then there were only four people left in the Black Fire Palace Guard, and that was including the last Guard Four. Three of the strongest four Black Fire Palace Guards had been sent out to handle trifling matters.

"Chief, then what about us? What can we do?!" The modified human Komodo and the other large man stood together, asking stiffly.

"You guys go with Big Brother Maxilan, listen to whatever he says."

"Lord Chief, then we…?" A female representative stood out from the group of five Form One totem users that had always followed the family faithfully.

Garen was a lot more polite towards these people.

"If you’re willing, you can be in charge of one shop each, or you could be supervisors of the auction. To be honest, I would still hope for the auction business to bloom."

Chapter 440: Chaos 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The female representative was a middle-aged woman nearing forty, she mused for a bit and then discussed it for a while with the companions behind her, eventually nodding.

"Thank you for your faith in us, Chief, we are willing to help develop the auction."

"That’s good." Garen sent the last of the four Guards and two others to escort them to the auction house.

Everyone in the family firmly believed in everything he said, which made him very satisfied. There were all sorts of rumors going around outside, saying that the Kingdom was about to be conquered by monsters, and many families with power had escaped together with the three departments.

The ones who stayed behind weren’t powerless, like Garen or the highest level people such as the Grand Duke or the First Princess, they all had a few trump cards in hand.

And then there were the smarter ones, who saw that most of the biggest powers hadn’t left, so they stayed behind as well.

This caused most of the Kingdom to end up empty, while the remaining nobles were busy snatching up resources and territory, whereas naturally no one bothered with the civilian chaos. Everyone was only bothered with their own territory.

No one at all bothered with the public space.

After dealing with these matters, Garen took the last two Black Fire Palace guards along with him and left the estate, rushing towards his cousin’s house.

On the way there he could see some horse corpses waylaid on the road, houses lit on fire, robbers hustling for supplies, and some noble-looking people crashing up shops and civilian houses.

The three of them rode on three Aberrated Unihorn Horses, rushing straight for the Cloud Light District.

Of the three main districts in the Kingdom, the Cloud Light District was the most chaotic.

Most of the people living here were officials or rich merchants, so there were the most bandits and robberies around here too.

Garen and the two others encountered a blockage by some groups of fearless bandits, but after the Black Fire Palace guards sprayed out poisonous liquids and melted them into pools of acid, no one else dared to stop them.

After more than twenty minutes, Garen arrived straight at his cousin’s door in the Cloud Light District.

Outside the small white building by the roadside, there were a few bodies lying around, and large puddles of bloody water that had nearly dried up on the floor.

Garen had his horse step in the bloody water, emitting wet splashing sounds.

The two Black Fire Palace guards jumped off their horses, and started scanning around their surroundings quickly, eliminating all uncertain elements.

Garen glanced at the second and third floors of the building.

The building was completely quiet, as though there was nobody inside.

Garen rode his horse and took one round around the building. He didn’t see anyone. The two Black Fire Palace guards burst through the doors and searched the place, but couldn’t come up with anything either.

His cousin and the others had evidently left in advance.

Garen was still rather worried, so he turned around and took the other two towards the White Phoenix Forest Academy. This was where he had asked his cousin and the others to go if anything happened.

******************

Dani felt as though today was all just a dream.

She had reached home in the middle of the night, and was planning to have a good night’s beauty sleep, but she was just drifting off when her older sister pulled her up, put the clothes on her and then rushed her out.

Her sister’s best friend, Sylvia, who was also working at the palace, came with them too.

The two of them both looked rather worried and hurried.

She saw her sister and Sylvia meet a middle-aged man at the door, this man had a group of guards with her, and said something to her sister sternly, the two of them seemed to be hesitating at the door.

But Sylvia seemed to say something as well, and then her sister finally agreed.

Her sister pulled Dani away, and followed the middle-aged man as they left their building.

When she left, her mind was still a mess, as she wasn’t properly awake.

Suddenly, there was a piercing siren from the sky, shocking her awake.

The three girls were taken by the middle-aged man to a campsite. It was a large empty space, and there were many white tents standing beside it. There were already many people gathered there.

A nobleman calling himself Cohen came quickly and took them away, the three of them following a group of extravagantly-dressed men and women as they raced towards the large lake at the back of the Kingdom. On the way there, these people kept pointing and whispering about Sylvia, as though they were appraising a product, making her feel terrible.

"I told you we already had too many people. You still insisted on bringing her along! Great, she alone would be fine, but now she brought two burdens with her as well." The female leader’s shrill voice could be vaguely heard.

"She is Little Brother’s only daughter, after all, let’s help her where we can." The man pleaded softly.

After that, the two of them continued complaining and pleading respectively. Dani suddenly felt unspeakably frustrated.

"Relax, it’s fine." A gentle man’s voice came beside Dani. It was a handsome man in white, "I’m like you all, I’m also a hitchhiker following this family as they retreat. My name is Kane. What’s yours?" The man’s gentle smile seemed to have washed away some of Dani’s worries.

"I’m Dani."

"Oh, you’re one of Miss Sylvia two friends." It dawned on Kane. "Where are your sister and Miss Sylvia?"

"Up ahead." Dani looked up straight, and saw her sister and Sylvia standing in front of a woman in a red dress, lowering their heads as they listened to the woman speak with an expression of disgust.

Kane seemed to have seen them as well. He rubbed Dani’s hair, hard. "Relax, it’s okay."

"Kane!"

Suddenly someone called him from a distance.

"Come here!"

"I’ll go over there a bit." Kane turned around and hurried towards the voice.

Dani watched him leave, and then started to survey her surroundings, extremely bored.

They were surrounded by guards in heavy white armor, with a few men and women in differently-colored robes mixed among them. These people all looked arrogant, and looked at others with contempt. They only talked to each other, as though even talking to normal people would damage their status.

"What’s so good about them!" Dani pursed her little lips.

Suddenly, there came a sound she might never forget for the rest of her life.

Not too far away from her, a sudden scream gave her a huge shock.

Dani instantly woke up, and she stared towards that direction. Kane, who had just left, was now holding his stomach, kneeling on the ground as blood kept flowing from his body, pooling on the ground. His gaze was painful and despairing, helpless and powerless.

Just like them, he was someone who followed this group afterward, according to what they said, he was also a friend brought by some other family member.

Dani seemed to have frozen utterly.

She felt as though the only one left in the world was that man moaning in agony, there was a golden-haired man with a twisted expression in front of him shaking the blood off his blade, his face full of contempt.

"Mur… murder…" Dani felt her mind go blank.

The man who was just standing in front of her, who had just been speaking with her, that man with the gentle smile. Right now his body slanted down, and fell down with a whumph, while none of the surrounding guards even gave him a glance, their expressions cold.

Dani felt her mouth go dry, an unprecedented terror suddenly gushing out of her brain.

The person who was just alive and kicking and standing in front of her, was now lying on the floor, rapidly becoming an icy cold body.

This was the first time she witnessed a murder.

Her first time seeing a dead person, a person who died in front of her…

Her mind was a total blank. She didn’t know when her sister came up to her, and didn’t know when Big Sister Sylvia pulled her into her arms.

She just kept replaying Kane’s final helpless gaze in her brain. That gaze seemed to be looking at him.

"It’s fine… it’s fine." Her sister’s voice kept coming from beside her ear.

"How do we deal with these burdens?"

"We’ve no time, put them in Cabin Three."

"But that’s for livestock…"

"We have no more space for them, if they want to come then come, if they don’t then scram!" A piercing woman’s voice reached their ears.

Dani felt cold all over. She had seen what happened to Kane, their status was just like his, maybe that would happen to them as well…

It was her first time feeling, that the world outside could be so dangerous.

All her life, she had lived under her sister’s protection, but this was the first time, the first time she saw the cruelty of the real world outside.

When these normally polite and graceful nobles revealed their fangs, they were even crueler than beasts, treating human lives like livestock.

The girls forced themselves to follow behind this group of people, there were about a dozen more people like them, all with the same status.

The disgusted faces and impatient voices of the nobles in front of them kept reaching Dani’s ears, and she realized for the first time just how childish and ignorant her previous life was.

Every day she fought with her sister self-indulgently, over trivial matters, over small allowances, she became stubborn and illogical, occasionally taking some things out to sell, until she thought herself familiar with the Kingdom’s Cloud Light District. She dealt generously with the hooligans on the street, calling them her sisters.

But now that it had come to this time, these surroundings, those normal little hooligan bosses were as helpless as chicks faced with the powerful guards and totem users around her.

On the following journey, the group kept encountering attacks by hooligans and bandits, people kept dying around her, while those who were badly hurt were quickly abandoned.

Dani’s heart grew colder and colder, and more and more scared.

She saw the same hint of worry on her sister’s face, and the shadow on Sister Sylvia’s.

Before they knew it, their team was nearing the large lake behind the Kingdom.

Dani’s mind was in complete chaos, and she was barely aware of anything.

Vaguely, she heard shouts of surprise from up ahead, and the whole group had stopped instantly. It seemed that someone had blocked the road.

"Scram!"

A cold man’s voice came from the distance.

"Lord Earl! We truly don’t have the person you’re…" That shrill woman’s voice kept pleading. As though the power of the person ahead was way beyond hers. She had lost all of her confidence from before.

Bam! Ahh!!

After one scream, the woman’s voice vanished.

"Everyone stop right there, stay where you are, and let milord examine you!" One of the group’s female totem users called out, trying to appease them. The guards began maintaining order.

There were almost a hundred people here, the front was slightly panicky, but they quickly quieted down.

The time ticked by.

"Big Sister!? Why are you guys here?" Suddenly, a surprised man’s voice came from the front.

Dani raised her head from her sister’s embrace, and glanced over.

But she saw a familiar figure.

It was Acacia! But how did he find them?

Dani was instantly like a drowning person who saw someone familiar, her heart surging with warmth and a sense of security, as though her body was instantly filled up.

Dressed in white, he rushed over hurriedly. A few opportunistic nobles and totem users came with him.

"I’ve been looking for you guys for so long! Why didn’t you listen to me, why did you come all the way here!? If it weren’t for the fact that someone saw you all and told me, I might not have made it in time to catch up with you! What’s the matter with Dani?"

"She was shocked…" Her sister’s replied softly.

"Come!" Acacia turned around and barked.

Soon enough a figure dressed fully in black armor came up to them, and lowered his head wordlessly.

"Carry her, we’re going straight to the Royal Hospital! Forget it, I’ll do it myself!"

Dazedly. Dani felt herself lifted by a broad chest, and an unprecedented sense of security flowed out of her heart.

Huh, so Cia had a side like this too. Dani had never seen this side of his, as though her companion since childhood was suddenly unfamiliar to her. He became more blinding, more sparkling, and was beginning to merge with some fantasy in her heart…

She plastered her face to his chest tightly, and finally fell asleep in a short while.

Chapter 441: Chaos 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen made a trip to White Phoenix Forest Academy and couldn’t find his cousins, which was when he knew things had gotten bad. It was very likely that they had followed an escaping group and were planning to leave the Kingdom.

He had always tried not to interfere with his cousins’ lives, hoping they could live their lives peacefully. He tried his best to leave their lines of sight, and prevented others from finding out his relationship with them as well. After all, his villainous reputation as the Black Fire Palace Master was growing out of hand, it wasn’t a good thing to get involved with him.

Although there was no way he could truly fool the significant factions, it was still better than being completely public about it.

But he didn’t think this would be the result, his cousins misunderstanding his power and not listening to his opinions, telling them to go to the White Phoenix Forest Academy that didn’t look like much but actually had a deep and powerful background. Instead, they were convinced by Sylvia, and had left together with her distant relatives.

When Garen realized this, he immediately rushed towards the evacuation point, the large lake behind the Secret Service, and directly set up a barricade in front of the only entrance. Anyone who wanted to enter had to undergo his examination first.

After stopping several groups of people, he finally managed to stop his cousins. After some advise, Hathaway finally left the group with Dani.

Several members of the group were casually killed by Garen, so they left quietly.

Carrying little Dani, Garen rushed directly to the Kingdom’s Royal Hospital. Most of the doctors had chosen to leave with the nobles, only a few older doctors staying put. As they grew older, apparently, they began to look at some matters more openly.

In the clean white hospital room

An old doctor dressed in white took a thermometer out of little Dani’s mouth, pulling up her eyelids and mouth. Next to them, Hathaway was waiting anxiously, and asked for some details.

"She was probably shocked, her heart couldn’t take it so suddenly. She’ll be fine after a night’s rest." The old doctor finally concluded.

"Thank you, Doctor Hurley." Hathaway hurriedly thanked him.

Garen gave his thanks as well.

Hurley nodded calmly.

"I still have other patients, I’ll go for now."

"May I ask, are there many patients in the Kingdom?" Garen asked suddenly.

Hurley glanced at Garen. He knew this Black Fire Palace Master, and he didn’t just know him, he was very familiar with him, in fact. Because the Royal Hospital had to deal with too many of the people he had executed or punished.

Even though this person was powerful in court, Hurley didn’t like him.

"Why must I answer that?" He retorted stiffly.

Garen was slightly taken aback. Seeing how this old man had rushed over just now, he had thought his reputation had scared the doctor, but this was one stubborn old bag of bones.

A young green-haired nobleman next to them immediately raged.

"Damn you! How dare you speak like that to the Palace Master!?"

Clang!

The man drew the sword from his waist, and was about to attack.

Garen raised his hand to stop him. He examined the stubborn old man in front of him carefully.

"Interesting, it’s rare for someone to know my identity and still not fear me."

"I’m about to die soon anyway, why should I fear you?" The old man replied stiffly. "There are enough dead people in the Kingdom, I won’t make a difference either way."

He glanced at Hathaway.

"Alright, since it’s not a serious injury, I’ll take my leave first, there are still many patients I need to settle over there."

"Thank you, doctor." Hathaway hurriedly thanked him again.

They watched the old man leave straightaway.

Surprisingly, Garen wasn’t angry, it was rare for him to meet a normal person who had no power but wasn’t afraid of death.

"Oh, right, Big Sister, where’s your colleague?" He suddenly realized that woman was nowhere to be seen.

"She didn’t come with us." Hathaway shook her head. After all, no matter how terrible her family was over there, they had still planned to let the girls leave with them. Without knowing Garen’s identity, they were still willing to give the girls a chance. But as soon as Garen arrived and killed several of them barehanded, the relationship instantly changed.

No matter what, Sylvia couldn’t have immediately left with them. She was part of that family, after all. There were relatives who she cared for there, and relatives who cared for her.

"After this, Big Sister, you should still go to White Phoenix Forest Academy, I’ve arranged matters there." Garen frowned. "Prynne, Andel and Marin are all there, they’re all people you know. You don’t have to worry about only meeting strangers there."

"Mn…"

Hathaway was like a guilty child, lowering her head and not daring to meet Garen’s eyes.

She felt as though the situation had changed, before this she had always been the one scolding Garen at this angle, but now it was the opposite.

Before she knew it, Garen was now half a head taller than her. At first she wanted to gather her courage to retort him a little, but remembering that other awkward relationship between them, whatever courage she had immediately faltered.

"Alright, alright." Garen took her into his embrace lightly. Patting her back. "It’s okay, it’s all okay. No matter what I’ll always be here, I’ll take care of you."

His cousin’s soft body went slightly stiff as she leaned into Garen’s arms, feeling their chests plastered against each other. An intense sense of safety surged into her heart before she knew it.

"Sorry… I shouldn’t have disobeyed you." Hathaway bit her lip, and said softly.

"Before this you were taking care of me, but now it’s my turn to take care of you." Garen let go of her. Towards this cousin of his, although he didn’t feel as deeply as the Acacia from before, he could still tell that she truly cared for him.

If others treated him sincerely, he wouldn’t repay them with falseness either.

"Okay, once Dani is properly rested, I’ll have someone send you all to White Phoenix Forest Academy." Garen said softly.

Suddenly, the hospital ward door was knocked open.

Bam!

A young man dressed in white rushed into the room hurriedly.

"Garen, is Dani okay?!"

"Prynne?" Garen immediately recognized him.

"I was looking all over the outer city! But I just couldn’t find Sis Sofie! In the end it was still because you were dominant enough to block the exit point directly, so no one could leave until you found them! Impressive as usual!" As soon as Prynne saw that Hathaway and the others were there, he instantly heaved a sigh of relief, and gave Garen a huge thumbs-up.

There was also a girl with a purple-red ponytail behind him.

The girl was pretty, tall and slender, and wore figure-fitting white clothes with a waist belt.

"Marin! You came too?" Hathaway recognized the visitor as well.

"Sis Sofie, where do you all run off too? Prynne and I looked everywhere but we couldn’t find you!" Marin complained as soon as she came in.

"It was my fault…" Hathaway smiled slightly bitterly, and as though suddenly realizing how close she was to Garen, her face turned red and she pulled away imperceptibly.

Just then another girl squeezed in through the door, with flax-colored shoulder-length hair and purple-red eyes, like beautiful ambers.

"Sis Sofie!" She pounced into Hathaway’s arms in an instant.

"Andel!" Hathaway was slightly panicked, she was actually closest to Andel, back then when they left the Vanderman estate, the two of them had traveled together.

"Thank goodness you’re fine!" Andel hugged Hathaway, her eyes reddening.

Suddenly she realized that Hathaway seemed to be standing too close to Garen next to her, and instantly looked confused.

Prynne noticed too, and understanding quickly dawned on him.

"Okay, okay, the girls can catch up in the room, and chat a bit. Garen, let’s go out and talk?"

He led the way out of the ward.

Garen hinted at the two Black Fire Palace guards to follow, and went out as well.

There was a clean and tidy corridor outside the room. The two Black Fire Palace guards and the green-haired nobleman who wanted to suck up to Garen had already chased the other patients away, and everything around the room was quiet.

Prynne and Garen left a few totem user guards behind to protect the girls, before walking towards an empty hospital room on the left.

Garen noticed that a short, fat man with a huge aura had also followed beside Prynne.

Judging by this aura, this guy had to be at least Form Three and above.

He closed the door after entering the room. Garen turned around and glanced at the fatty.

"Not bad, you did well for yourself! A Form Three totem user as your guard, how extravagant!"

There were only the two of them in the room, so Garen let loose as well, and didn’t maintain his image like with outsiders.

"I still can’t compare to you." Prynne suddenly gave a dirty laugh. He went closer and asked quietly, "Hehe, Hathaway’s tits feel good, don’t they?"

Garen was instantly speechless.

"From what I see, Hathaway’s butt is pretty tight too, and there isn’t any gap between her long legs when she puts them together, so it seems you haven’t really gotten into it yet." Prynne abandoned his usual graceful mannerism, and smiled pervertedly.

"Are you saying you finished Marin?" Garen squeezed out one sentence after a long time.

"Of course, who do you think I am!" Prynne flicked the hair at his forehead, as though showing off his good looks. "But Marin still can’t compare to that cousin of yours, tsk-tsk, that small waist, those long legs, and of course that chest, and she’s also an official with the Royal Guard, that means she’s not like those totem users who never train at all and have no power, until their bodies lose their shape too. Big Sister’s figure, if clamped onto your body… Tsk-tsk…" Prynne was obviously started to fantasize.

Garen kicked his shin fiercely.

"You dare fantasize about my, Garen’s fiancee, do you have a death wish!" He scolded while laughing.

"Ow!" Prynne cried out in pain, "I just thought about it for a while, it’s not like you lost anything! I’m telling you now, back then I was planning on chasing Sis Sofie, if it weren’t for you suddenly making her your fiancee, I would probably have been on the full-on offense by now!"

"Then what about Marin?"

"Of course she’ll sleep with us! Everyone on one bed, two beauties serving me at once, ducking under the covers naked…" Prynne was starting to fantasize again.

"You seem to be living pretty comfortably recently." Garen said pointedly.

"Naturally." Prynne chucked. "Why don’t you come with me for a few days?"

"I’m busy with work, do you think everyone’s as free as you, with a grandfather up there supporting you?" Garen couldn’t help but kick him again. This fella used to be fairly serious, but now he was obviously getting more and more perverted.

"Alright, alright, on to the serious matters!" Pynne had enough of joking around, and stopped smiling as well. "I happened to bring my grandfather’s request as well on this trip here. After His Majesty passed, the situation in the Kingdom has changed. Since you have no intention of leaving either, I bet you must surely know the secret of the inner palace. Is that true?"

Garen was not surprised at all, Prynne’s grandfather Benoc was one of the Empire’s long-time peak-level fighters. Unlike the newly-risen Garen, Benoc had deep connections, countless trump cards, and naturally knew more secrets than usual.

"Your grandfather means to?"

"Our family supports the First Princess. Grand Duke Cody also intends to fight for that position, they support the Fourth Prince, probably to make him a puppet. Right now, there are four powers that can truly decide the situation in the Kingdom." Prynne said solemnly.

"Which four?"

"My grandfather Grand Duke Benoc and the First Princess are one, Grand Duke Cody and the Fourth Prince are one, together with the support of the minister Veska. And then there are the residual palace powers controlled by the Silver Palace Master, Lord Edin and yourself, as well as the last Little Alliance."

"Little Alliance? What Little Alliance?"

"The War Guild, Assassin’s Guild, Mercenary's Guild, Kovistan Merchant’s Guild, Forger’s Guild. The five groups joined together to form the Little Alliance, founded a long time ago, but never revealed until now. They represent most of the middle-lower powers in the country, and they have many important trump cards as well. Although they don’t have many peak-level fighters, but there are quite a few of high-level totem users who are willing to fight with their lives on the line. They shouldn’t be underestimated. This is exactly what my grandfather wanted me to tell you. Don’t underestimate them."

"Oh?" Garen naturally wouldn’t underestimate this Little Alliance. They call themselves the Little Alliance, but out of the five guilds, he didn’t really know much about the others, but he was also a member of the War Guild himself, so he knew a little bit insider information about the War Guild’s power. They weren’t very strong, but they weren’t by any means weak either.

The other four were at the same level as them, so they couldn’t be all that weak too.

"My grandfather and the others call the Little Alliance Five-Colored, the Five-Colored Alliance, because their official alliance flag has a mix of five colors." Prynne brought Garen information about the general state of the Kingdom.

"Now the entire Kingdom has been split into four by these four powers, out of the three districts in the Kingdom, the Palace District has been controlled by you and the Silver Palace Master. The Cloud Light District is under Duke Cody. The Trading District is under the Five-Colored Alliance and my grandfather, since it is the largest in area.

"Then the area outside the city?"

"All abandoned." Prynne shrugged. "Too many nobles ran away, their farmers and laborers, as well as their guards mostly rushed into the Kingdom, it’s too hard now to even maintain order. Once they hear that the monsters have come attacking, who would dare to go out of the city and walk into certain death?"

Garen nodded.

"What about the three departments? Anybody stayed behind?"

Chapter 442: Chaos 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I didn’t pay any attention to that, but my grandfather said that the three departments have utterly given up on Kovistan, this situation is now set, and all their power has gathered in Daniela now. The situation there is even worse, but there’s still hope of salvaging it." Prynne said simply.

"But if it goes on like this, the situation in the Kingdom will only get worse, without farms, where will we get our food? Our daily necessities?" Garen frowned.

"So we need to stabilize the situation as soon as possible." Prynne shrugged. "My grandfather’s plan is for us to join forces, call a large-scale nobility meeting, create a Noble Senate, and unify the situation in the Kingdom, or rather in Kovistan."

"True, right now all the powers are no different, nobody is willing to bow to anyone else, so this is the only method to stabilize the situation as soon as possible." Garen nodded. "I agree, let’s see what the others think."

"Great, let’s not waste any time, I’ll go back now to report to Grandfather."

"Okay, I was about to go settle some things too." Garen agreed instantly, "Take care of my cousin and the others for me."

"Of course!"

As soon as they left the hospital. Garen and that green-haired noble messenger boy immediately rode their horses towards the National Department of Experimentation.

The National Department of Experimentation was a critical technical lab that Avic always supported wholeheartedly, and it had been under Veska’s jurisdiction this whole time. The finances also leaned heavily this way.

The method of handling the meat of aberrated monsters so that civilians could eat them as well came from here too.

Taking advantage of the chaos in the Kingdom now, Garen headed straight for the National Department of Experimentation rapidly.

The two of them were followed by more than ten aberrated horses, each of them ridden by the green-haired noble’s subordinates and guards. There were two Form One totem users among them, and the rest were all normal people trained in martial arts. But their bodies looked strong and sturdy, so they had an impressive presence as well.

On the way, the group went straight through everything, not afraid of anything. Wherever they went, everyone just let them past, by now even some bandits and vigilantes who couldn’t tell all that clearly had no choice but to avoid such a formation.

"What’s your name?" Garen finally remembered this young man who had passed him the message.

The green-haired nobleman immediately looked gleefully surprised.

"My name is Bivon! Bivon Caelus! Sir, I am your avid supporter!"

"You did well this time." Garen nodded, slightly accepting this fella’s show of loyalty. Since he had this sort of gaze, he did not fear his terrible reputation, and had enough guts, it was enough for him to be considered a talent, one that could be used.

As soon as he said that, not only the green-haired man, but even the host of men and women behind him all looked happy. But they also knew that this was just the beginning, because the biggest problem with following the Black Fire Palace Master wasn’t getting him to accept them. But the pressure that came after that acceptance.

The Black Fire Palace Master had executed many and offended far too many more in the Palace, but anyone who could reach the inner palace had to have some background, yet Garen killed them without hesitation, no matter who went to plead for mercy. Or rather, he didn’t give anybody any time to plead, and just killed them straight away.

That was how he offended a huge group of people, but with Garen’s villainous reputation there suppressing them, nobody dared to make a move. Even then, it was a small matter to manipulate some things in the shadows.

The Black Fire Palace Master was strong, but he wasn’t undefeatable in the Kingdom. The two Grand Dukes, the defense minister Lord Veska, and even without these three, Garen was still alone, a few more Form Four fighters gathering their tactics together would still pose a huge threat to him.

Garen knew where his limit was too.

One of two Form Fours he might not mind, three or four might not be too much, but seven or eight of them, combining the power of their tactics would make a formidable power. After all, he wasn’t a Form Five yet, faced with Form Fours, if he were to fall into a formation that gathered power such as tactical formations, he would be stuck in a dead end no matter how many lives he had to waste.

And besides, the two Grand Dukes definitely had an Ultimate Heirloom each.

The Black Crow Formation back then was just a forgery of an Ultimate Heirloom, and it was already so powerful, enough to fully use Form Four power. If it was a true Ultimate Heirloom, used in the proper hands, who knew how strong it could be.

After sorting out the information he just received, he had also arrived at the National Department of Experimentation.

The street outside the door was cold and empty, with nobody at all in sight, rubbish scattered all over the floor, papers and clothes, shop signs, overturned carriages, and even two corpses burnt to a crisp.

Right now he was in the west area outside the Kingdom’s city walls.

He was surrounded everywhere by large swathes of black mountain ground, and of the whole Department of Experimentation, only one empty street was connected to the road outside, which made it the only exit and entrance.

The Department of Experimentation was in the middle of the mountains, just like a ring, surrounding several tall buildings and factories inside. He stood outside the large entrance and looked in, seeing a mushroom-shaped white tower standing there quietly.

At the top of the tower, there were occasional flashes of blue lightning circling around it.

"Palace Master, what are we here to do?" The green-haired man, Bivon, asked softly.

"Looking for something, something I had given to His Majesty in the past." Garen replied calmly, not attempting to hide anything.

"Come, let’s go in and look!"

Garen led the way and rode straight towards the tightly-shut door.

Just as his horse’s neck was about to crash into the large door, a red shadow instantly flashed by.

Boom!!

The door was directly smashed open, the metal door more than ten centimeters thick fell down just like that, and even large chunks of the tall wall on either side were ripped out.

There was the sound of crackling explosions in the air, but no light appeared.

"Hm?" Garen glanced at his left hand, the palm and the back of the hand were both charred black. "Invisible electricity?"

When he released the Dragon Shadow from his left hand to smash open the door, he also went numb from the powerful retort of electricity, just a second’s contact was enough to make his entire left(1) hand completely charred. The Nine-Headed Dragon’s defensive Totem Light was destroyed just like that. It made Garen feel the Nine-Headed Dragon’s defense was falling behind.

As he began going to more dangerous places, even though the Nine-Headed Dragon’s dragon skin defense was considerably strong among low-level totems, it was still too far away compared to others of the same level. Recently its Totem Light kept getting easily destroyed.

After all, whenever the Totem Light was destroyed once, that meant the totem had been grievously injured once. To other totem users, it was a terrifying injury that would require years of healing and recovery if done naturally.

Normally, this was a very rare possibility, because after all totem users’ Totem Light was twice as strong as the totem itself.

But to Garen, this situation was happening more and more frequently recently.

No wonder the Nine-Headed Dragon had nine lives, between defense and reviving, it had chosen the latter to evolve into. Only then did Garen begin to understand.

Feeling for the Nine-Headed Dragon’s condition in the dark space, one of the dragon heads had begun to wither up again.

Garen quickly took twenty points off his potential points, and patched it up, returning the nine lives to full once more.

But out of his previous potential points, he was now only left with slightly more than fifty.

He led the others into the Department of Experimentation, taking striding steps.

Inside the door was a ring of grassy land, equivalent in area to three or four football fields, unnaturally wide.

The white tower was standing right in the middle, arches of blue electricity continuously sparkling around its peak, its surface as smooth as a mirror, with a strange futuristic feel to it.

Garen didn’t even look at the other tall buildings around it, walking straight towards the white tower, while the others followed behind him.

There was the sound of many rapid footsteps around them, and even some heavy stomping.

Whoosh!!

A beam of white light brushed past Garen’s body horizontally. It nearly touched his nose.

"It’s the White Guard!!" Green-haired Bivon was slightly panicked, and hurriedly reminded Garen, "Palace Master, the White Guards are the Department of Experimentation’s best masterpiece, half human and half totem, they’re very powerful, and not afraid of dying! There are a hundred of them in total, they’re all made from dead high-level totem users. You must be careful, Palace Master!"

"How strong are they?" Garen had already seen the people in white-armor surrounding them.

"That depends on how strong the totem user they were made from had been…" Bivon’s face had gone white as he looked at the circle of white-armored people around them.

These people had their entire bodies hidden under the white armor, two blood-red crystals on their helmets in place of their eyes, glimmering with a faint red light. They held a sword in one hand and the other had been engineered into a silver cylinder, shining with a vague white light inside, as though it could spray out at any moment.

"Looks like this is one of Veska’s trump cards…" Garen glanced around appreciatively. "They should be somewhat similar to my Black Fire Guards, but they seem to be even stronger by a little. Tsk-tsk… there are fifty of them in three waves, and more than ten Spiritualized ones… impressive, as expected!"

The surrounding White Guards seemed oblivious to everything, as though they hadn’t heard what Garen said at all. They all stood quietly on the spot, completely motionless, not attacking or letting them pass.

"Veska, looks like you don’t nearly have as may back-up White Guards as my Black Fire Guards, right? If you don’t want to waste your power, then let me pass. I’m just here to take what was originally mine." Garen harrumphed, and ignored the White Guards blocking in front of him completely, riding his horse forth. Going straight for the white tower.

These powers and a few more trump cards would pose a certain threat to him as well, but he took the most pride in his survival power, without enough same-level power to suppress him, even if something could utterly destroy his power, he still believed that he could escape in one piece. That was probably the terrifying power of the Nine Life talent.

Bivon and the others followed Garen, terrified, and as expected, the White Guard in front of them kept retreating, naturally opening a path for them.

Veska must have a method that allowed him to see the situation here.

Garen understood now, the other party didn’t want to lock horns with him, and he wouldn’t go looking for trouble either, declaring war on Veska and all that. After all, he still didn’t know how strong that fellow was, he was also at the peak of Form Four. And he was connected to the other Grand Duke, Cody, too.

Riding his horse to the foot of the white tower, Garen leaped off the horse and strode to the door of the tower.

The door to the round white tower had naturally spun open, and there were a few researchers in white bustling about inside, as though they hadn’t noticed the changes outside at all. Each of them looked utterly lost in their work.

Garen strode into the tall tower. A voice came from behind him suddenly.

"Your thing is in the third secret room on the second floor." It was still that old, traditional-sounding voice, Veska’s voice.

Garen smiled, strode through the crowd, and followed the stairs up to the second floor, while the others followed closely behind.

On the second floor’s white corridor, the door to the third secret room was clearly glowing with a faint red light, as though showing Garen the way.

This light was slightly piercing, even with Garen’s sight he had to narrow his eyes, while the rest seemed to not feel it at all.

He strode towards the secret room.

There were two people in white standing guard outside the secret room. Seeing Garen approach, they actually lifted their feet as though ready to kick open the door.

"Without a decree from His Majesty or the defense minister, you cannot go in!"

"Scram!" Bam! Garen pushed aside the people blocking him, he strode into the lab, took a glance around everything, and instantly identified where the Green Vine Sphere was.

The thing was kept in a crystal bottle, a cylindrical crystal glass bottle, filled with a green liquid.

The whole Green Vine Sphere was like a green ball of thread with claws and teeth, bits of thread sticking out everywhere.

Garen walked over.

He smashed the glass with a bam, and reached his hand in directly, fishing the Green Vine Sphere out and pressing it onto his shoulder.

Psst…

The Green Vine Sphere waved its green tentacles around madly, rapidly piercing them into the flesh on Garen’s shoulder, and had completely melted into him in no time.

"Let’s go!"

Garen turned around and left the lab, if he stayed here any longer, he was afraid Veska’s weak will couldn’t take it.

Translator’s Note:

Raws said ‘right’, which directly conflicts with the previous bit, so I’m assuming left.

Chapter 443: Caeserton 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Black Fire Palace in the Kingdom.

Garen sat on his Palace Master’s throne, carefully playing with the Green Vine Sphere in his hand.

This little thing was like a small animal, crawling from his left hand to his left shoulder. After he caught it and put it on the back of his hand, it began to crawl towards his left shoulder tirelessly again.

Garen kept bringing it down, and watching as it kept crawling up.

Ivycius stood behind the throne, holding a sword with both arms as he leaned on a round black pillar. Watching Garen play with the Green Vine Sphere out of boredom.

"The second Nobility Conference is about to start, aren’t you going?"

Garen smiled.

"How was the first one like? I wasn’t there, but I heard some fun things happened."

Ivycius closed his eyes and rested.

"Just some trivial things."

Garen felt the Green Vine Sphere carefully, saying casually, "All sorts of people joined this Nobility Conference, any middle-level nobles or above can join. Too many cooks spoil the broth, so how could they possibly come up with any good ideas?"

Of all the nobles, most of them were middle-level nobles, these people were all the pillars of the various departments and units, and they tended to make up most of the levels among the nobles too, since they liked to suck up and compare, prioritized their pride and reputation, throwing themselves at the higher powers. At such a time as this, they were probably mostly arguing about how to divide the land in the Kingdom."

Garen could easily imagine what kind of scene that would be.

"It’s different this time, we’re deciding the true state of the Kingdom." Ivycius said calmly.

"We’ve taken over the Palace, who dares to say anything else?" Garen said lazily, "Forget it, might as well make a trip there, and see what those old fogies have to say."

He had gotten enough materials, and the Royal Treasury was still under his control, his people endlessly bringing out large amounts of weapons, supplies and treasures from it.

But he didn’t see the most important item. The Precious Heirloom!

Garen was suspicious because they hadn’t found a single Heirloom in the entire Royal Treasury. That was illogical.

The only possibility was that the royal family surely had another secret treasury. That was where they really kept the Heirloom.

"I won’t go then, I’m currently at a pivotal moment." Ivycius said from behind him.

Garen didn’t bother him either, although Ivycius had been modified into a Dragon Demon, but if he simply force-controlled Ivycius all the time, Ivycius might lose his potential to level up.

Walking out of the palace hall, on the way to the conference hall, many Black Fire Guards walked out of the surrounding corners in the Black Fire Palace.

Some of these guards seemed to walk straight out of the dense foliage, out of the shadows.

Garen walked towards the garden and the flowers, and suddenly countless green plants grew madly, twisting and twining, rapidly forming a silhouette that quickly grew a suit of heavy black armor as though growing fruits.

Within several minutes, the plants in the garden grew into a brand new Black Fire Palace guard, who followed closely behind Garen.

Holding the Green Vine Sphere in his hand, he had already completely understood how the Black Fire Guards were formed.

In other words, the Green Vine Sphere gathered plants to form a body. They needed a plant called varde flowers, and would rapidly hasten the plants’ roots to create the Black Fire Palace Guards.

The Black Fire Guard was completely covered by the suit of armor, and the insides couldn’t be seen, so nobody knew that there weren’t any humans inside their armor, but a congregation of plants instead.

The Green Vine Spheres could only make two hundred Black Fire Guards at any one time, four of them Form Three, also known as the Four Guards, while rest were all Form Two. Their weakness was that they were individually rather weak, but their strength was that they were never afraid of death at any time, and their self-destruct ability was powerful.

Garen had almost used up all the varde flowers in the Black Fire Palace, before he managed to scrape out the numbers for the Black Fire Guards again.

At the same time, he needed to have his servants plant more varde flowers, stimulating them with a special method, a single varde flower only needed two months to bloom, spreading their vines everywhere. And he only needed ten flowers to form one Black Fire Guard.

Other than the Black Fire Guards he sent out, Garen had recreated more than a hundred Black Fire Guards here in the Black Fire Palace, sending them to all parts of the palace, to amp up defense together with the Silver Palace Guards.

The Silver Palace’s Royal Guard wasn’t the same royal guard as they told others outside, but were instead the true inner guard made fully of totem users.

Royal Guards like Big Sister Hathaway were only the outer members, and had no right to interfere in the really important matters.

**************

The Kingdom’s Trading District

Royal Theatre

This huge black building was as large as a football court, standing in the east wing of the palace, it was shaped like a huge ship, and had Kovistan’s black-red flag in front of it.

The Royal Theatre’s square was already filled to the brim with people.

Out of the entire crowd, three groups were particularly eye-catching.

Three groups of people dressed in fighting clothes stood together respectively, their military uniforms being white, black, and dark blue each. They were the Empire’s Three Armies, the Hawks of Dawn, the Third Heavy Armor Regiment, and the last one, the Navy Flag.

These Three Armies were the main forces defending the West Farm. And now their people had all returned to the Kingdom, which meant something intriguing.

The rest of the empty spaces were filled with the major and minor nobles from all areas.

The carriages kept arriving, and occasionally there were totem beasts like colossal birds slowly descending onto the square.

By the time Garen arrived with the Black Fire Guard, it was already afternoon, and the sky was growing dim.

Four extremely tall monsters with really long legs appeared in front of the theatre, carrying four bright fire basins on their backs.

These four monsters looked like black buffaloes, it was just that compared to the regular buffaloes, their legs were too tall and long. They were over ten meters tall, and looked unnaturally strange.

"Whose totem beasts are those?" Garen curiously asked the white-haired noble lady leading the way.

"Palace Master, they are the ornamental Aberrated beasts belonging to the theatre’s original owner, Earl Eli. They’re not totems." The young white-haired woman replied quietly.

"Oh? Aberrated beasts?" Garen felt as though Aberration was influencing life in this whole world more and more.

They walked onto the square, and the nobles who had been chatting now fell silent, glancing over at them.

Some of them bowed while the others looked wary, others curious. But they all opened up a path for him.

Garen walked past the crowd, followed by four Black Fire Guards, the black cape on the Black Fire Palace Master’s billowing in the wind, flapping loudly.

In front of the theatre’s large arching white door, Veska and the other two Grand Dukes were chatting.

"The Black Fire Palace Master is here!"

The herald roared loudly.

The three of them hurriedly stopped talking, and looked towards Garen’s direction.

Veska was expressionless, the slightly plump Grand Duke Cody looked calm, and just nodded at Garen.

Of them all, only Grand Duke Benoc, the tall and skinny white-haired old man gave Garen a friendly smile.

Garen smiled back.

There weren’t any guards around the three of them, so they made a small empty space.

When Garen walked over with the Black Fire Guard, his steps stopped suddenly.

An immensely powerful force was pouncing at him, full-frontal. This force was extremely powerful, until even Garen’s Nine-Headed Dragon strength paused slightly.

His expression surprised, he looked around him.

Nobody was within thirty meters of them, as though an invisible and terrible power was bordering off a certain area around the three of them.

The noble leading Garen had stopped respectfully, and stood at their right, lowering her head.

"The area ahead isn’t for us to enter, Palace Master, kindly enter yourself."

"Interesting."

Garen licked his lips. The glowing red dragon shadow flashed past his face.

Bam!

He forced his hand to step out, as though forcefully embedding his leg into the force field the three of them had gathered in.

The three dots on his brow became a darker blood-red.

Garen took two consecutive steps, as though he wasn’t under any obstruction as well, walking straight towards the three of them.

The force field around him instantly scattered, as though admitting that he was powerful enough to deserve entrance into their circle.

The four Black Fire Guards couldn’t enter, and could only wait quietly outside.

"Welcome." As the Kingdom’s strongest fighter by name, mysterious and unpredictable, Benoc began by expressing a friendly attitude towards Garen.

"Grand Duke Benoc, I have long heard of your reputation from Prynne, nice to meet you, I’m Garen, Garen Trejons." Garen pressed one hand to his chest, and bowed as a junior to a senior.

"Not bad, not bad!" Benoc laughed and nodded. "Let me introduce you. This is Cody, Grand Duke Cody." He patted the short and plump old man beside him, it seemed that the two of them were closer, which was why he was so casual with him.

"As for Veska over there, I believe you’ve met a long time ago."

"Naturally." Garen looked at Veska. The latter nodded calmly, and didn’t express anything more.

"Since everyone is here, let us begin." Benoc clapped his hands, and said a few words to the herald beside him. "Come, let’s all go in."

He was the first to walk into the theatre.

"The Second Nobility Conference, has officially begun!!"

With the herald’s loud declaration, Garen and the three of them walked into the theatre, followed by the normal high-level nobles, sixteen in total, half of them were the two Grand Duke’s relatives. The rest were some of representatives of the Kingdom’s academies, and the ministers of some important department, such as the minister of military, the minister of finance and so on. These people had some speaking rights when Avic was alive, but at a critical moment like this, since they didn’t have sufficient power, they could only be one step lower than Garen and the others in the hierarchy.

And then there were the tides and tides of middle-level nobles, these people represented the many different families of all sizes. Some of them took advantage of the chaos to conquer certain territories and benefits, and needed the conference to acknowledge them. Once they succeeded, these properties would then really belong to their families.

Some of the others were victims, who needed the conference’s power to obtain justice.

Yet others were observers, here to decide their direction and camp from here on out. The remaining ones had their own plans.

When the middle-level nobles walked in, the empty theatre filled up quickly and became a lot noisier, buzzing like so many flies in the sky.

Above the theatre, there had already been a row of chairs arranged by others. There were eight seats in total. They faced the several hundred seats below, from high up above. Guards in dark golden armor surrounded them.

But right now Garen’s attention was elsewhere.

In the four corners of the theatre’s black ceiling, there were four pitch-black bat statue gargoyles.

The four gargoyles had blood-red eyes, curled quietly in the corners, looking like normal ornamental statues, but in truth there was a hint of a strange force in the air.

Garen pulled back his gaze, and just happened to see Grand Duke Benoc smiled at him slightly.

This tall and thin old man had pale skin, a tall nose, a cross-shaped scar on his forehead, and a slightly grotesque smile.

He had evidently realized that Garen had noticed the set-up here.

He had suggested this conference, so this set-up was naturally his doing as well.

Chapter 444: Caesarton 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

While the four people, both politically and physically powerful, took their seats up there, the First Princess arrived fashionably late as well, curtsying at everyone before getting seated.

There was also a handsome copper-skinned man, wearing the signature white-silver colors of royalty, who walked up to the platform and sat together with everyone else. This was obviously the legendary Fourth Prince.

The Fourth Prince looked utterly confident, exchanging a glance with Grand Duke Cody, smiling composedly as he sat down. At the same time, he nodded politely towards the others.

Garen sat towards the left near the curtain, the next two seats beside him completely unoccupied.

He was glad for the quiet too, leaning on the chair back, lacing his fingers together with an expression as though ready to watch the drama unfold.

The seats beneath him were mostly filled in now as well. The theatre's doors fell to a gradual close.

Bam!

A circle of silver ripples spread across the large arching marbled-white doors, expanding quickly along the surrounding walls, covering all the walls inside the theatre.

In an instant, all the forces within the theatre became a single entity.

The middle-level nobles below made a slight commotion, but they quickly settled down.

"The Second Kovitan Conference! Has officially begun!!" The herald shouted loudly.

As his voice sounded, the whole theatre slowly fell quiet.

Benoc smiled slightly, tapping the long white table with his finger.

Tap-tap!

"Silence, everyone. Silence!"

Instantly, everyone inside the theatre fell completely silent, and everyone's attention focused on Benoc.

"Yesterday, our Kovitan's great ruler, His Majesty Avic, passed away due to unfortunate circumstance, and the royal bell of mourning was sounded throughout the Empire. But the dead are gone, and we the living need to consider the serious matters at hand." He spoke slowly and clearly, trying hard to make sure everyone present could understand what he meant.

"The people seated here, are all those who haven't abandoned the Empire even at the most crucial moment. Right here, representing Her Highness the First Princess, I sincerely thank all of you."

Benoc stood, and solemnly bowed slightly towards those seated below.

Whoa…!!

There was instantly thunderous applause from below.

It took several whole minutes before Benoc straightened up.

"Right here, we are gathered together, and everyone's aim, is to help the Empire through this crisis. The Three…"

Brrr!!!

The ground started vibrating all of a sudden, as though there was an earthquake, the entire theatre shaking constantly.

Benoc steadied himself, and even though he was just interrupted, his expression was one of joyful surprise.

"It's here!!"

Grand Duke Cody stood up. Turned his head up to look at the sky.

The center of the whole theatre's ceiling began to swirl and open, like a blooming flower, a huge circle hole appearing in the middle to reveal the afternoon sky outside.

The sky was golden-red.

The setting sun had dyed the white clouds outside red, and amidst the red clouds, a pillar of silver-white light, straight as an arrow, pierced into the sky.

Whoosh!!

The light pillar broke apart the clouds, leaving behind a clear straight white line, flying into the distance.

Countless clouds surrounded the traces left behind by the pillar of light, twining around it, as some of the sparkles of white light scattered down like raindrops.

"God bless the Empire!!!"(1) Benoc was the first to yell loudly.

"God bless the Empire!!" Cody shouted as well.

"God bless the Empire!!!!!" Suddenly the First Princess, the Fourth Prince, all the attending nobles, everyone all stood up, and yelled passionately.

They weren't really sure what happened, but this shot of white light was flying towards the West Farm's defense lines.

Before, the Wall of the Empire, General Georbas had led an army to resist the monsters and eventually self-destructed, temporarily slowing the attack of the sea of monsters. Plus there were many monsters, impeding their speed, which was why the Kingdom was spared from attack.

But everyone was also worried because of this, and half of the people had fled the Kingdom even before the sea of monsters arrived.

And now with this sudden pillar of white light shooting into the sky, the reactions of Benoc and the others were enough to tell everyone that this was very likely the Empire's final trump card.

Garen stood along with the crowd but didn't shout, simply lip-syncing with them.

He looked up and watched that pillar of light, even the traces of forces it had left behind could linger in the sky for so long without scattering, and it even permeated through the sky above the entire Kingdom, ending up several tens of kilometers long!

Such power had indeed far exceeded that of a single Form Four peak-level fighter.

After the crowd vented their passions for a while, Benoc finally began calming everyone down again.

"Ladies and gentlemen, our Kovitan's final shield, Lord Caeserton, has finally been truly activated. "The Ultimate Shelter Caeserton had actually merged fully with the previous emperor, Hanison, but when His Majesty Avic was on his deathbed, he used his life as the price to fully activate Caeserton's true power as an Original Heirloom. As for the situation here, I invite Her Highness the First Princess who understands it best to explain."

The First Princess stood up on cue, her expression solemn. She wore wholly white, black crepe tied onto her hand to look like a pure black rose.

"Caeserton is Kovitan's biggest secret, and was also the most integral core that Father had been studying his whole life. This Original Heirloom isn't like what others assumed, with a simple activation maneuver and huge power."

She paused and glanced beneath her, vaguely seeing some greedy gazes among them.

"Every time Caeserton is activated, it requires all of the inheritor's life force. This time, the price was Father!"

As soon as she said that, the whole audience beneath her gave a jolt.

Even Garen, sitting at the side, was shaken, he never thought that the price for using Caeserton's power would be so high! At the same time, he also understood why Benoc and the First Princess would choose to openly announce this secret.

Obviously, this was to cut off the ambitions of Obscuro and the masterminds behind them. An Heirloom that required all of the inheritor's life before it could be used, what was the point no matter how strong it was?

Besides, Caeserton had already been merged into the previous emperor of Kovitan, and it was hard to say what it had become inside. Rather than trying to get this thing, they might as well set their sights elsewhere.

"That pillar of light just now was the previous emperor hearing His Majesty Avic's plea, officially activating Caeserton's power and throwing it all at the sea of monsters near the West Farm defense line." Cody's deep voice began explaining. He evidently didn't want the First Princess to keep stealing the show.

The Fourth Prince stood up hurriedly.

"Father mentioned before that Caeserton's power is enough to cover the entire Kingdom of Kovitan, as well as the surrounding area of about five hundred meters in radius. And it can last for thirty years. Therefore, we are now completely safe!"

"May I ask, can Caeserton's power truly fight the endless army coming from the nest of monsters?" A bulky middle-aged man from below stood up and asked.

This man's forces around his body had actually reached Form Four, he was a Form Four elite fighter!

He was obviously the representative of that Little Alliance formed by the many different guilds. They didn't have any peak-level fighters like the Grand Dukes and Garen, and couldn't get much say through their status, so naturally they didn't have the right to sit at the very top. But quite a few of the middle-level nobles down there were among their ranks.

"Of course, this is for certain. Caeserton had fought against the snowstorm disaster from the North for up to ten years, this was recorded in history." The Fourth Prince replied calmly.

"They're all Original Heirlooms, so why aren't the other powers' Original Heirlooms as powerful as Kovitan's?" A child stood up, wearing a black cape, and asked like a little adult.

Sitting at the side, Garen was drinking some fruit juice to moisten his throat, but when he saw this child, he nearly sprayed out that mouthful of juice.

That child was evidently a member of his Crimson Team, Kid.

He was still the same as ever, completely wrapped up in black clothes, only revealing his black eyes, a strange air still winding around his entire person.

How did this guy get in here! Hadn't he left with the Secret Service?

Garen was speechless, he wouldn't forget that this guy could actually kill without hesitation just because Kid was friendly towards him.

After that large strawberry, he realized that strange things would always show up around Kid.

Hurriedly swallowing his juice, Garen waved at Kid.

"About that, the price to be paid is directly proportional to the rewards." The Fourth Prince was in the middle of answering Kid's question. But suddenly he saw the boy retreat into the crowd, and vanished as though he had gone invisible.

At the same time, a small head popped out from behind Garen's seat, it was Kid who had just been beneath the stage.

The crowd beneath the stage began to rumble again.

A hint of surprise flashed past the eyes of the other three strong fighters on stage, but none of them showed anything strange.

The Fourth Prince and the First Princess were also people who had seen all sorts of strange powers, so they paused for just a moment before continuing to answer questions from beneath the stage.

"Why didn't you leave?"

Garen said quietly to Kid behind him.

"You haven't left, and you still owe me money." Kid said matter-of-factly. "Of course, the main reason is that I realized that compared to the others, you are more…" Suddenly his voice went silent. As though he was a duck whose throat had gotten abruptly stuck, he went completely quiet.

Garen turned back to look at him in confusion.

He saw Kid's mouth hanging open, his black eyes like dark deep bottomless black holes, staring hard at Grand Duke Cody's direction.

Following Kid's gaze, Garen paused slightly.

Behind Grand Duke Cody's seat, just like his, there was a little girl in a red dress who wasn't even as tall as the chair.

The little girl was completely wrapped in a red cloak, revealing only a pair of blood-red eyes, dressed extremely similar to Kid.

The little white legs sticking out from under the little girl's dress looked completely bloodless, barefoot, and gave off the strange feeling as though they were swollen and about to rot.

Just like Kid, the girl was staring hard this way as well.

Suddenly, thick blood began to flow slowly down the girl's inner right thigh, flowing down her thigh to her calf, all the way down to her foot, but as it was about to touch the floor, Garen's eyes blurred suddenly.

He blinked, and realized that the blood had somehow disappeared.

Garen looked at the girl's head instead.

She suddenly pulled up her mask, revealing a fair, delicate chin and a small blood-red mouth.

Bleh!

The girl suddenly stuck her little tongue out at Garen.

It was supposed to be a mischievous and adorable action, but after she stuck out her tongue, she didn't pull it back in, instead making it longer and longer, longer and longer.

The previously pink tongue had somehow become blood-red, and kept going down, falling to her chest, stomach, groin, legs, and like a snake, began to twine and crawl up the little girl's right shoulder, poking the tip over her shoulder.

"Lu-lu-lu…"

The girl seemed to be making a cute face, but Garen didn't find it cute in the slightest. He just felt a terrifying feeling surge over to him endlessly.

Suddenly, a tiny figure in a black cloak stood in front of him. Blocking away all of that terrible air.

It was Kid!

Translator's notes:

天佑帝国, lit. Heaven bless the Empire

Chapter 445: Parliament Established 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the sky above the Kovistan Kingdom

A hemispherical silver veil of light was rapidly spreading towards its surroundings.

Like a hemispherical glass cover, it kept expanding, quickly expanding in all directions.

All the people and objects covered by the veil of light didn’t change in the slightest.

Some people looked up and stared at the sky blankly, watching as the veil of light disappeared into the distance before vanishing at the horizon.

A few black Stone-Armored Rhinos in the bushes turned their heads towards the direction where the veil of light had left.

Moo~~~

The rhinos called out in their deep voices.

A group of large white birds flying quickly in the sky were shocked by the veil of light that brushed past in an instant, and scattered.

In the distance, the veil of light went across the mountain, crossed the plains, leaped over valleys, and scaled hills.

An oval shroud of light seemed to have fallen over everything around the Kovistan Kingdom. It completely covered a large area of and around the entire Kingdom.

The shroud of light was fully silver-white, and was slightly translucent, the shadowy figure of a man’s top half with his arms held wide open appearing vaguely at the very top.

The man seemed to be hugging something, his gentle gaze looking down, as though carrying endless nostalgia. His lower half was directly connected to the shroud of light, his whole body glowing with a faint silver light, himself vaguely translucent. As though he was an unbelievably huge statue of light.

Countless people and animals raised their heads, trying to decipher the man’s shadowy face, but they couldn’t see him clearly no matter what.

The shroud of light lasted for a few minutes, and eventually disappeared totally together with the figure of the man.

Just then, the endless black sea of monsters swept over heaven and earth, all surging towards the direction of the Kingdom.

The innumerable monsters gathered together, like a black tide, rushing madly towards the Kingdom.

Roar!!!

Within the sea of monsters, a black centaur-like monster, several dozen meters tall, threw its head back and howled at the sky.

It had black curved goat’s horns on either side of its ears, the neat and dense fur on its back burning with crimson flames, as though they would never go out. The flames danced constantly, scattering bits of red sparks.

All the monsters around this goat-horned centaur moved faster than the others, their bodies considerably lighter.

There were several hundred of these goat-horned centaurs in the sea of monsters, and others kept showing up quickly behind them.

A huge grey stone statue of an angel in the sky held a huge sword in its right hand, flying towards the Kingdom. It was followed by large herds of little red monsters, the groups of red Unihorn Lizards screeching as they flew around the angel, mixed with some huge, fully white bats.

There were also some floating eyeball-like monsters. They occasionally shot out beams of black light. The beams splashed apart when they hit the floor, turning into countless dots of black light, sticking onto the monsters within several hundred meters of them, causing these monsters to keep expanding as though their bodies were being inflated with air, becoming stronger and stronger.

Bam!!

The first huge black wolf monster stepped onto the ground that was covered by the shroud of light.

In an instant, it howled in agony, its whole body rapidly burning starting from its feet, the white flames engulfing it from bottom up. In the blink of an eye, it was completely lit on fire.

The huge wolf darted out several meters away, and turned into black ash with a whoosh, disappearing completely.

Hot on its heels, countless monsters rushed into the area covered by the shroud of light.

In an instant, countless white fire torches were lit on the ground.

Bam-bam!

The huge goat-horned centaur swept aside the other monsters around it, and ran directly into the area covered by the shroud of light.

Roar!!!

Its whole body was instantly ignited with an intense milk-white flame, holding its arms out, it suddenly began howling madly, the scarlet flames on its back rapidly extending downwards, as though trying to stop the white flames.

But eerily, the red flames were directly absorbed into the white fire, and the flames grew stronger.

The goat-horned centaur was more than twenty meters tall, but it only lasted several seconds, and was directly burnt into black ash, scattering in the wind.

The endless sea of monsters kept rushing into this area of white fire, and then turned into countless black flames.

Strangely, the more monsters rushed in, the faster the white flames burned and destroyed.

A-wooo!!!!

The huge wolf had a wolf’s torso but its bottom half was that of a giant python, pale white flames burning around its body but somehow not igniting anything else around it, as though it was just an illusion.

The huge figure, more than thirty meters tall, stood like a coral outside the area of the shroud of light.

"Purified Land…" The white wolf actually spoke in a deep voice. It was the Enderian language! "To think that after all these years, I could still see Kovistan’s Wheel of Purification, Caeserton."

"It can only last thirty years, after thirty years, we can still continue to rule this earth." The other, largest stone angel statue slowly landed beside the huge wolf, and instantly trampled large masses of small monsters and dead babies. It was somehow speaking Enderian as well.

"Or maybe it won’t take thirty years…" The wolf licked its lips. "Once the President(1) wakes up, we won’t need to go to all this trouble anymore."

"Seems like you’re doing pretty well with this clone, aren’t you?" The huge stone angel statue glanced at the wolf in surprise.

This statue, the largest one, was more than sixty meters tall, twice the height of the wolf, but the two of them seem to be equal in standing, without any difference in level due to the discrepancy in height."

"Although I don’t have the brute power you do, what’s important is that I don’t spend as much either. And I can control it perfectly," the wolf replied. "Since the Wheel of Purification had finally appeared, do we still continue attacking?"

"There’s no need, although our plan only succeeded halfway, the change in the situation is already enough. What’s important is Daniela. My real body and the other two clones are there, but I’m not powerful enough, this side is a lot easier."

"Then I’ll go meet my other clone, I can’t simply lose the Distorted Beads." The wolf retreated slowly, and turned around, running back towards the direction it came.

"There are fifteen nest leaders, and three of them are Form Four nests, hehe… If this plan completely succeeds, the entire Kovistan won’t be able to fight back, unfortunately…"

The stone angel stared at the faraway Kingdom, and after standing there for a moment, it also spread its wings, flying back the way it came. Among the countless advancing monsters in the crowd, its figure was totally unassuming, and rapidly disappeared into the sea of monsters.

******************

Outside the area shrouded by light around the Kingdom, in a small and isolated valley

Beckstone opened his eyes slowly, lying in the mud with his face covered in black dust.

"Ugh…"

He propped up his body, his entire body covered in wet black mud, his long robes completely sullied into a black-grey color.

The bearded uncle was lying not far away from him, and the Eleventh Princess Tina lay beside him, the two of them cushioned by a white object that looked like a circular mushroom, protecting the two of them perfectly.

Cough cough…

Beckstone bent his head and coughed a few times, spitting out a large mouthful of foul mud. He raised his sleeve to wipe the mud away from his face, but it just made his entire face even more filthy.

He looked up to see what was above their heads, and saw that a hole, several meters wide, had been punctured through the previously dense forest canopy. The sunlight shone down through the hole, and the Black Crow King was nowhere to be seen, which meant it had probably thrown them off after a struggle, and escaped on its own.

The three of them were already grievously injured, their Totem Lights punctured through, and their core totems useless. They only had the Totem Light of their support totems in case of emergency. Before they ran, they were hit by the Nine-Headed Dragon’s poisonous gas spray, and Beckstone still felt utterly weak even now, the Solidifying Tactic he had on him, Purifying Spirit Light, had been completely countered. He could clearly feel it, the poison swirling in his chest, like a cold snake.

Touching his waist pouch, Beckstone was just planning to take out his pocket-watch to see the time. But his hand found nothing. His waist pouch had long since disappeared in their bid for escape. Who knew where it had fallen.

Actually, now that he really thought about it, he didn’t have many memories of his hatred or his surprise towards the Nine-Headed Dragon, Garen. In this period of time, after finding out a lot about Garen from Mr Emin, he had a clearer understanding of this man who had once been Acacia Trejons.

After his escape this time, he also felt that Garen wasn’t really in all that much of a hurry to kill them. It felt as though he was simply killing time, or playing with some toys. He didn’t really want to kill the three of them.

Although he didn’t know why, but add that to the previous incident, and Beckstone was slowly starting to feel his hatred towards Garen fade.

Since then, it wasn’t just with the Nine-Headed Dragon, he experienced many things in many other situations as well, and this had completely rubbed away Beckstone’s past arrogance. He understood as well, that in this world, talent wasn’t enough to take you to the top. Talent merely put your starting point slightly higher compared to others, but the of factors that truly decided how high you could go, one was the accumulation of time, and the other, persistence.

He surveyed his terrible condition.

"How pitiful." Beckstone smiled bitterly. He took off his filthy overcoat and threw it directly to the ground, but the clothes inside had mostly been soaked through by the mud as well. Not only had they turned gray-black, they were also emitting an intense odor. Some bugs he couldn’t name were crawling all over them.

After some hesitation, Beckstone raised his left hand, and twisted the black metal ring on his little finger.

The finger did not react.

Beckstone blinked, and twisted the black ring on his ring finger instead.

He waited a moment, but there was still no reaction.

Beckstone froze, his gaze falling on the yellow wooden ring on his middle finger. Neither of his communicative rings had any signal to reach others. Now all he had left was the one ring he didn’t want to use in the slightest.

The person who gave him this ring had so connections to Terraflor, but was instead a totem user with Obscuro. Each of the people these three rings could reach specialized in providing a certain service.

In exchange for a price, he could obtain temporary hiring, medical, or protection services.

It was like an elite fighter’s seal, one ring could usually equal to one commission.

And now, of the three rings he had prepared this time, two of them were useless, leaving him with the final, most dangerous one.

Translator’s note:

社长, lit. president of a/the society

Chapter 446: Parliament Established 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beckstone looked at the two people lying beside him, especially the unconscious Eleventh Princess, Tina. This adorable little girl had blood clotting on her forehead, her beautiful hair scattered and her face pale. Her lips were also turning vaguely purple, which meant she had slight poisoning.

Even though she had Beard's protection, as a normal person, it was probably inevitable that she would be slightly affected by the poisonous gas.

Seeing how bad Tina's condition was, Beckstone finally made the decision, and twisted the yellow wooden ring on his middle finger.

Brr!

The ring instantly shone with a faint yellow light.

"Oh my my, to think you actually contacted me? How surprising." A slightly piercing woman's voice came from within the ring.

"Miss Nesat… I really have no other choice." Beckstone replied with a bitter smile.

**************

Garen's expression was stormy as he pressed his hand to the armrest of his chair.

"I don't need you to protect me from evil intentions." He said calmly, "Stand aside, Kid."

"She's different from totem users." Kid slowly stepped aside, and that little girl had utterly vanished.

On the other hand, it was Grand Duke Cody who narrowed his eyes, and looked their way.

Their gazes met, and both saw something inexplicable in the other's eyes.

In unison, he and Garen broke away their gazes.

"Different? How so?"

The First Princess and the Fourth Prince were battling over who could win the support of the nobles beneath them, keeping up performances and making promises.

Meanwhile, Garen and Kid spoke quietly at his seat.

Kid returned to standing at Garen's left.

"I don't know, either." He seemed to be considering how to explain it. After a moment's silence, he finally spoke,

"Our existence is different from that of normal people. In many ways."

Garen's gaze was sharp as he glanced at Grand Duke Cody's surroundings, but he didn't catch another glimpse of that little girl.

"Interesting, my interest in that little fella just now is growing…" He was starting to get slightly excited.

"She chose that person as her Imprint."

"Imprint? What's that?"

"It's a symbiotic relationship, if we want to use our own power, we need to sign an Imprint with someone." Kid explained a lot more clearly this time. "I can only remember this much, I can't remember anything else."

"No rush, you'll know eventually." Garen smiled, calmed down his emotions, and once more brought his attention back to the conference.

Just then, there was a giant white oval mirror hanging in the air above the conference.

The mirror reflected images of the sea of monsters far, far away. Countless monsters rushed into the land surrounding the Kingdom in droves, and were all set aflame, turning into white torches of fire, rapidly scattering into countless black ashes.

Slowly, some of the stronger monsters began to retreat.

Although the nest leaders weren't particularly smart, they still knew how to instinctively avoid danger. As the nest leaders retreated, the monsters following those nests also began to leave in herds.

As the monsters kept retreating, tides upon tides of cheers washed over from the bottom of the stage.

Everyone heaved a sigh of relief.

As emotions were running too high, and could not be suppressed for now, they had no choice but to take a timeout.

Just then, on the higher seats, Veska stood up, gathered those who controlled the three armies and said something softly to them, his expression solemn.

Grand Duke Benoc stood together with the First Princess, chatting about something cheerfully.

The Fourth Prince was accepting questions from the nobles at close range.

On the other hand, Grand Duke Cody got up straight away, and walked towards Garen.

Garen got up as well.

"Your Excellency the Grand Duke, I just saw the little fella behind you. She sure is cute." He smiled, reaching out his hand.

The two of them shook hands.

Hearing Garen's words, Cody's eyes flashed with a steely light.

"I didn't think you would be a Listener's Imprint as well, after all these years, I could count the number of Imprints I've met on one hand, and here I thought no one else would know this secret."

"Oh? What secret?" Garen looked utterly mystified.

"You don't know?" Cody was slightly stunned.

"Should I know?" Garen asked back.

"Can I see the Imprint on your hand?" Cody paused, and requested.

Garen was about to reply when suddenly he felt Kid grab his right hand.

All of a sudden, there was a burning sensation on the back of his hand. This feeling only flashed by for a second, and then vanished as rapidly.

Garen looked at Kid, and saw him shake his head slightly.

"Sorry, seems like I jumped to conclusions." Cody smiled instantly, and said no more as he turned back to return to his seat, sitting down.

Only then did Garen raise his right hand and looked at it.

The back of his right hand was printed with a small red dot, like a tiny round red mole, as though someone had dotted his hand lightly with red ink.

"What is this?"

"An Imprint." Kid replied honestly, "When I heard that guy ask you just now, I accidentally Imprinted it onto your hand."

"What is this for?" Garen was speechless.

Kid looked frustrated.

"I don't know either, this is my first time giving someone an Imprint. In any case, any Imprinted people would get certain benefits, but these benefits are easily absorbed and robbed away by other Imprints, after absorbing them, the successful robber will keep getting stronger."

"You must be careful." After that, Kid added, "I think this Imprint can allow you to enter the world I can listen to."

"The world you can listen to?" Garen's heart skipped a beat. For some reason, he had inexplicably thought of the Secret Technique World he was at before he transmigrated here.

"Also, you gotta protect me." Kid hurriedly added, "That little girl just now wanted to steal my powers."

"Alright, alright, I'll protect you." Garen patted Kid's head. "Even though I still don't really know what's up here."

"I knew I was right in choosing you!" Smilingly, Kid took a plum out of pocket. The plum was strangely slightly blackened, but Kid threw the whole thing into his mouth and started chewing it loudly.

"Do you want one?" He pulled out another plum and held it in his palm.

Garen glanced at these plums, both of which were round and smooth, with thin skin and thick flesh, looking fresh and juicy.

But thinking back to that strawberry from last time, he suddenly had no appetite.

"Forget it, you eat it yourself."

Coming back to the present.

The site of the conference was slowly growing quiet.

The First Princess spoke again.

"At this conference today, as a representative of the royal family, I announce that Kovitan's National Parliament is hereby established!!"

Whoaaa!!!

There was thunderous applause.

Everybody present began clapping excitedly.

That was followed by the distribution of seats. Now that the threat had been nullified, everyone was a lot more relaxed, and the Parliamentary voting seats were divided according to status and faction. Nobody had any objections.

The four powers: The First Princess and Benoc, the Fourth Prince and Cody, Garen and Edin, the Little Alliance. The four powers were the core forces that decided the Kingdom's current situation. So they equally split eighty percent of the votes.

Garen and Edin got twenty votes, meaning each of them had ten votes, while the remaining twenty votes went to the middle- and low-level nobles, sending their representative to cast their votes.

That way, the basic structure was settled.

Although it looked very fair on the surface, but in truth, the ones who had the most advantage were Benoc and Cody, they were both Grand Dukes, and had many relatives below them, as well as hordes of noble children and nephews, who made up a substantial portion of the normal middle-level nobles. They had a large influence over those final twenty public votes.

But in any case, Garen had no intention to fight for power, he was fine as long as he himself was comfortable. Political nfluence and physical power were always connected, no matter which world it was. He just needed to raise his own abilities, and his political power would naturally grow as well.

In the end, the conference ended. Everyone was dismissed, and the conference's doors opened grandly.

Everyone stood up respectively.

Garen brought Kid and the four Black Fire Guards with him, walking towards the side door.

"Palace Master." Suddenly the First Princess' voice came from behind him.

Garen turned around, and saw the First Princess walk over to him gracefully, her low-cut black dress wrapping her slender waist tightly, emphasizing her perky chest even more. Her long slender legs showed vaguely through the slit of dress, so high it nearly split to the tops of her thighs. It gave her an air of pure, sexy temptation.

"Your Highness? Is there a problem?" Garen lowered his head in a slight bow.

"Can't I talk to you without a problem?" The First Princess looked slightly wistful. She approached Garen lightly, her body tilting forward and the tip of her nose about to touch Garen's chin. The tips of her firm breasts brushed past Garen's chest lightly.

"My words from before, still stand now…" A thin, soft voice, as soft as a mosquito's hum, reached Garen's ears.

The First Princess finished speaking, and took her servants away with her as she left with light steps.

Grand Duke Benoc smiled suggestively as he nodded at Garen, and then took his people away as well.

"Boss, don't touch that girl." Kid's voice came from behind him. "That woman's body has a problem."

"That's how she was controlling all these master fighters to serve her, it'd be weird if she didn't have a problem." Garen nodded in understanding. "Let's go, this time we've confirmed the situation in Kovitan."

The situation in the Kingdom had settled, and it would definitely cause the surrounding areas to stabilize as well, while the refugees who had escaped to the other chaotic defense lines would also slowly grow steady. But after this raid by the monsters, the crops that they had just planted had all basically gone to waste, so the issue of food would be the biggest problem at hand.

Garen suddenly thought of Beckstone and the others, he had always been using Beckstone as the standard to measure the progress of history, to see how far history had gone according to the original.

In the original history, while Obscuro rose and the royal family fell, due to the continuous warring and riots, as well as the raiding by the monsters, even though Obscuro succeeded, the civilians nevertheless descended into an abyss of despair, as food and water had to be purified before it could be eaten, now that everything had been polluted.

Many civilians starved to death, since they couldn't afford to eat the food that had become so expensive.

That was when Terraflor's largest advantage finally took centerstage.

They had powerful control over plants, allowing them to own incomparably cheap crops and food, hastening the growth of paddy as well as other fruits and vegetables to win the support of the majority.

"I wonder if Ivycius' men have found Beckstone and the others." In the original history, Beckstone and the others had successfully escaped the palace, but they weren't so badly injured, instead they had encountered that poison witch from the Secret Service, and were heavily poisoned by her.

He didn't know whether they would still encounter that Black Nesat this time.

"Is there still anyone in headquarters?" Garen asked.

"Very few, not many left." Kid answered honestly.

"Let's go see." If he could meet the Black Nesat, he might as well settle their grudges from before.

Chapter 447: Stable 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Several days later

Black Fire Palace back garden

Bam!

Garen thrust out his first and pulled it back slowly, as though pulling something from mid-air, countless white mists appeared in the air, like white ropes, and madly gathered in his hand.

Like a huge white web.

Garen wore loose white clothes, closing his eyes to concentrate, and then he swung out his left hand as a fist again.

Bam!!

There was another dull sound in the air.

"Do you need me for something?" Ivycius was slowly walking out from the corridor on the right of the garden. Looking at Garen, doing his morning exercises in the garden.

"How’s the situation on Beckstone’s side?" Garen asked with his eyes closed, never stopping his movements for a moment.

Turning around, thrusting his fist, reaching out his palm, as the white mist around him roiled around, giving off a foggy, blurry feeling.

The flowers and plants in the garden, and the surrounding varde flowers kept waving in the mist, whooshing as they went. The pebbles and dried leaves on the ground also formed whirlwinds of different sizes, constantly spinning.

Ivycius watched Garen train casually. He replied,

"My men have searched the whole area around their landing spot, we could only find the marks of their landing, they probably ran away. After all, Form Four fighters would have a few survival methods no matter what."

"Then forget it, there’s no rush for now, when the time comes they will naturally appear, how about the Wells Castle?" Garen spread open his fingers and grabbed lightly, five little snakes made of white clouds appearing instantly and then disappearing as rapidly.

"The people from the Secret Service have all left. We didn’t find that Black Nesat you were talking about." Ivycius replied calmly. "What do you plan to do now? Just staying here and training?"

Garen gradually pulled back his stance and stood on the spot. Ever since his fight with Ivycius, he had obtained a brand new and deeper understanding of the secret techniques he had learned before.

"The situation has just only stabilized here, if we want to take root here, we have no choice but to stay temporarily and steady our forces here."

"It’s not that easy to steady our forces, since we’re the ones controlling the palaces. As Palace masters, we had always been sponsored by the royal family, paid from the country’s coffers, but now that Avic is dead, our main source of income has been cut off as well."

"Other than the royal family’s sponsorship, what other sources of income did we have back then?" Garen accepted some faintly salty water from a Black Fire Guard at the side, and gargled lightly, then he used a warm and damp towel to wipe the sweat from his body.

"There are also the offerings and teaching fees from our disciples." Ivycius said mildly.

"Then we’ll start from there." Garen smiled slightly. He was preparing to introduce the things he learned from the Secret Technique World to this world. Naturally, he couldn’t simply reveal his secret techniques, these were a form of martial arts that required a background in the culture, and wasn’t something one genius could invent by himself. Anybody with a good eye could be able to discover the completely different culture embedded in them.

But while the secret techniques couldn’t be taught, basic martial arts and fighting techniques would be fine.

Some totem users liked close combat as well, and although there were Master-level fighters among the normal people, their martial arts had never been appreciated by others. And they were an utter mess, with not a single unified system.

"Thankfully I have the Green Vine Sphere here, so other than the Black Fire Guards ability, I can also bestow Totem Light on regular armor. This will infinitely reduce the distance between normal people and regular totem users. Wouldn’t this prove to be the best basics?"

"Aren’t you afraid of raising a future threat? Since your father could create the Green Vine Sphere, surely someone would be able to neutralize it."

"That was why Avic was too scared to use this on a larger scale, right?" Garen said calmly, "If I don’t even have that much generosity, what right do I have to pursue the legendary Strongest Way?"

"The Strongest Way?" That was the first time Ivycius heard Garen mention his dreams.

"That’s right. I used to contemplate often, how the universe has limitless colors, limitless miracles, limitless mysteries, limitless horizons. Since I was already born into this world, if I don’t see and experience everything I find interesting, then wouldn’t I have come to this world only to waste my life?"

Garen had recently started fusing his fist fighting secret techniques, and in his silence, he had an enormous aura like the peaceful sea.

Every day, he would use his own body to channel the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, his unimaginably powerful Nine-Headed Dragon’s body had its blood qi rise and fall like the tide in the process of training with his secret techniques. It was enormous. It reflected back to nourish Garen’s spirit, until his spirit reached an indescribable level. He was also growing closer to the legendary Form Five.

Every time he channeled his blood qi and made it boil, Garen could feel the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon’s body slowly merging with his own. The huge totem power kept slowly nourishing and modifying his body.

If the other Form Five totem users could only start training their secret techniques after they achieved the highest form of merging, then Garen was approaching the peak of this step by using his level as the strongest secret technique practitioner, the King of the Century.

He just had to achieve Form Five, and then he could instantly reach the very peak of the Form Fives.

This was the base he had forged himself from the previous world. It was a spiritual level and height.

This was the powerful will that came from countless battles of life and death.

In the Secret Technique World, although Garen had his special power to help him, he still experienced many life-and-death battles. And as he continuously crossed swords with many peak-level masters of the ancient martial arts, he had successfully walked out of his failures and fears, the martial arts of his spirit having achieved an extremely high level.

The more he feared something, the more this will of his made him excited.

Because he could feel terror, that meant he had seen a taller mountain for him to scale.

Ivycius was the person closest to him, and the one who had the best view of the changes Garen had been undergoing recently. He also knew the method to train for Form Five, but usually Form Five required a period of adaptation after the user merged with the totem.

This was because a person’s will couldn’t control the totem’s massive power. This adaptation period was a time to get used to it. Usually, this would require years. The stronger the totem, the more years needed to get used to it and adapt.

Only after experiencing this adaptation period, could someone truly be considered a Form Five elite fighter. Even the Form Five fighter that spent the shortest amount of time in this adaptation period used a full twenty years. The longer ones could take up to a century.

This was also the main reason most Form Five users didn’t usually walk the grid, they were too busy adapting, so they sent their clones out, and let their wills continuously adapt to the totem.

Even for those powerful fighters who had experienced the adaptation period, if they wanted to use their totem bodies to learn the secret techniques that had been discovered in the ruins, that would also be an extremely long process. A decade or two would pass like nothing. Each time they tried to train, during the time it took for them to close and open their eyes again, even their grandchildren’s grandchildren might have been born.

And they could only start from the beginning after achieving Form Five, by channeling their immense blood qi through their bodies, which made it far harder than using just a normal person’s body.

This was Garen’s biggest advantage, in that he could easily learn this sort of secret technique.

"Is your dream to pursue the position of the strongest?" Ivycius looked at Garen, as though affected by this atmosphere, his experience growing slightly solemn as well.

"Rather than pursuing the position of the strongest, it’s more like I want to overcome life and death." Garen replied calmly, "I’m just a normal person myself, it’s just that my desire to avoid death is too strong." It was as though he had instantly returned to that pure state of mind he had in the Secret Technique World.

"Once you reach the strongest, nothing will be a threat to you?" Ivycius was slightly surprised.

"Perhaps." Garen didn’t reply, it was a question even he didn’t really know the answer to.

"We better return to the previous problem, since we have no source of income, and we also need to build a strong influence. Then let’s open the palace doors."

"Open the palace doors? You intend to?" Ivycius had thought that Garen had only wanted to expand a little, but to think he actually…

"That’s right, I plan to truly open the palace doors, and recruit disciples on a large scale!" Garen said deeply.

He didn’t want to teach the Secret Technique World’s secret techniques, that was his biggest secret, no matter how much of a genius he was, it wasn’t something he could create by himself in such a short frame of time. What he truly wanted to teach was a series of understanding he had come to after coming to this world and using the Totem Light to fight.

With Garen’s level now, without using any of the Secret Technique World’s secret technique basics, it was still possible for him to invent some rough and simple blood qi channeling methods without revealing anything.

Although it wouldn’t reach the level of secret techniques, but mixed with the martial arts and fighting techniques of this world’s masters, he could naturally still form a school of his own.

During these days, the stuff he had been training every day were the simple exercises he was planning to teach. At the most, these exercises could only train the human body to infinitely approach the level of a Grandmaster of Combat, but it could never break the limits of this world. So it couldn’t be called a secret technique.

The so-called secret technique was something that could theoretically approach the level of a Grandmaster of Combat, a secretive form of martial arts that could approach the limits of the human body.

Garen’s aim now was only to build his own power and influence, so naturally he didn’t have to go so far.

This rough and shoddy exercise, added with some various other useless steps and methods that he himself couldn’t remember, plus some messy, meaningless spirit training methods. He hid the truest, simplest technique into the countless intercepting signals.

This guaranteed that Black Sky from Obscuro, and the ancient antiques of Terraflor, would definitely be unable to decipher its secrets.

Seeing Ivycius’ somewhat surprised expression, Garen continued.

"I invented a form of fighting exercise, upon surveying all of the normal people’s fighting techniques from this world, I noticed that most of them began from the outside moving in, and there are even some Master-level fighters who achieved the peak of their techniques. Unfortunately they worked for most of their lives, and still can’t defeat even a normal Form One totem user. In the world of normal people, this sort of elite martial arts fighter would naturally grow weaker in influence. But everything will change with this Green Vine Sphere technique of mine."

He smiled slightly.

"I plan to use the Green Vine Sphere as the basic, and use the normal people as the base, to create a force that belongs to us completely."

"As long as you don’t find it troublesome." Ivycius gave Garen a long look. Then he turned around and left.

Garen stood alone in the garden.

"Won’t it be fine as long as I give all the troublesome bits to the people most suited to handling it?"

He reached out with one hand and grabbed with his five fingers, so the countless white wisps appeared instantly, surrounding and dancing around his arm like many little snakes.

These simple exercises used his Ten Thousand Mammoths technique as a base, and was an adaptation of his Northern Capturing Hand. He used his own body to vibrate rapidly, the blood qi inside turning and rippling, absorbing the countless water vapor around him to form rapidly vibrating micro water droplets that could permeate into the enemy’s body and wreak havoc.

After Garen simplified it, this simple set of exercises created from this move could also control water vapor to permeate and destroy the enemy’s insides, while at the same time he could also use Totem Light to sense the movements of any possible threats around. Once it was given the quality of Totem Light, this move’s ability to kill and destroy tracelessly would be unstoppable! If enough water vapor was gathered, the ripple of water vapor summoned would be bigger and bigger, stacking up to an extremely powerful vibrating force with countless water vapor. Even if its ability to break defenses was slightly weaker, it was still a peak-level ability to cause large-scale destruction.

In terms of power, once it was trained to the peak, it could at least reach the Form Four level.

Chapter 448: Stable 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Of course, this happened when the Green Vine Sphere was given Totem Light characteristics.

However, these exercises had to be created, and although they were minor exercises in the Secret Technique world and therefore were very rough, once they were integrated with Totem Light, they could then be considered as rare and powerful resolutions.

However, exercises were merely exercises, and of all the people who had practiced Secret Techniques like the Southern Holy Fist Gate, Neptune Fist, Red Sand Sword, Star Ring Door and many others, how many of them had actually reached the absolute cutting edge like Garen or Cayduran?

Appraisal, perseverance,will, luck. They were all elements that one could not lack on the path to the top.

Thus, though these exercises were created, a worthy disciple would still be needed to inherit them.

The techniques of the Green Vine Sphere would be discovered sooner or later. It was a matter of time. However, the imprints left by these exercises would never disappear.

A great martial art with this as its foundation would need to be established, to allow the disciples to possess a sense of belonging, so that everyone would automatically allow themselves to be part of the group.

Of course, preparations on the Green Vine Sphere were needed as well. Then, they would truly be able to achieve an incomparable synergy, and regardless of whether or not the Green Vine Sphere techniques would be discovered elsewhere, the effects on them would be negligible..

Garen narrowed his eyes and left the flower garden. After washing himself, he wore his clothes neatly, before walking straight out of the Black Fire Palace, towards the palace book collection hall.

Currently, he and Ivycius were the only ones living in the palace due to the sheer destruction that swept the area. The princess and the royal family had moved into the other palaces on the opposite side of the abyss to seek refuge.

The whole KIngdom was separated into three hilltop territories. The center of which was near to a large canyon where large clouds rolled by, and each side was connected by a stone bridge,

The Palace District and the Cloud Light District were conjoined on top of the largest and tallest cluster of hills. Looking from afar, the black palace had undulating layers, towering minarets, and high, scale-like walls.

The other two hilltops were slightly smaller, and were both Trading Districts. One of the hilltops had been built with a palace.

Along the way, Garen saw many of Ivycius’s subordinates supervising the tasks being carried out to clean up the debris in the damaged palace.

When they saw him, they all bowed with their faces in awe and their heads lowered.

He reached the book collection hall, where there was only a single Black Fire Guard guarding the doorway.

Walking into the palace, on both sides of the dark golden hall were countless, tightly-packed copper-coloured bookshelves.

The interior of the palace was almost completely empty; there were less than ten people who were standing in front of the bookshelves with books in their hands.

In the book collection hall, as long as the aristocrats paid a reading fee, they were allowed to come in to research information and learn about subjects that they wished to have a deeper understanding of. Of course, the books were separated by level, and books of different levels would require different fees. Moreover, they were not allowed to be borrowed out to be read outside the library.

Garen walked in quietly, without attracting anyone’s attention. He glanced at the bronze notice sign at the doorway which acted as a directory to the different contents of each area’s bookshelves.

Garen, who had already visited this place yesterday, immediately walked towards the area that he was looking for. He stepped past a few bookshelves, before taking out a black copper key and opening a small door on the wall, then walking inside.

There were two large bookshelves filled with books inside. This was different from the outside, because the books on these shelves all had black covers, while the front of the bookshelves were engraved with secret characters.

These were the records of the research findings by the scholars and researchers after many years, under the command of Avic. There were research notes, and also some precious documents that were nearly out of print, including some of the best academic books.

For most people, even if they were Form 2 or Form 3 Totem Users, if they stood in his position, they could not even dream of understanding the important information there. Perhaps the Forgers and Luminarists who were proficient in research would be able to understand, but even ten years of painstaking studying were not equivalent to reading these Bible-like books.

But Garen was different.

Although Attribute Points were unable upgrade Secret Techniques, learning new knowledge could still prove to be extremely useful nonetheless.

Garen’s foundation was already very good, firstly because of Edin’s teachings and books, later Reylan, then Windling, and Vanderman’s underground book collection and research journals. After his exchanges and the nurturing he received from these talents with excellent techniques, it added to his terrifyingly powerful photographic memory.

Here, the advantages of his ten full intelligence points would finally come to fruition.

These attributes allowed his logical thinking to become more cautious and efficient. His memory and rationality had become stronger as well. In other words, it made his brain more advanced, enabling the potential of his brain to reach frightening heights.

But to Garen, these things were only useful when he was studying and acquiring knowledge here.

It was as if someone was handed a pistol but never fired a round, which, in the end, would result in the the pistol being completely useless. Even with an advanced brain, Garen himself did not like using schemes to solve his problems and troubles. He had always used his raw strength to crush his opponents.

If he could not beat them, he would just flee, and once he had returned and strengthened himself, he would go back and fight again! He would fight until the end!

This habit of his made planning completely unnecessary.

Therefore, even if his brain became any stronger he still refused to use it. Naturally, none of its uses would become apparent.

Garen had always treated everything in front of him as opportunities that he could use improve himself and move forward, transforming them into forces that would make him stronger. This allowed him to constantly increase his strength and deviate more from normalcy one step at a time.

A force that was strong enough to increase the pace at which strength was gained. This increase in speed would, eventually, reach a terrifying stage.

However.

While most people were still coming up with schemes to beat their strong villains, Garen had already unconsciously surpassed his enemies, and had become stronger than his opponents.

He had already become the King of the Century, and while he promoted his abilities to reach far, another reason was this.

This was one of the threads connecting all the different worlds together.

Even a genius with an agile mind would not necessarily possess the persevering characteristics that ensured a life of success.

There was only one factor, which was to remove distractions, and to find the right direction and the courage to go forward. That was the key element to achieve success.

Geniuses always had agile minds, and a lot of problems were not serious to them. Many troubles were also minor issues when placed in their hands.

This way, the chances for them to encounter difficult obstacles were far and few in between. The desire to become stronger was insufficient. If a motivating force was insufficient, they would naturally take a back seat. Resulting in them stagnating.

This was similar to the reasoning behind the hare and the tortoise, except that in real life, the tortoise was never as slow as most people assumed, and neither was the hare as fast as they had expected.

Many times, the act of surpassing others isn’t as difficult as they thought it would be.

Thus, Garen’s method of thought paid attention to ensuring that he would never end up like the devilishly smart geniuses that chose battle strategies that involved scheming their way to victory. Although conspiring was still a type of strength to be had, it was not the path that he wanted to pursue.

A large chunk of biochemical research and Totem research knowledge had been stuffed into Garen’s brain.

He stood in front of the bookshelves while the faint yellow sunlight reflected off the crown of his head, and continuously flipped through books and read them.

The ceiling of the book collection hall was not thick, and was made with a layer of polished yellow crystal stones. When the sunlight touched it, went through a refraction process, allowing some light to pass through while not harming the books. Instead, it expelled the moisture within the book collection hall.

Garen hurriedly flipped through the informative notes inside the records. It passed through his own experiences and experimental statistics in his mind, and kept correcting some of the mistakes, while some of the unclear and blurry parts where temporarily marked out. Waiting for future experimental verification.

A large chunk of the knowledge and statistics in his mind were continuously intersected, perfected, and deepened.

Garen was indeed a professional in this field, who had once given himself core organ transplant surgery. He had modified a part of his body, experienced and practiced Secret Techniques for many years, absorbed so much of Obscuro Society’s knowledge, plus deepened his knowledge through the notes in the palace. There was probably no one in this world who could possibly be stronger than himself.

Obscuro Society specialized in Creature Totem modifications. Terraflor Society specialized in plant cultivation research.

Meanwhile, the Royal Alliance of Luminarists had an assortment of things, and had all kinds of information which was all sophisticated, but none of them were the deepest in the world.

Garen was most concerned about human body modification techniques. He was the successful result of a human body modification that was alive and well too. Although many death row prisoners were sacrificed in exchange for this, it could not be denied that through this path, Garen had successfully lifted the restrictions of a Luminarist whose Appraisal value was insufficient.

If only another person was able to obtain King of the Century’s precise control and Secret Technique realm, plus this technique, and had a Silver Totem that was able to adapt to organ transplants. If they were able to control rejection reactions and after effects, perhaps they would achieve Garen’s current state as well.

Other than human body modifications, Garen had seen many other things, such as research reports and records that involved the Green Vine Sphere’s techniques.

The research regarding the Green Vine Sphere was kept in Vanderman’s underground library, and Garen had already understood it deeply, and was now combining it with the royal research notes and knowledge systems.

He had gotten a better grasp of it, and after he had mastered it thoroughly, he was one step closer to perfecting the Green Vine Sphere.

Once he had actually come into contact with the Green Vine Sphere’s core techniques, Garen finally understood the importance of the coincidence that allowed Vanderman to forge this plaything.

There was a very low possibility there was another thing like the Green Vine Sphere in the entire world.

Because its main body was made of an endangered plant that was likely to have been destroyed more than ten years ago.

After Vanderman had moved back home with this plant, there were issues with its climate and temperature, and there was no way to stop it from constantly wilting to death.

He never expected that during one coincidence, when an accident occurred while Vanderman was practicing his Totem Tactics, would ultimately affect this plant.

Most of the plant died, but one stem of it barely survived. This was the original part of the Green Vine Sphere.

As he had never expected that even Totem Light would be unable to destroy this plant stem, Vanderman began his lengthy research journey. He search the four corners many times in between, in an attempt to find more of these plants, but unfortunately, this plant had soon died out completely, because it was unable to adapt to the ever-changing climate environment.

Thus, Garen was not worried that someone would be able to discover the secret of the Green Vine Sphere in such a short span of time. Most of the highest royal scholars were only able to touch the shallowest surface layer as well. Unlike himself, who had Vanderman’s research notes.

His visit to the book collection hall this time, was mainly to find a way to combine the techniques of the Resonance Stone and Green Vine Sphere, to form more complete and complicated Green Vine Sphere abilities. If it was possible, he hoped that he could break out of his current bottleneck situation.

Other than that, he was also hoping to see the other Core Totems of the other Totem Users that were stronger than the Nine-Headed Dragon, to find out how they actually obtained them.

Although his Nine-Headed Demon Dragon was not an actual ancient complete body, its powers were not to be dismissed. It was actually ranked around number one hundred on the list of Totems.

This made Garen wonder about the remaining Ultimate Totem Users, and how they came about. He also wanted to know how it was possible that their Totems were stronger than his own Nine-Headed Dragon!

Chapter 449: Seed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He gingerly took a large book with a black cover down from the end of the bookshelf.

He had read almost all of the books that contained research notes. This book was a complete glossary of rare Aberration Totems, and was similar to the atlas that Edin had given him earlier.

That book was kept in the underground library inside Blue Bay manor.

He opened the book cover, skipped past the foreword and preface, and went straight to the table of contents.

Suddenly, rows of faint words appeared in front of Garen’s eyes. Much like a tree, the entire table of contents were divided into many little branches.

‘Aberration Totem ---- Idealized Totem ---- Coincidence Totem ---- Sacrificial Totem ---- Ancestral Totem’

Below the four main groups were countless thin branches that listed out the various types.

Naturally, the books that were stored here were not those that had regular research contents, instead, they contained deeper research that could not be found outside.

Garen read the bottom part attentively.

Soon, he found a tiny branch of words at the Ancestral Totem pane.

‘Swamp Nine-Headed Snake ---- 8882’

The words at the back were the page numbers.

Above the Nine-Headed Snake was the Moth Wing Giant Lizard, while the Rainbow Bird was below it. These two animals were species that only existed during ancient eras.

He flipped to the Nine-Headed Snake’s page number immediately. The records on top appeared before Garen’s eyes instantly.

‘Swamp Nine-Headed Snake ---- The ultimate overlord of the swamp areas during the ancient times; great life force, uses strong sound waves to attack airborne creatures, and takes on the Dragon Demon’s life after confusing it. Entrenched in the deepest part of the swamp, it releases endless amounts of poisonous gas. It is the main producer of poisonous fumes in places with toxic swamp types…’

Garen read carefully, but realised that the above records were mostly things that he already understood. He felt that they were only added recently, and was perhaps information that was only discovered by researching his Totems.

Wordlessly, he remembered Ivycius’ plant series Flowering Plant Totems. After looking through the book for a while, he quickly found the White Rose Totem.

‘White Rose Totem: Plant series Totem, exists in theory. Flowering Plant Totems have strict cultivation requirements, requires the blood of immediate family members as raw materials, and needs sustenance from a part of one’s close relative’s Totem Power. Before it achieves Spiritualization, its power is weak, but after Spiritualization, its power will increase explosively. According to rumors, once Flowering Plant Totems are successfully cultivated, it can hastily sustain the spirits of its relatives. This has not been proven to be real or not.’ Behind were different kinds of variations, and the White Rose Totem was divided into different types, and each type had a general introduction. Their abilities were also abundant and strange, but most of them were either poisonous or illusion types.

Garen began to find Veska’s ocean whirlpool type Totem.

But it was slightly harder to find it this time. The Totem images that resembled large whirlpools, included four different types of Totems.

Siren Totem: An Aberration Creature that was theoretically cultivated, it was the result of a small family’s accidental experiment, and when this Siren Totem was born, it used its singing voice to destroy the whole family, before mysteriously disappearing.

Beluga Whale Totem: The overlord of the ocean, the Beluga Whale, can stir up huge whirlpools to hide itself.

Elemental Totem Ocean: Pure Ocean Totems, that were theoretically formed by the successful evolution of Elemental Totem water spirits. Possesses exceptional attack control even in large ranges. Its units of power are not very strong, but its wave range is the largest among all the other types. Its master, Minister Veska can even attack creatures within distances of a few thousand meters. It is one of the strongest war Totems.

Although the news about Veska’s Totem experiments were recorded above, the ability section that Garen was most concerned about was just a blank space.

The same Elemental Totems also included Earth Elementals, a creature that was purely made up with soil, also known as a humanoid that could control terrain changes.

Ghost Wind, a strange formless Totem, had very little information, but was immune against any type of movement based attacks, and could only be harmed by abilities with static natures.

Lava Rock Men, high-temperature humanoids made of lava, abilities still unknown.

Garen scanned past these entries, and noticed some Item Totems above.

Weapon Totems, much like God Cloud’s chains, and Green Dragon Swordsman’s sword light.

Armor Totems, like the Triangular Shields of the wall generals who had just sacrificed themselves for the Kingdom.

There were also Sacrificial Totems that, through certain secretive measures that led to countless successful cultivations when put together, used these measures to allow it to swallow itself, before finally obtaining an ultimate Totem King, before then using these sacrificial means to borrow the Totem King’s power.

The most successful Totem King system, belonged to Daniela.

Daniela’s strongest Totems, were not the King of Daniela’s Core Totems, but rather a Cthulhu Totem that had been successfully evolved by the Totem King.

It had swallowed the ninety-nine Totem Kings that were cultivated in the world, and achieved Cthulhu status, only allowing families of specific bloodlines to borrow its strength.

Cthulhu Totems possessed unimaginable strength, and no one knew their true power. No one knew how many levels they had evolved.

Daniela’s possession of the Cthulhu was their strongest form of protection. It was like Kovitan’s extremely powerful Caeserton Ultimate Protection. Ender had ancient mystical Giant Stone Sculpture battle groups. The three large kingdoms each had their own trump cards, and this was the result of the three main Emperor’s painstaking efforts.

When Elemental Totems were first successfully called Core Totems, they allowed Totem Users to quickly leap towards Spiritualized status, however, the starting point was extremely high, and evolution was also extremely difficult.

This book recorded many cases, and all of them were examples of Elemental Totems that could not evolve successfully.

It was different from the information outside that depicted the Elemental Totems as legendary items, as this place clearly pointed out the existence of these Elemental Totems. Obscuro Society was one of the representations of success.

Once Garen had finished reading this book on that introduced Totems, more than two hours had passed already.

His Totem knowledge had also become much deeper from when he first started.

The Nine-Headed Dragon was actually not as amazing as the other extremely strong Totems.

Moreover, the entire Aberration Totem series was unlike other Totem series.

Other than Elemental Totems, he could easily find a Totem that was stronger than the Nine-Headed Dragon. The Storm Elemental Totem for example, was a terrifyingly powerful black storm, and this was only its primary body, because after its first evolution, it would become a Hurricane Totem. Two people in history had obtained this Totem, and they were known as Hurricane Kings.

Each of them could single-handedly dominate a war. When regular Totem Users stood before them, all who came to fight would end up dead.

‘Mass war tactics were ineffective’

These comments were a bloody lesson that arrived in exchange for the life of an ancient kingdom.

There was also the Hill King Totem, an Elemental Totem made up of large rocks, which evolved and was known as the Mountain King, and once the entire Totem fused with the Totem User, it would transform into a large endless mountain that spanned over ten thousand kilometers, swallowing the three thousand elite Form 3 Totem Users that once invaded its homeland, destroying their Tactical Thunderstorm Formation at the same time.

These peak Totem records flashed past Garen’s eyes continuously. He was initially unconvinced, but seeing these Totems that were more frightening than myths, he knew that his own strength could not compare to these deviants. To be able to rank within a hundred of them already meant that he was strong enough.

However, although these Totem Users were extremely powerful, they all shared one characteristic.

Their short life spans.

Using these powers that could be considered the pinnacle of strength, in other words, made them grow old and reach their deaths quicker.

No one found the reason yet, but the most popular assumption was that they used strong powers that greatly surpassed themselves, but did not have an equally strong spirit to control them. In the end, they were affected by these powers and were ultimately assimilated.

Excluding Elemental Totems, there were still Daniela’s Nineteen Cthulhus, and besides the strongest Cthulhu King, the other eighteen Cthulhu Totems were distributed in different areas, each occupying their own territories and providing protection for the local Totem Users, and accepting their sacrifices.

Thus, Daniela was unlike the other kingdoms, as they were a religious country.

In actuality, Daniela had two rulers, one was the King of Daniela, while the other was the Cthulhu King.

The Royal Alliance and the Cthulhu Church both dreaded each other, creating a sense of balance. The Kings of Daniela of previous generations died inexplicably, and discerning people could see that it was highly probable that the Cthulhu King had caused it. Only the Emperor of this generation sat soundly on the throne, governing well, and strengthening the system.

Among the three Kingdoms, Daniela’s losses were probably the smallest.

The Cthulhu Church took the opportunity to save ten thousand people during the Great Chaos, thus receiving the trust and worship of countless people. The consequent result was that the Cthulhu King’s strength increased day by day, and his powers expanded as well.

Garen could finally see a clearer picture of the entire current situation through this secret information.

If Obscuro Society wanted to overturn Daniela, they were most likely to join forces with the Cthulhuism Society, as Obscuro Society’s ideals were of the survival of the fittest, coinciding with the ideals of the Cthulhuism Society. Except that the Cthulhuism Society’s aim was for the weak to become the food source for the strong, to provide everything for the strong, and to satisfy their every need. If one did not wish to be considered weak, they would need to strengthen their body quickly, and the fastest method was to sign a sacrificial contract with the Cthulhu. As long as it was suitable, within a night, a regular Totem User could make the leap into a strong, ultimate Form 2 Totem User.

They would receive the Cthulhu’s son as their Totem, and when the number of sacrifices increased, the Cthulhu’s son’s upgrade speed would increase as well.

If the sacrifices were strong enough, it was also possible for the Cthulhu itself to become one’s Totem.

Among Sacrificial Totems, Cthulhu levels were higher than Elemental Totem levels, and Cthulhu’s was at least Form 4, and became the backbone of Daniela’s strength. The eighteen Cthulhus and Daniela’s other Cthulhu that had once appeared in history; when these different types of Cthulhu Totems were added together, the number of Totems that were stronger than the Nine-Headed Dragon would naturally increase. Getting pushed to a ranking of one hundred was expected.

But fortunately, Garen understood that Kovitan’s Ultimate Shelter Caeserton actually had another name, and was called the Wheel of Purification. It happened to clash with the attributes of Daniela’s Cthulhu.

Since the Cthulhuism Society’s strength attributes had been restrained by Caeserton, naturally the alliance between Daniela’s King and Kovitan would be very close, and that was expected as well.

In reality, only very few people knew about this secret.

The average person, and perhaps the majority of Daniela’s Totem Users, did not know that they were worshippers of the Cthulhuism Society, and one of the Cthulhus that they worshipped actually originated from a Totem.

However, there was also a possibility that Kovitan was looking at the problem from a different angle. They were like the scientists on earth. Any problems that they faced would always require a scientific explanation.

Many things probably just needed a change of perspective.

Many consecutive days were spent at the book collection hall and Black Fire Palace, and every day Garen would forget to eat while burying himself in his research. The presence of his Attribute Points allowed him to forget this tiring process completely.

He quickly entered the practical experiment stage.

The Green Vine Sphere began to undergo encryption measures.

The principle of the Green Vine Sphere used parasites in reality, and would implant tiny spores into non-living things. These spores would progressively change the structure of these non-living things, and would release a special active substance known as Zibane at the same time. They already possessed strong contagious natures and viability, and their size was also smaller compared to other types of bacteria. They could almost be compared to viruses.

The strangest thing about these substances was that once they were mixed with specialized techniques, they could be arranged into a sphere-like structure, like countless wireless receivers that could accept certain types of nerve signals and neurotransmitters. They would follow the commands of the nerve signals to infect and infiltrate.

In simpler terms, the Green Vine Sphere could make objects into Totems that would still be under the command of their masters.

People who wore equipment that was made into Totems by the Green Vine Sphere, would actually need to be connected to the equipment through their flesh. The energy that they used looked like Totem Light, but was actually a type of energy that was closer to the active substances of the Totem Light’s Polluting Power. This strength was named Zibane Power by Vanderman.

Thus, they were able to turn their surrounding substances into Totems within a designated span of time, except that this Totem-inducing time was very short. However, the time needed for the Zibane Power to infect others required a high level of spirit control, and without spirit control, this strength would not be able to infect others automatically.

However, Garen was satisfied despite this.

The Green Vine Sphere gave regular people a chance to become strong.

As long as your spirit and physical body were strong enough, even if you did not have Totem User Appraisal, as long as you had a Green Vine Sphere, you would be able to reach a powerful level.

This was a brand new strength system, just like Totem Power!

No wonder Obscuro Society, Royal Alliance, and Terraflor Society all wanted to seize this technology.

Within the Green Vine Sphere’s system, one’s spirit would decide the Zibane Power’s level and strength, and after offsetting the nature of the gap, the physical body’s strength would determine the gap between each other.

Garen arranged everything carefully and came to a conclusion.

"In other words, after obtaining the Green Vine Sphere’s Zibane Power, spirit will would largely decide the class, like Form 1, 2, and 3 of Totems.

Meanwhile, the physical body would decide the strength difference between classes."

While he encrypted the Green Vine Sphere, Garen also allowed it to implant itself completely into his right shoulder.

However, this technology could not be directly announced, because it would be a large impact against the entire Totem User system. Zibane Power’s activation also needed certain requirements from his will and spirit strength. It required extremely high spirit levels to be activated.

But this final research was impactful towards the Totem User system, as Totem systems were the foundation of the aristocracy’s control over the world, and if it was discovered, it would surely become the target of public criticism.

Chapter 450: Seed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ding.

Garen placed the forceps back into the glass bottle gently.

He looked at the oval-shaped silver pauldron in front of him, and exhaled slightly.

He picked up a piece of white cloth from the side and gently wiped some stains off the surface of the pauldron.

"There are some defects apparently…" He furrowed his eyebrows and murmured softly. "The roots of the Green Vine Sphere can only support fifty-three divisions of Zibane Power. It can only forge fifty-three sets of weapons or armor to be made into Totems. No wonder… No wonder there were only two hundred Black Fire Guards. This was also the best result that could be obtained when Avic integrated his cutting-edge technology carefully. Nearly four times of increment would be enough to frighten most people."

"Two hundred Black Fire Guards, giving up their control would mean obtaining two hundred sets of Black Fire armor. It would grant normal people Totem Power traits. This was the foundation, and geniuses with strong wills and strong bodies would be able to truly activate the Black Fire Armor."

Garen picked up the pauldron in front of him, and illuminated the surface carefully, as many faint silver dots began to light up on it, showing the characteristics of Zibane Power after its activation.

"Zibane Power requires strong to reach activation; the stronger the will, the greater the power that can be controlled, allowing Zibane’s activation to become stronger, thus strengthening its infectiousness as well. This beneficial cycle made it like a seed, the more substances it absorbed from the outside, the stronger its main body and armor would become."

He put the pauldron down.

"Avic gave up on this potential, and used the absolute loyalty of the corpse-like Black Fire Guards instead. But this kind of power was ultimately too small." Garen shook his head. "If those with weak wills received the armor, they would be swallowed by the Zibane Power in the end, turning into the living dead. They would lose their whole personality. This thing seems to be extremely dangerous."

He began to think about ways to solve this danger, and after some thinking, he thought of more than ten plans, but still had no clue. Vanderman had researched this level for many years, but had yet to find a conclusion. The people in the Royal Alliance had no conclusions either, thus it was natural for him to not be able to even touch the sidelines when he was working alone.

"No matter, to gain power, one must surely be aware that a price must be paid in exchange." Garen exhaled.

To gain two hundred sets of heavy Black Fire armor would mean that two hundred people would have to be chosen as the carriers of the heavy black armor, to walk on the path towards strengthening oneself.

In other words, Garen would not be able to ultimately command these people. He only had the right to recover the Zibane Power, but if someone was strengthened to a powerful degree, even if the strength was recovered, his power would still remain. The physical characteristics that were altered by Zibane would not change.

It meant that even if more than half of the strength was recovered, it would still remain.

This way, his control of his subordinates would not be as tight anymore.

But Garen was unconcerned.

The only thing that he wanted was power, and strength that was sufficient enough. Whether or not he could grasp it, depended on his own abilities.

Bang bang bang.

Suddenly, a series of rhythmic door-knocking noises broke his train of thought.

"What’s the matter?"

He asked in a slightly impatient manner.

"P… Palace Master, there’s a group of people… They’re carrying a heavily injured woman, and are here to see you, saying that they’re your old friends," said the servant girl in a loud but shivering voice.

"Old friends?" Garen closed his eyes and converged his thoughts. He pulled the curtains on the right closed.

He walked towards the doorway and opened the main door. Outside the door stood a servant girl with shivering legs, she was extremely pale, and did not dare to raise her head. It was obvious that this girl had just entered the palace, and did not seem older than eleven or twelve years old.

Garen opened the door and eyed the girl carefully. He was about to speak.

"Don’t… Don’t eat me!!" The little girl was frightened to the point where she sat on the floor. "Palace Master… I beg you, I was wrong! I’ve learnt my lesson!! I’ll never do it again!!"

Garen’s had a blank expression on his face, he was merely surprised at the rare arrival of a new servant girl at the Black Fire Palace, and when the time he took to size her up increased slightly, he had frightened her to this degree. He assumed that this girl thought that his curious gaze was actually him deciding on which part of her flesh he would like to devour first.

This girl seemed like she was used to getting bullied, and would frantically admit to her wrongdoings before the situation cleared up.

"Damn, those rumors will be the death of me!" he cursed softly.

"Take me there!" A noise echoed behind the little servant girl instantly.

The little girl got up from the floor quickly and ran inside the palace with Garen while her whole body was still shivering.

Garen followed closely behind her silently.

At the side of the Black Fire Palace hall, the girl dragged Garen behind her, before disappearing in a puff of smoke as she ran.

Garen was not the only one who was speechless, as the people in the palace hall were speechless as well.

There were a boy and girl in black clothes, who both had white leopard heads printed on the arm sleeves of their clothes.

They were led by a young boy and girl, and beside them on the floor, lying on a simple stretcher, was a pale yellow woman in a coma.

Garen glanced over, and was suddenly startled.

"Angel?!"

He recognized the woman on the stretcher as Angel, the female fugitive he had met in Iron Tank City.

She had once given him some raw material supplies in either the Kingdom or Trejons territory.

"How has she become like this?!" Garen walked over frantically and knelt beside the stretcher, before checking Angel’s condition carefully.

This allowed the group of people to let out a sigh of relief suddenly, while their initially frightened faces also began to look much better.

"So it’s true that the Palace Master knows Teacher!" said the young man that led the way, or perhaps the young boy, as he stepped forward immediately. "We’re from the Black Panther Mercenary Group, and Commander Angel is our teacher. I’m Gracie, and she’s Hill."

His upper lip had a soft, faint green mustache, he had short brown hair, and he could be no older than eighteen years old, but his face had a certain childlike perseverance and paleness. It seemed like he had lost a lot of blood as well. Currently, the boy was looking at Garen frantically.

"I’m begging you, please, please save Teacher!" The girl who was standing on the side had a red ponytail, and was crying terribly, and could not help but plead Garen. "We’ve thought of everything, and tried all kinds of medicine! All of the hospitals said that there was no cure."

"Stop crying! How can I save her if you don’t tell me the whole situation?!" Garen looked towards the boy, Gracie, who appeared much calmer. "You, tell me!"

The boy nodded solemnly.

"Teacher went out last month, and I heard that she had planned to go out with some of her old friends to do something, but I never expected that when she returned two days ago, that she would collapse suddenly, and become unconscious. We initially thought that she had been poisoned, but all the hospitals and Luminarists did not detect as much. After that, we assumed that her brain had suffered injuries, so we hired the best brain disease curing Luminarists, but to no avail. They could not detect any wounds."

"What did Angel say before she fainted? Did she allow you to come find me?" Garen asked softly.

"Teacher didn’t say anything, she just looked exhausted, as if she hadn’t had proper rest for many days." The boy shook his head. "As for coming to look for you, Palace Master, Teacher had never mentioned this. We only heard from our seniors in the group that Teacher and Palace Master used to be friends. Since we had no other options, we decided to come and beg you."

"You did well." Garen patted the boy’s shoulder. "Calm in moments of danger, very good!"

He bowed his head to check on Angel’s condition again.

Angel, who used to be curvaceous, was now a skinny bag of bones. Her blood flow was not unusual, and her body did not have any traces of poison, while her brain remained in a sleeping state, a sign that everything was normal.

"Oh no, this person is about to die," Kid’s voice suddenly trailed out from behind Garen.

"Do you know what’s wrong?" Garen was used to Kid’s elusive manner, and he did not even turn his head to ask.

Meanwhile the others were frightened to the point where they moved away, and some of the easily scared members swallowed their saliva, as they glared at Kid with a shocked expression.

Kid was sucking on a lollipop as he crouched beside the stretcher like Garen, while both of his hands shook aimlessly, waving around.

He furrowed his eyebrows and touched Angel’s forehead.

"She’s having a nightmare," He said certainly after a few seconds.

"Having a nightmare? You’re saying that someone pulled her into a nightmare, and now she can’t wake up?" Garen asked.

"Perhaps. Someone planted a seed on her that induces nightmares. She failed to realise it, and then fell right into the dream," Kid shrugged, a mature expression on his face.

"How do we solve this? Garen asked directly.

"It’s simple, we just need to get rid of the nightmare seed, however, most of these seeds will naturally hide themselves in her most private areas," Kid pursed his lips. "We’ll just have to see which of you can find it."

"Get rid of the nightmare seed?" Garen stood up and pondered. "I’ll do it."

"What are you planning to do?" Kid looked at Garen curiously. "If the seed has burrowed itself in her most intimate parts, you’ll be responsible."

"It won’t be that troublesome," Garen said nonchalantly.

His toes raised themselves, and the crowd cried in shock when Angel who was on the stretcher earlier was suddenly lifted up in the blink of an eye, and began constantly turning around in midair.

It was as if she was suddenly suspended in front of Garen.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh… The violent flipping of her body caused blowing wind noises to be heard.

Bang!

Garen slapped his palm against Angel’s shoulder suddenly. He instantly held her in place, clutching her in midair.

Bang bang bang!!

Endless slapping noises could be heard between the two of them continuously.

Garen’s palms slapped the unimportant parts of Angel’s body.

Each slap made Angel’s whole body shake, and some tiny, loose objects immediately fell off her body, and flew towards all four corners of the room.

This was one of the higher level skills of the Secret Techniques, Shake.

Using it here, with some added tricks, was just enough to shake all of the hidden things loose.

In the Secret Technique World, it was used to get rid of the hidden weapons and poisonous darts that were left in the dead soldiers, but was also extremely suitable for Garen to use here.

Soon, the objects that were shaken out lessened, and her outer clothes had almost fallen off as well.

Plop!

A purple dot fell suddenly fell out of the bottom of Angel’s shirt.

Bang!

Garen used both of his palms to support her, before carefully placing Angel back on the stretcher, with incomparably gentle strength. He showed extreme and precise control over his power.

"This is it."

Kid picked up the little purple dot, and saw that it was obviously an oval-shaped plant seed that looked like a soybean, except that its colour was different.

Garen and the others looked at Angel, noticing that her complexion had improved. She did not look as haggard as before.

Kid held the seed, wiped it on his shirt, and put it in his mouth instantly.

Crunch!

"Seems like something weird is flowing out, but it doesn’t matter, I’ll just chew it up." He chewed it for a few moments, before the sound of something falling could be heard, and swallowed it.

A group of people including Garen, immediately stared at him silently.

"You’re… alright??!" The red-haired girl stared at Kid with a shocked look on her face.

"Yes, I’m alright?" Kid rummaged his pockets, and took out a handful of purple seeds immediately. "I still have some, do you want any? They taste pretty good."

The others around him stood dumbfounded.

Chapter 451: Eve 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You…!! You…" The red-haired girl was at a complete loss for words.

"Why do you have this thing?" Garen stood at the side with his eyebrows furrowed and asked the question that everyone wanted to know.

Kid threw another one of those things into his mouth.

"This seed is actually from a type of plant called the Nightmare Vine. It has a strange ability that forces people into nightmares and makes them unable to free themselves, but I naturally have specialized physique, thus I wasn’t affected." He trailed behind Garen, as the opportunities for him to speak increased.

"But the seed from earlier tasted weird, as if it was cultivated wrongly, and were not as tasty as mine." He added another sentence right as he finished the first one.

"Do you always have dangerous things with you?!" The red-haired girl could not help but scream.

"You guys are just too weak." Kid looked at them contemptuously. "If you reached Form 3 you wouldn’t be affected by this anymore."

His sentence rendered the entire Mercenary Group speechless.

"Alright, Angel will recuperate here with me while the rest of you return to inform the others," commanded Garen the moment he opened his mouth.

Most of the Mercenary Group members did not dare to disobey orders, except for two of Angel’s disciples who stood on the spot and did not move.

Both of them exchanged glances.

The boy Gracie suddenly said in a loud voice.

"We want to stay behind and take care of Teacher as well!"

Garen looked at both of them carefully.

"Okay." He waved his hand.

Once the Nightmare Seed was extracted, Angel was fine. When she woke up, the situation cleared up naturally.

"Someone’s here."

Immediately, an older female servant rushed into the palace frantically.

"Palace Master?"

"Take them downstairs and arrange rooms for them there, make sure that their food and drinks are light and soft. Hire some doctors to come into the palace to take a look," Garen told her.

"Understood."

Soon, most of the people from the Black Panther Mercenary Group had left after Gracie and Hill’s instructions. Both of them carried Angel, and followed the servant into the guest room.

Garen pondered for a moment, and realised that he definitely lacked palace staff. Tasks such as arranging food and lodging required him to command them individually, which was very troublesome.

Suddenly, he thought of the two Dragon Blood death prisoners that he had modified. Those two had insufficient strength, but could do some housework at least. They could also help the extremely busy Lala.

Although Lala did not have a lot of strength, the critical thinking skills she had gained from the law department allowed her to manage the family business in perfect order. Those two could now become her subordinates.

After handling Angel’s situation, Garen called both of her disciples to his study room alone.

Watching Garen drink his green tea slowly as he sat on the chair made the two others slightly cautious of him.

"Have a seat."

The three of them were the only ones in the study, and there were no one else in their surroundings.

The entire Black Fire Palace was unlike the rumors from the outside, there were no violent bloody scenes, but instead it was deathly quiet.

Neither of them dared to defy him, so they quickly sat down on the bench on Garen’s left side.

"I called you here, because I wanted to know about Angel’s Mercenary Group, and what the current developments are? Why didn’t she contact me all this while?" Garen called a servant girl over to serve two cups of green tea to the others.

The boy Gracie smiled bitterly.

"Palace Master, I think I know why Teacher never contacted you."

"Oh?"

Gracie remembered for a moment.

"Everytime Teacher taught us, she would always sigh for an unknown reason. From Teacher’s words, I could always hear a certain.. longing." Gracie lifted his head and glanced at Garen.

"Teacher seemed like she always wanted to surpass somebody. Because of that, she worked hard determinedly. Meanwhile, Teacher always complained that her talents were not strong enough, and although she worked hard, she could never see a ray of hope. Frankly, we could never understand the meaning behind Teacher’s desire. In our eyes, Teacher was already strong enough. There would always be people in the world who were stronger than ourselves, and if we wanted to surpass all of them, one lifetime would be insufficient," he smiled bitterly.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows slightly.

Gracie seemed like a calm person who would not be fazed during peril, but he never expected that he would lack the desire and strength to improve. He did not like people like this.

Pushing that aside, he understood what Gracie meant.

Perhaps the person that Angel always wanted to surpass was an old acquaintance, or a friend, or maybe even Garen himself. This was something that nobody knew for sure.

"That’s right, this is the open communication device that Teacher left behind before she left." Gracie had thought of something suddenly, as he took a little square black box out of his arms.

The little box was made of black iron, and looked unimportant. There were rows of horizontal cracks on its surface, exposing its hollow interior.

This thing looked like the outside of a radio from earth.

"Open communication device?" This was the first time Garen had heard of this phrase in this world, it was a name that was obviously connected to technological terms.

"Hmm, could it be that Palace Master doesn’t about this?" Gracie was slightly shocked. He quickly explained. "This is a communication device that is currently very popular. Initially, only high levelled Totem Users had the right to use it; it can communicate with others from distances of over a thousand kilometers, using a shapeless resonance technology. It was developed in the Rainbow Domain, as it was said that they caught a small insect species that possessed natural resonance abilities, thus they used these insects build nests, and researched them for a while, before finally creating this thing. Its price is…"

"This thing is very cheap, only ten copper rumbs for one," interrupted the red-haired girl on the side, as it was finally time for her to present herself, as her brother had said everything earlier, making her feel non existent. Now that Teacher had finally gotten out of harm’s way, she had almost returned to her normal, girlish lively nature.

"It only requires one copper rumb?" Garen picked up the black box, and noticed that there were two switches on the right side. One of them was a button, and pressing it would decide if it was opened or closed. The other was a knob that was probably used to adjust something.

"This communication device can self regulate frequencies, and if a predetermined frequency is chosen, many people from distances of over ten thousand kilometers could communicate with each other at the same time, which would be extremely convenient. Except that its consumption source is something called an Acer Crystal, which is only sold in Rainbow Domain. One piece requires two copper rumbs, and is enough to last for an hour."

"No wonder this thing is so cheap," Garen realised. "So the key is its consumption."

"Mm," Gracie paused, before realising. They had only thought that this thing was interesting, but had never expected that Garen would look at it through the perspective of Rainbow Domain, and see the problem through the bigger picture. He saw that Rainbow Domain was controlling a large business opportunity through this.

Garen was quite impressed, after watching Gracie’s demonstrations of this thing, he learned how to use it after a few tries.

It had almost the same functions as an original radio from earth.

But it was more advanced than a radio, because this thing could be used to communicate. As long as the other person’s frequency was known beforehand, both parties could communicate directly. The distance between them could span up to ten thousand kilometers as well.

In simpler terms, if you spoke on one frequency, whether you intended it or not, everyone who happened to be on that same frequency would be able to hear what you were saying, and this was the true meaning of open communication.

However, these resonating frequency adjustments could reach extremely fine degrees, and there were a total of more than ten thousand grid scales, and the slightest movement would mean that the next grid would be a new frequency, making it impossible to use all of them.

The moment Garen turned on the communication device, strange loud noises could be heard from inside, as if many people were speaking at once, in chaotic confusion.

He adjusted it slightly, and changed to a different grid scale, before it quietened down.

"Are you here?"

"I’m here. Where do you want to exchange the goods today?"

"Did you bring the money?"

"Give me the goods first!"

"Give me the money first!"

"You don’t have the right to set requirements!"

Why did it feel like a gangster movie?

Garen looked at Gracie with a weird expression, while the latter slapped his own head suddenly, and took out a piece of light red foil and pasted it carefully on the surface of the communication device, covering the top of it quickly.

"This is a sound insulation membrane, it will ensure that the sounds you make on this side will not transfer over."

Gracie explained.

Garen tinkered with the communication device for a while, and felt that it was extremely fresh, as he had never expected that the technological advancements in this world would develop so quickly, as the Totem User’s usage of research could not be underestimated.

Since Totem User’s powers had already developed to such extreme lengths, they did not need such destructive technological advancements.

Large defensive covers that spanned over hundred square kilometers would never exist on earth.

Gracie and Hill noticed that Garen was having fun with the communication device, so they decided to just give it to him.

"Palace Master, a lot of people are using this now because it’s popular. They are other grades in Rainbow Domain, and this one here is medium grade. Below it are normal grade, while above are premium grade, luxury grade, aristocratic grade, gold grade, diamond grade and the only silver grade. The price increases with their grade. The important part is the difference between sound filters, and the variations in packaging appearances," Gracie explained.

"Understood," Garen nodded. The interior structure of this thing was very primitive, a sign that the Forgers in Rainbow Domain were unable to thoroughly study the principles properly, and were thus unable to make minor adjustments.

Upon seeing that Garen was playing with it intently, the other two got up to leave.

Next, Lala entered and quickly announced the recent news regarding the family business.

Garen listened casually and continued to play with the communication device, and asked some questions occasionally.

Lala had really managed everything properly, the resources that Garen had gained from the palace were used as the foundation of a new reward and punishment system, to establish a new set of perfect management systems.

This would motivate Totem Users to work hard, creating improvements as well. It also ensured that they were not too exhausted or troubled.

As for normal workers, there was a different set of beneficial methods as well. But it was obvious that it was not something that she had thought up on her own.

Garen just listened to these things casually. He only cared about his final income and expenditure summary.

"This is a set of welfare and wage systems that I came up with, could you look at it and see if anything needs to be added?" Lala brought out a thick stack of white documents.

Garen took the documents and flipped through them, and since his reading speed and memory analysis abilities were extremely quick, he was able to read through the entire thing within a minute, before he took his seal out and stamped it.

"I pass it, so you can take this to the Black Fire Palace’s treasury to take the necessary financial resources for each month. The elite Black Fire Guards there will release them automatically." Garen passed the documents back.

He paused.

"Furthermore, as the supervisor, you can elect a vice supervisor on your own to manage the other tasks. You have the authority to approve one hundred thousand gold rumbs for all of these receipts, and these one hundred thousand gold rumbs will be the total monthly expenditure."

Lala’s eyes widened suddenly, as she did not expect Garen to give her such great authority.

It was important to note that although the Trejons household was undergoing significant expansion, in reality, the entire household’s assets were under a million gold rumbs. This happened after Garen became one of the Four Gargantuans of the Kovitan Kingdom, and succeeded in selling a large number of houses in the vicinity of the palace.

Although the palace still belonged to the Royal Family in name, once Avic died, Ivycius and Edin of the Silver Palace remained silent, and immediately supported the Black Fire Palace. Under the circumstance that no one objected, naturally, no one would dare to object his invasion of the palace areas as well. Although the other three Gargantuans were at odds, they were not entirely innocent as well, and would obviously not dare to provoke him directly as well, in case everyone would be thrown into an uncomfortable state.

Especially under the circumstance when Garen’s name was related to violence and cruelty.

Chapter 452: Eve 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Lala, you’ve been with me for many years, haven’t you? Garen changed the subject suddenly.

"Yes." Lala adjusted her attitude quickly, and relaxed again, except that an irrepressible ecstasy was still present deep within her eyes.

She had always took care of everything for Garen behind the scenes, and had never complained. Even when she was held captive and had almost lost her life, she had never asked Garen for rest or remuneration.

Now she had finally received her due reward.

She had her own friends, and relatives too. During the period when she came to the Kingdom, as Garen’s influence expanded, she used this opportunity to find her lost relatives as well. As these people gathered beside her, they naturally became her source of strength.

To outsiders, she was the Black Fire Palace Master’s spokesperson.

Her position was respected, except among the Gargantuans, and everyone in the Kingdom regarded her with status and respect.

In the days when the Kingdom calmed down, she would receive many banquet invitations daily. Some of them would be rejected, while others would be chosen to attend.

Countless people fawned over her and flattered her, in hopes of getting some of the power and profits from her hands. As long as one formed a relationship with her, they would be able to gain the favour of the fearsome Black Fire Palace as well. Everything she did was done with confidence.

In that moment, Lala had thought of many things.

She suppressed her excited emotions, and bowed in front of Garen seriously.

"I will not let you down."

Garen nodded, and watched her turn around to leave. He had given a large amount of his authority to Lala. With the protection of the Black Fire Guards and his namesake, no one would dare to make things difficult for her. Even the other three Gargantuans would need to give her face.

************

In the weeks after that, Angel recuperated completely, and her body finally healed. When she knew that Garen had saved her, she immediately fell into an absent minded state. It was obvious that the person she had always been trying to catch up to, was actually Garen.

She had initially swore that she would protect Garen in Iron Tank City, and had never expected that she would be overtaken by Garen, as she once assumed that she would be able to catch up.

But the brutal reality completely shattered her remaining bits of pride.

Although she had never admitted defeat, and had never given up, now that she could see that she was being pushed further behind, and in the end, she could not even reach the borderline. This feeling made her remember the first thing she had said in front of Garen when she slapped the table.

She was a person with high self-esteem, and she had always felt that she could never be worse than others. Initially, she thought that she could never catch up to the geniuses because her talents were different, and they were treated in different conditions.

She never expected to encounter a living example like Garen.

For some time, she could not face Garen, and could only continuously force herself to become stronger, and this attitude brought her to the wrong path, and caused her Totem cultivation to become stagnant, forming consecutive failures. Later, after receiving encouragement from some friends in her circle, she attempted to find a shortcut, only to end up in an almost fatal coma in the end.

After she woke up, she did not come to see Garen properly.

But every morning, when Garen practiced his daily Myriad Water Jasper Technique exercises, she would always watch him from afar, but would say nothing.

It started as a coincidence, but after awhile, she would always wake up on time, and would always observe Garen from afar while he sat cross-legged on the ground, practicing his Secret Techniques.

Although she felt that it was weird for Garen to merely sit on the floor motionless for a period of time, she never came over to question him.

When Garen practiced his Secret Techniques daily, he could always feel the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon being absorbed and fusing with his body slowly. Through this specialized Secret Technique method, he could operate the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon’s blood flow and his own Totem Power, allowing both of them to fuse, and adapt to one another.

He practiced day and night, and during breaks in between, he would play with the open communication device, and soon Garen had started to call it a radio. It made him nostalgic about his days on earth.

*************

Many weeks had passed.

Angel finally came to face Garen properly.

In the morning while Garen was practicing his Secret Techniques, she finally walked over to him.

Garen, who was still sitting cross-legged on the floor, suddenly opened his eyes.

"You finally decided to come."

"I just couldn’t face you," Angel bit her lip, and her face was still slightly pale. "My main wish for the longest time, was not to let anyone feel that my achievements came from other people. Thus, I never mentioned our relationship to anyone."

"You’re quite extreme," Garen smiled, and got up from the ground.

"The War Chain’s abilities, are they still useful?" he asked casually, before taking a cup of mouthwash tea from a servant girl’s hand.

Angel did not answer, but the unhappy expression on her face clearly showed her emotions.

It was not useless, instead, it was extremely useful. But everytime the War Chain’s abilities increased, it meant that the distance between her and Garen was widening. The insulting part, was that she had always wanted to surpass Garen, but many times outside, the key moment that saved her life, was always reliant on the Chain’s abilities.

She had relied on these abilities when she had a disagreement with another Form 3 Totem User, and neither of them would give in to the other, and because this happened in the small scale mercenary community in the Kingdom, it also affected certain reputations.

Kovitan Empire was unlike Iron Tank City. This place was extremely powerful, and if it was not for the Chain’s abilities, she would have been swallowed without a trace already. Moreover, she would not be standing securely right now.

Garen drank a mouthful of tea, swirled it in his mouth, and spat it out immediately.

"You’re too preoccupied with strength, and your reputation. Put down your reputation. Sometimes, a friend’s strength is also a part of your strength. You need to understand this, strength that is borrowed and made your own, is the mark of a true victor."

Angel nodded unwillingly.

She looked at the twenty-something year old young man that stood before her, at this young age, he had already become the famed Kovitan Gargantuan. Unknowingly, he had already become a true genius that had left his youth behind.

Some people even compared him to the Three Heroes of the Three Main Domains.

Each of the Three Heroes stood firmly in the endless sea of monsters, and had built a powerful presence of illustrious feats.

Garen himself, had deep contacts with Black Field’s Hawk King, Goth.

This background, this strength, and these battle records quickly made Garen one of the biggest influencers of Kovitan’s situation.

His each word and command, would lead to actions of the people around him, and would unconsciously bring a surge of hidden movements.

"The situation in the Kingdom is unlike the past, and although many aristocrats have left, remaining soldiers from the defense line after the defeat flooden in instead, forming three major garrisons, meanwhile the common people from the border areas flooded into the outskirts of the Kingdom as well, and as their numbers increase, our food storage has become insufficient, and now that it is summer, more support will be needed for the arrival of summer."

As the main Gargantuan in the parliament, Garen would naturally receive sufficient news regarding the current situation.

The parliament had took over the previous imperial system, but the ministers below them remained, and were tasked with managing their own problems, and summarizing the messages from the bottom before they were sent to the higher ups.

The difference between the two systems was that Avic used to rule on his own previously, but now the parliament of the Four Gargantuans were the rulers. Only issues that were deemed too serious for the Four Gargantuans, or situations where there were similar vote numbers, would require them to hold large parliament votes again.

"Currently the elite soldiers are flooding inside, and have robbed the livelihood of you mercenaries to a large extent. Competition within the mercenary world will become greater in the future." Garen looked at Angel. "I’m getting ready to establish a school-of-thought-like organization, to receive more disciples. I happen to have a powerful method in my hands, but the danger is far too great."

"What method?!" Angel suddenly had an unrepentant feeling in her heart, she did not care that she had been saved by Garen anymore, and although the war Chain was dependent on the mercy of Garen and many others, she knew that she would never be able to surpass this man in her lifetime, and had simply relaxed her mind.

She was no longer tangled in the incident that required her to rely on Garen.

"It’s very dangerous, and you could be inflicted with an intense amount of pain. I’ll let you have a taste, and if you can handle it, I will let you try," Garen said earnestly.

"I'll do it." Angel answered without hesitation.

She had always been a persevering person, she had once been pursued for a thousand kilometers, and had been fled the Northern Region for her life. Even then, she had never once given up.

Garen nodded, as Angel’s reply was just as he had expected.

"Be careful."

Just as he finished speaking, his fingers shot out like lightning, and touched Angel’s forehead.

Angel felt as if she had been caught in thunderstorm, and was frozen on the spot, motionless.

Her face contorted, and the skin on the entire body gradually became red, while both of her hands were tightly balled into fists, and her fingernails had pierced directly into her palm, but she felt nothing.

Pap!

Garen stretched his fingers out and touched her forehead again.

Whoosh!!

Angel suddenly bended at the waist, while her entire body was covered with sweat, as if someone had just pulled her out of the water, as her clothes were completely soaked through. In those few seconds, the sweat that was expelled from her body was enough to form two wet footprints on the ground.

She began panting violently.

"How is it?" Garen looked at her worriedly. "This kind of pain, if we really begin, it will be one level stronger, as this was just a slight example."

"It’s… Amazing!!" Angel raised her head, and saliva was beginning to dribble out of her mouth, while a joyful, blushing expression appeared on her face.

"This feeling… It’s simply wonderful!!" She seemed to have enjoyed it, and was panting continuously, while she moaned quietly and alluringly.

Garen’s mouth gaped opene. He wanted to say something, but finally settled on closing his mouth and exhaling a deep breath.

He never expected that Angel would have these attributes, as the world was truly full of mysteries.

No wonder she was so strong-willed. She was a true masochist…

Frankly, he could already see that Angel’s Luminarist talents were slightly stronger than his own, but because she had diverged on the wrong path, and attempted to take a shortcut, she had ultimately lost her conscience. On the path towards Totem cultivation, when one’s original adaptability with their Totem decreased, it would finally become completely stagnant in the end.

Thus, he thought of allowing her to use the path of the Green Vine Sphere. In this chaotic world, the ones that were least likely to be lacking were the regular people with strong wills.

Extreme hatred, extreme desire, extreme madness, and extreme hurt. All of these were factors that could strengthen one’s spirit and will.

In this chaotic world, these things were definitely not lacking.

"Alright, you should go and get ready. After three days, I will publicly announce that I am officially looking for disciples." Garen had already decided that he would make the official public announcement after three days.

This time, his main aim was to find regular people, especially those who excelled in fighting but were quickly declining. They were lacking a lot of master-level fighters, and this was a good chance.

After getting modified by the Zibane Power, they would soon become strong, peak-levelled masters.

"Besides this, your revenge…"

"I’ll solve that on my own!" Angel interrupted Garen, and said decisively.

Chapter 453: Martial Arts 1

Translator:EndlessFantasy Translation

Editor:EndlessFantasy Translation

As he saw Angel turning to leave, Garen shook his head slightly.

"It's not so easy to fuse with this power…"

There was a limit, even for a masochist. Although this kind of breakthrough was an enjoyment, she might even collapse faster than a normal person.

However, everything had its pros and cons. He hoped Angel could get through this.

Without much emotions, Garen thought for a moment.

"Come."

Very quickly, a heavily armored Black Fire behind him and kneeled on one knee.

"Go and bring the Lord of the Silver Palace. I have something to discuss with him."

The Blackfire Guard did not answer. He merely stood up quietly and quickly left the courtyard.

They had capacity for speech. Although they maintained some form of abilities and intelligence, they were only equivalent to ten-year-old children.

Garen then instructed another servant to inform Lala, the supervisor, to prepare some essentials. It was all needed for Angel to adapt to Zibane's power.

When Ivycius arrived, Garen was busy instructing his subordinates on the things required for the next few days.

Maxilan and Edney behind Ivycius. As usual, the two of them were each in Green Vine Sphere armor. There were a blood vessel-like structures on the top, with green liquid speedily flowing through them.

"Just in time. I have something important for you to do." Garen nodded as he saw the pair. "Everything has been clearly stated in my previous letter. Have you all decided?"

Maxilan and Edney nodded their heads positively with firm expressions.

"That's good. The process is simple. In my Blackfire Guard, there are fifteen of them who can fuse. Once you reach the place, all you have to do is sit on the position and the armor will initiate the fusion process. The process will be immensely painful. Of course, the longer you withstand it, the greater the improvement of your abilities. Go to the Blackfire Palace once you're ready. I've already prepared everything there."

Garen explained in simple terms.

Maxilan nodded. They came together with two of the toughest guards in the Trejon Household. It was all about whether they could succeed this time. If they did, they would be able to step into a level that could compete with totem users.

As normal humans, they were different from Angel, who was innately a totem user. Obtaining powers like these would be a totally new experience for them.

Obtaining the power of Zibane did not mean that they would become strong overnight. It simply changed the attribute of the body to be able to withstand totem light. This gave normal people an opportunity to be on a level playing field as totem users.

Garen did all he could to prepare for his family and alleviate the pain. However, was barely effective. 90% of the process was dependent on the person's will and body.

Maxilan and the rest didn't utter much. The days of meditation had cultivated a strong will in them to surpass this barrier.

Garen could also see this. Without asking much, he waved his hand and instructed them to go.

Ivycius was the only one left in the courtyard as he stood quietly at a side.

"What's the matter?" Ivycius was already somewhat different than before.

His hair had already reached his waist. It was white as silver and tied in a bundle. His eyes were like high-quality white jade as his pupils were completely invisible. At the same time, there was a faint fragrance emanating from his body.

"I need your men for something." Garen whispered. "Send someone to the Seven Night Tower on the North Snowy Mountains. As my Blackfire Palace is recruiting disciples and announcing to the world, naturally we need some masters with substance to view the ceremony. The Lord of the Seven Night Tower, Anjiad and I hit it off well."

"Where's the gift?" Ivycius was lazy to even ask.

Garen threw out a small, black bag.

"This is the deposit. The Seven Night Tower is the strongest force in the North Snowy Mountains. Although their followers are poor, their elites still count for something."

"You want to invite the Lord of the Seven Night Tower as a guest?" Ivycius furrowed his brows. "But you've robbed a big portion of the Royal Treasury. This doesn't affect you at all."

"That's unimportant. What is most important is our own strength." Garen shook his head. "How has your progress been?"

Ivycius shook his head slowly.

"I'm stuck at the most important stage. If I take this step, I would definitely level up within a year!" He spoke confidently with an air of determination.

He gave Garen a glance in the end. "God Cloud's clone of the Emperor was heavily pursued by the Director of the Secret Service and almost fell. Do you know of this?"

Garen was caught off guard.

"When did this happen?"

"The news came the day before yesterday. Out of desperation, God Cloud had to reveal his actual self to fight. After battling with the Director from a distance, he managed to save his clone. But in this battle, he was slightly weaker than the Director and was heavily wounded. It's estimated that he won't be able to recover within these few years." Ivycius repeated the news that he heard.

"Not listening to the Director's words is looking for death. He can't blame anyone." Garen laughed coldly.

"But he still achieved half of his objective." Ivycius sighed. "Besides, the elites that you wanted to find have been found. What do you plan to do?"

"Set up a ring, the winner is king. The final three people standing would be given a place to join my Blackfire Palace." Garen had no expression, as if he had long thought about it.

"That's good. I'll go and make the arrangements." Ivycius nodded as he gradually disappeared into the shadows and left quickly.

Garen stood alone in the courtyard. He closed his eyes and descended himself into a state of mind to train his martial arts.

As time passed, he gradually understood the details of fusing with the Nine-headed Hydra.

Regarding this type of fusion, it was far easier for other totem users compared to Garen.

They only had to fuse once to complete the process.

But Garen had nine lives. The Nine-Life Talent brought an incredibly strong life force, but at the same time also brought a huge burden.

Garen had to fuse nine times in order to fuse all the nine heads into his martial arts and become one with his body. Only then could he could step into fifth form.

He had been meditating daily for the past few days. Every time he activated the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, it would shorten the distance between himself and the first of the nine heads.

As the Nine-Headed Hydra moved from the sides to the middle, the dragon heads gradually strengthened. The most terrifying of them all was the golden dragon head in the middle. It was the source of almost 80% of the Nine-Headed Hydra's power.

Every time Garen trained his martial arts, he would come to realize that the Myriad Water Jasper technique and the Nine-Headed Hydra were not a perfect fit. The majority of their paths fared well, but there was a small minority which rejected one another.

He had vast experiences in martial arts. He could even master theoretical techniques like the Divine Statue Technique. Naturally, he had ways to overcome this problem.

Recently, he had been spending most of his time adjusting the Myriad Water Jasper Technique to suit himself more.

Most of the adjustments were slight tweaks, according to the Nine-Headed Hydra's blood flow.

　　*********************

On the day of the announcement, everything was prepared.

Garen sat quietly in the garden. The four sides were surrounded by four heavily-armored Blackfire Guards to prevent him from being disturbed.

He was clothed in a white robe as he sat cross-legged on the ground. Black fog surrounded his body while faint strange noises came from within.

Undeterred by the black fog, the jade-like moonlight shined on Garen's body.

On Garen's skin, the faint, constantly moving red shadow of the Nine-Headed Hydra was visible. Each of the nine heads looked different. Some of them were grim, terrifying, quiet or even lonely.

Cheeeee!

Garen abruptly opened both of his eyes. Two red rays of light shot out like arrows, converging into two red lines midair. They dissipated after a brief period.

The left dot on his forehead was emitting a bright red glow.

Garen raised his hands and opened his left palm. Red light flashed over it, forming a red ball the size of an egg. A ferocious dragon head faintly appeared on the surface of the ball. It disappeared as quickly as it appeared, as if it were never there.

Garen abruptly clenched his fist.

The red ball exploded silently into tens of thousands of smaller red balls of light, gathering and quickly circling him.

The black fog mixed quietly spread towards his surroundings, permeated by the red lines.

The plants in the garden were like living things drinking water, greedily absorbing the black fog. Gradually, each of their surfaces turned black. Some of them even had red lines like the black fog, strangely mysterious.

Very quickly, the black fog completely covered the garden.

As the black fog rumbled, there was a ray of white moonlight that formed a puddle through the fog and onto Garen's body.

The moonlight pillar was incredibly clear, as if it were an actual solid.

At the same time, like resonance, the Silver Palace also emitted thick white gas.

A fragrance of faint rose came from the Silver Palace.

In the middle of the Silver Palace, swathes of white smoke formed a huge slowly rotating white whirlwind. Ivycious was seated right in the middle.

He gazed towards Garen from afar. Both of his eyes were white and devoid of pupils.

"You've found the juncture as well?" Ivycious mumbled. He retrieved his gaze and continued to close his eyes, focusing on the totem fusion.

Three white fire stations were placed in a triangular shape surrounding his body. Three basins of white flames were burning on top of them. The large amounts of white smoke were from these flames.

After some time, the gas in the two palaces gradually dissipated.

In the Blackfire Palace, the abnormalities all over Garen's body had disappeared as well.

He slowly opened his eyes. A red light flashed over his face. The left red dot on his brows dimmed a little, not as red as before.

As he felt the changes to this body, he let out a long sigh.

After being repressed for so many days, he finally understood all the details of the fusion process. After ensuring there would not be any problems, he started fusing the first dragon head proper.

It was the dragon head on the far left.

As the Nine-Headed Hydra had nine heads, he had to fuse nine times to thoroughly complete the fusion process. The difficulty level of the nine heads slowly increased, starting from the easiest in the beginning to the hardest at the end.

Moreover, fusing each dragon head with martial arts would cause drastic changes to this body.

Garen stood up, faintly sensing an unexplainable change in his body. His breath capacity seemed much larger than before.

This time, he completely fused the dragon head to the far left into his body.

He glanced at the attribute pane below his vision. Sure enough, there were new changes.

'Strength 14. Agility 10. Vitality 10. Intelligence 10. Potential 710%. Possesses Luminarist Qualities.'

'Martial Arts - Myriad Water Jasper Technique, Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills.'

On one of the martial arts panes, there was a clear transformation.

'Myriad Water Jasper Technique: Myriad Water True Technique (Second Level, Total of Five Levels). Can control all forms of liquid within a specific area.

Martial Arts Additional Effects

Toxin strengthened by two levels. (From the Color Changing Butterfly Totem, Nine-Headed Hydra. All attacks have hallucination and deadly toxin effects)

Regeneration strengthened by one level (From the Nine-Headed Hydra, quick recovery after injury.)

Chapter 454: Martial Arts 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The two consecutive strengthening effects caused Garen to think deeper.

It was evidently the effect of totem fusion and martial art training. With his martial arts level, it naturally wasn’t hard to identify. Even if no adjustments were made to the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, there was already a feeling of beyond recognition.

"What if I had not fused with the Nine Headed Hydra but with other totems? Will the additional strengthening effects be different?" He gave some thought. "This fusion method could be a self-propelled evolution method. It changes to suit the user into a form that suits the user the most."

In simple terms, the Myriad Water Jasper technique was just the basic foundation. As different totem users reach fifth form and fuse with different totems, the effects of the techniques will also be different.

At this time, Garen had a subtle realization. If he passed on his techniques to a normal person and trained him to the peak, the person might have similar effects with himself. Even if the power was slightly lesser, it was just a matter of compatibility.

If he continued to fuse with the Nine Headed Hydra, even he himself wasn’t clear how his techniques would evolve and strengthen.

This effect was as if his martial arts were using the totem fusion to evolve itself into a higher level.

If ten thousand people were trained in the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, there might be ten thousand different skills.

"Are martial arts the ultimate foundation?"

Sitting cross-legged in the garden, confusion arose in Garen’s mind.

Martial arts, totems, and oneself. There was a mysterious connection between these three elements, although they seemed independent. In fact, they were one.

Within his churning mind, he secretly made a decision.

In this world, among totem users, martial arts peaked at the fourth form. In fact, only fifth form masters were qualified to train. Normal humans had no chance to even learn. Without sufficient abilities, there weren't much benefits in training. At most, it was to strengthen the body.

Among the normal humans, the Master-level elites had their own secret training methods similar to martial arts. It was just far less advanced compared to the level in his previous world.

It could be because of the existence of totem users, the martial arts of normal humans did not have a chance to shine.

But Garen could now see a silver lining for normal humans.

Initially the qualifications to learn the Myriad Water Jasper Technique were relatively demanding, but it was far simpler than a totem user’s qualifications. At least, the proportion among ordinary people would be far larger. There would be at least be one among a hundred who can train in this technique.

Now, the evolved technique had faintly surpassed the martial arts’ innate level.

The evolved martial arts could completely change the human structure. It has reached the level where it can evolve the body.

As Garen thought, he continued training the next level according to the instructions given by Celine.

Strangely, after fusing with the first dragon head, the Myriad Water Jasper Technique was no longer difficult for him. With only ten minutes or so, he entered the second level.

Initially he had completely understood the whole technique. As he was on the level of the King of the Century, the effects should have taken place long ago, but they've only happened now. Not earlier or later, but now.

This startled Garen a bit.

Since he was trained in the Divine Statue Technique, he had thoroughly opened the blood vessels within his body long ago. His vitality attribute was already strengthened until 10 points. In addition to the Nine Headed Hydra’s heart, he was on a mind boggling level.

These effects should be natural.

But Garen felt a little strange.

He quickly surpassed the second level. For a commoner-grade martial art, the Myriad Water Jasper technique wouldn’t be considered difficult to learn for Garen’s level. Next, it was the third level.

The third level took an hour. It cleared all the hidden vessels, and even some complicated vessels in the brain.

For a normal martial artist, without Garen’s foundation in the Divine Statue Technique, his elite control of blood flow and his deep understanding on martial arts, it might take ten years.

Next was the fourth level. He was on a roll. Few of the main blood vessels were the same as Garen’s Divine Statue Technique. He quickly surpassed that level.

For the fifth and final level, most of the effects were in the brain. It encompassed countless tiny blood vessels and nerves.

In summary, the fifth level used a unique method to activate certain areas in the brain to achieve the supernatural ability of controlling water.

This was the true form of the Myriad Water Jasper technique.

After surpassing five levels to the top in one go, Garen finally opened his eyes. The surroundings were in total silence.

It was already midnight.

The surrounding air was frigid. The garden of flowers and grasses let out a rhythmic sound in the wind.

The two oil lamps hanging on the roof glowed a faint yellow light.

After reaching the peak of the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, some combat skills would of course come as one.

Garen stretched out his hand and grabbed lightly. Droplets of moisture quietly gathered from the surrounding into his hand, forming water beads.

The perfectly round water beads floated quietly on top Garen’s palm. Their surfaces clearly reflected the surroundings.

Garen swung one of his hands.

Huaaa!!!

A clear stream of water gathered in the air before him to form a water dragon. The water dragon was circling around constantly like a clock.

Yet, Garen let out a sigh of disappointment.

In the Martial Arts world, a technique like this would be considered amazing and uncomparable. It was almost out of the human realm and could be known as a superhuman ability.

Once the enemy draws near, the blood all over his body would be controlled. Being free from the body’s control, it would be fully extracted. In the Martial Arts world, it would be known as the strongest assassination technique!

The Myriad Water Jasper technique was known as the best ambush technique. It indeed wasn't something to be trifled with.

However, although it was strong, it was still dependent on the environment it was in.

This was a world of totem users. A martial art like that wouldn’t cause fear to any totem user. It was a simple superhuman ability. If it could not penetrate totem light, everything would be useless.

The process of training the Myriad Water Jasper Technique was in fact a process that allows the human body to surpass its limits and develop superhuman ones.

The flow of water could also form a wall of defense by surrounding the body. Among the fighting skills that came with the technique, was the form of a high-pressured water gun, a skill that could suffocate the enemy to one that could quietly snap the opponent’s blood vessels.

Snapping different blood vessels would create different effects. All these needed a deep understanding of the human body. Unfortunately, the main opponents here were no longer normal people.

These methods had no value at all.

If it were in his previous world, maybe each of them would be elite techniques that could shock the world.

However, Garen subtly felt that he could surpass the limits of this technique through the fusion with the Nine Headed Hydra.

There were only eight heads left on the Nine Headed Hydra. It seemed a little depressed. Garen wanted to continue the fusion process but it seemed to be rejecting.

Since he could not fuse with the dragon heads in the near future, Garen did not force it, but instead diverted his attention towards researching the mystery of martial arts.

He noticed that although the Myriad Water Jasper Technique was already at its peak, but it was slightly different than the original. After adjusting it with the Nine Headed Hydra, there seemed to be space to continue progressing forward.

Since he thought about it, he decided to do it. Garen didn’t have to care about sleeping. He had incredible resistance and superhuman vitality. Not sleeping at this point of time will not bring any side effects to himself.

Step by step, he used the peak of the Myriad Water Jasper technique as the foundation and continued forward. With his nine lives, he wasn’t afraid of being injured or things going wrong.

He failed for more than ten times and was heavily injured up to the point of almost losing his life. However with his huge life force, he did not lose his life and managed to derive a new level for the Myriad Water Jasper technique.

Garen successfully connected it to his totem power.

The source of totem power was the brain.

Garen slightly adjusted the activation path for the Myriad Water Jasper Technique. He tweaked it to activate the part the produces totem power.

Under his constant experimentation, just like the Green vine Sphere, there was finally a glimmer of hope for normal humans to become strong.

It did not have an evil inclination like the Green Vine Sphere. The sixth level of the Myriad Water Jasper Technique that he derived allowed a normal human to activate totem power once they reached this level. They would then have the qualifications to be an actual totem user.

However, although this new technique was strong, it was difficult to find usages for it in a battle.

Garen thought for a moment and added in parts of the Divine Statue Technique that he was most familiar with. The Divine Statue Technique was formed by a combination of the White Cloud Gate and the Golden Statue Technique, to reach an level unreachable by mortals.

After all the incorporations, the Myriad Water Jasper Technique was totally unrecognizable. It had completely become a new martial art.

Garen wanted to carefully explore the next level. But without fusing with more dragon heads, he had no stronger path to base his derivation upon. He felt it wasn’t the best and forgot about it.

The new Myriad Water Jasper technique incorporated many of Garen’s martial art secrets. It gave normal people hope towards the peak.

Even then, this path was equally difficult.

The first step was to train the new Myriad Water Jasper technique to its peak as the foundation. Then only could they face the next key checkpoint - breaking through totem power.

Even after Garen’s adjustments and improvements, finally he could only simplify the Myriad Water Jasper technique into four levels.

Only by training these four levels, there was a chance to activate totem power.

This technique was based on Garen’s foundation. Its greatest effects were basically similar to the ones described in the ability pane.

Water control, toxicity and strong regenerative abilities.

In other words, Garen’s current state of martial arts was the peak state of this technique.

Garen had a feeling. After finalizing the martial art, for everyone training it in the future, those that arrive at the peak will become weaker versions of the Nine Headed Hydra….With another dragon heart transplant, sufficient state of mind and the same natural talent, he would be another "Mini Garen".

However to train the four level of this technique was incredibly difficult. It was only slightly simpler than the original Myriad Water Jasper technique.

The original Myriad Water Jasper Technique was already very difficult. Only during Neptune Fist’s peak, there was someone that reached its peak.

Now it was only slightly simpler. To succeed, without suitable natural talent, strong will and relentless determination, it was impossible to reach the peak.

The only thing Garen could do was broadening the scope of qualifications. By broadening the scope, it would increase the number of people. Surely a talented and strong-willed genius would appear one day.

Sensing the martial art that had been totally revamped, it could no longer be called the Myriad Water Jasper technique. There were too many elements mixed into it.

He stretched out his index finger. A crystal water snake crawled up, looking beautiful and pure.

"I am the Lord of Blackfire Palace. My body totem is the Nine Headed Hydra, which is the lord of the swamp and a water totem. This martial art can be called Black Water Technique."

He hesitated for a moment.

"Out of the whole wide world, this is the only martial art that allows a normal human to walk towards the path of an elite. It allows activation of totem power, I should add the word "True" to it."

"From today onwards, this martial art will be called Black Water True Technique!"

Chapter 455: Disciples 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Outside Kovitan Palace. A plaza at an intersection.

Several tall circular rings stood quietly in a triangular formation.

There were three fully white rings, with huge crowds surrounding them. From time to time, there were people cheering, people lifting up their hands as support and whispering among worried faces. However, most of them were wholly fixated on the rings.

"Ice sword!"

A cold female voice came from the ring. With a tinkling sound, a ray of silver-white light turned into a sharp beam. It jolted forward towards a black-haired man on the opposite end of the ring.

The man's expression changed and thrusted his right hand towards the ground.

With a bang, a cloud of black smoke arose, hiding him within it.

Nothing could be seen within the black smoke. The sharp white beam quietly disappeared after.

After a moment, a white-robed female quickly retreated from it. She looked pale with her hand clenching her left shoulder.

After she came out, she could no longer keep standing. As she fell and sat on the ring, the thin white sword in her hand snapped into two with a crack.

"Blackbird wins!"

A red-robed noble with a white wig who sat beside the ring announced boomed.

"Next!"

An attendant beside the noble shouted.

"Don't understand what the Lord is thinking. I understand that he wants to recruit outside forces, but what's the point in recruiting normal human fighters like this?" A few noblemen and women beside the ring discussed between themselves.

The men dressed in red were handsome and graceful. The women who wore white lace dresses were feminine and charming. They weren't advanced in years but there was a hint of arrogance in their eyes.

"Don't guess the intentions of the Lord. We just have to follow his orders. Many people would fight for a supervising job like this." A beautiful girl wearing a round, white hat muttered.

She held a white umbrella that seemed to be more for aesthetics than practical use. She wore pearl earrings on both of her ears. She put her long, rounded legs together and tilted them slightly, her white lace tunic skirt evidently revealed her figure.

"My Lady. Do you think that our Lord received orders from the princess, which is why….?" One of the nobles asked softly.

"Who knows? Alright, stop guessing. My advice is good for you." The lady said softly. "This time, the Blackfire palace's disciple recruitment is incredibly rewarding. If we allow trash to enter the palace and something happens, it would be troubling for us.

"We can say that. But aren't the people in the rings private soldiers from different noble families? Once they saw the opportunity, they rushed here to gain connections." A girl on the side pouted her lips, displeased.

"Both are normal human fighters, why can the peasants use but not us nobles? Shouldn't one's abilities be decided in the ring?" The male noble folded his arms and gazed towards the ring. "Look, its another peasant."

The rest of them followed and looked.

True enough, a common looking man was carried down from one of the rings. There was blood at the sides of his mouth. He was unconscious, yet it was obvious he was quite severely injured.

A man in green tights stood on the stage with a thin sword in one of his hands. Blood dripped from the tip of his sword as he looked arrogantly at his opponent below.

"Pass. Winner has won 15 matches consecutively and advances to the finals!" The judge announced loudly.

The man in green nodded lightly. There was a glimmer of delight in his eyes as he walked towards the back of the ring.

There were rows of white chairs with winners sitting on some of them. All of them had won 15 matches consecutively.

Most of them were dressed as nobles. Their closed looked luxurious and delicate, with a distinct western vibe.

Only a minority were dressed like peasants, each of them remained solemn without uttering a word. They were different from the nobles. This viewed this audition with much more importance.

Scenes like this were all over the kingdom.

Yesterday, the Blackfire Palace announced that they would be having auditions to recruit disciples. They made announcements through the most popular radio channel and also by posting notices and distributing fliers everywhere.

For anyone who placed within the top three, the Lord of Blackfire Palace would personally take them as disciples. They would be taught a technique that would help them to surpass the level of normal humans, becoming a master on the level of totem users.

Even for those who failed to enter top three, the top hundred would also qualify to enter Blackfire Palace for an opportunity to be reborn as a Blackfire Guard.

Before the fight began, Lord Garen appeared personally for a speech.

"No matter rich or poor, old or young, male or female. Anyone who meets the requirements, I will bestow upon you the power you desire."

In that moment, twenty rings were opened at the same time throughout the whole kingdom. Elite fighters among normal humans were steadily being screened.

In the past, there were auditions like that by other departments. However, they were used to select totem users. The requirement for normal guards wasn't huge at all. They were commonly selected directly from low level noble disciples or knights.

Peasants had totally nothing to do with it. In fact, this path to success had been cut off by the nobles.

The only hope for peasants was to enter the noble's circle through achievements, contributions and military exploits, to become one of them.

But now, the Blackfire Palace was the first one to break this taboo.

It caused a lot of resentment among the major noble families.

The saving grace was thag the Blackfire Palace was only recruiting a hundred men. Moreover, according to rumors, the Lord would personally bestow upon them a martial art technique.

Nobody knew what a martial art was. What fighting technique deserves to be personally bestowed by the lord? Any form of fighting technique without a forger's tools, should be easily suppressed by a first form totem user.

However after the notice was updated for a second time, the entire kingdom went crazy.

Crowds rushed towards the rings in droves, with more and more people waiting for their turn to enter the ring. Some of them were locals, some were military men, some were noble disciples, and some were also mercenaries and foreigners from out of the kingdom.

There were elderly men, and immature boys and girls. Most of them were fighters that had no glimmer of hope.

All of this came from Garen's second announcement.

"Blackfire Palace recruiting disciples. Totem user qualifications are ignored. Totem users are not allowed to participate."

Someone verified the truth with a Silver Palace guard. The Lord of Blackfire Palace truly held a key technique that could allow normal humans to surpass totem power.

Someone verified it again with a Trejon. Initially everyone thought that this technique would require an abnormally large sum of money to develop. It was unexpected that the Lord of the Blackfire Palace would open it up, allowing the public to audition.

Time passed day after day.

The news from Blackfire Palace gradually solidified.

The Lord of Blackfire palace developed a martial art technique known as the Black Water True Technique. After training to a certain level, it will allow normal humans to surpass their limit and activate totem power!

In an instance, the Black Water True Technique became the hottest topic in the kingdom.

Elite totem users flocked to the Blackfire Palace to see Garen. Even the remaining Gargantuans personally visited Blackfire Palace for a long discussion with Garen before leaving.

Low level totem users panicked. But after enquiring, they found out that this technique had many prerequisites. To be able to train to the level that surpasses the limit was not relatively easier than having a totem user qualification.

It would be even rarer than totem users. Only with this did the fear in the hearts of the lower level totem users reduce slightly.

They were the foundation of the Totem World. Gathering materials for forgers and providing totem power for tactic formations were jobs that normal humans couldn't do, but elite totem users didn't want to do. First form totem users were responsible for most of them.

Although many have ran away from the kingdom, there were still thousands of first form totem users.

Not mentioning the arrival of the three major armies and the nobles who had gradually returned from their leave.

********************

A week later, Dawn.

Within the Blackfire Palace

In the red-patterned, black main court, extraordinary men and women of sat on two rows of black stone chairs. It looked like each of them occupied a high position, viewing everything around them as distasteful. They seemed to distaste everything around.

Black robed boys and girls were all over the court, continuously serving fruits and wine.

The throne on the front of the court was still empty. On the two sides close to the throne were six slightly shorter black highback stone seats. The similar heights showed that the people that were about to sit on these seats had roughly the same status.

The six seats were separated into two sides, three on each.

Below was the crowd that sat on the black stone chairs. These were the representatives of notorious and powerful forces in the kingdom; there was the representative of the War Guild, Assassin Guild, high level nobles, major businessmen and so on.

For the six empty seats, no one thought they were unreasonable. If the Lord of the Blackfire Palace set it up this way, the statuses of these people were only slightly lower than him. It was evident that for the people that sat on those seats, their abilities matched up to their positions.

Finally, after some time, a white light of dawn shined into the court from the flanking windows, , and gathered in the middle of the court.

There was finally a figure on the palace's right entrance.

Three strange looking men and women in white robes walked into the court. Under the guidance of the servants, they sat on the three seats on the right hand side of the throne.

The nobles and representatives immediately caused an uproar. They turned to talk to each other but realized that no one recognized the three white-robed men and women.

The three of them were not young. The eldest of them had a head of white hair, estimated to be 70-80 years old. The youngest one was also about 50 years old. They had similarities in their dressing, where all of them had different amounts of white fox skin as decor. On the left of their faces were pitch black crescent marks, and the lone girl wore bells of different sizes all over her body. They rang continuously as she walked, giving off a foreign feeling.

"The Lord has arrived!"

With a swoosh, a black blur appeared on the throne. The figure was in black, his eyes electric. This was evidently the Lord of Blackfire Palace, Garen Trejon, whose fame had spread throughout the kingdom and even the whole of Kovitan.

Garen was tall and had good body proportions. As he sat on the throne, he gave off an imposing feeling, as if he were some huge tiger or dragon.

In the split second he appeared on the throne, the whole court shook mildly, as if they were letting out soft, overwhelmed sounds.

As the strong ones struggled to snap out of it, they realized that the palace was in perfect condition. The tremor just now was just an illusion of the heart.

In that instant, the crowd was shocked beyond words. Their respect towards the Lord deepened. Then they the realized, as one of the Four Gargantuans in the kingdom, he was currently still young. He could still be improving every second.

"The Lord of Silver Palace has arrived!"

Quietly, Ivycius' handsome figure appeared on the first seat to Garen's right. He held a long, white sword. He frowned slightly at the three people opposite him.

Only then did the crowd notice; the three mysterious persons on Garen's left weren't affected at all by the strong tremors just now. Their expressions only grew more solemn. If originally they seemed casual or even displeased with their seats, it was more evident now.

A circle or white faintly surrounded the three people. Suddenly, a young man or girl appeared behind each of them.

The three of them were also in tight-fitting snow white clothing. A small crescent-shaped white lock of fur was sewn on each of their shoulders. They had a respectful demeanor about them, and evidently they were the descendants of the three seated people.

At this point, three men walked out behind Ivycius. It was the Moonies. They wielded thin swords and stood behind him with the same respectful stance.

Garen swept his gaze throughout the court from his elevated seat. It finally landed on the three people to his left.

"This selection is an important matter that determines the foundation of my Blackfire Palace. Many thanks to the three Lords of Seven Night Tower who travelled far to come personally. It is indeed my honor."

"Your words are too kind. My Snowy Mountain Seven Night Tower has been Kovitan's neighbor for a long time. We have heard your fame. Being invited to view the ceremony is my Seven Night Tower's honor."

The white-haired elderly man in the lead quickly bowed his head and responded respectfully.

Chapter 456: Disciples 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I've heard that dangers are everywhere deep in the Snowy Mountains. Ferocious beasts roam the place and living conditions are harsh. The Seven Night Tower, as one of the strongest forces, can be known as the representative of the Snowy Mountains range. I never thought I would be able to meet the three Lords here." Ivycius slowly opened his mouth. As someone who already entered a mysterious level between fourth and fifth form, his speech gave off a strange indescribable feeling.

His words were clearly gentle and warm with extra attention to the terms, but it gave off a cold strange feeling to others.

"My apologies. I had some enlightenments recently, which changed my body." He himself knew the current state of his body and added on a few words to avoid any misunderstanding.

"This should be the Lord of Silver Palace? A hundred twenty years ago, White Rose Sword Sage Ivycius consecutively defeated the twelve Demon Lords of the East Sea, eradicating the Demon Lord Totem organization. For an achievement like that, even if we are located in the North region, we would have heard about it." The lady in the middle opened her mouth and said.

"Your words are too kind."

There was a commotion in the crowd below. Now only they knew that the White Rose Sword Sage from a hundred years ago was the current Silver Palace Lord Edin. His original name should be Ivycius.

"Let me introduce to all of you." Garen started to speak. He pointed towards the first person on his left - the white-haired elderly man.

"This is the Second Lord of Seven Night Tower, Moroba Blizzard. Known in the North as the Master of Eight Realms. The one behind him is his disciple."

The white-haired elderly man smiled as he stood up, and bowed towards the crowd below. His mannerism was a little different than central countries. He joined his hands and touched the tip of his own nose.

His disciple behind him followed in the same manner.

Garen continued to introduce the second person.

"The second one is the Fourth Lord of Seven Night Tower, Lucy Starnight. Known in the North as the Angel of the Night. The one behind her is also her disciple."

"Angel of the Night?" The one that just took a seat, Second Lord Blizzard grinned slightly. The Fourth Lord's nickname wasn't "angel", but "demon"... Her favorite thing to do on a normal day would be killing youths. Uncountable innocent lives have died in her hands. After aging in the recent few years, she toned down a little and stopped killing innocents. Before, just by mentioning her name in the North would stop a kid from crying.

Calling her an angel instead of a demon. Seeing Demon Girl Starnight smiling in pleasure, Blizzard knew a new side of Garen.

Garen didn't care and continued introducing the last one.

"The last one is an old friend. Third Lord Anjiad Spellcaster, known as the Spellmaster in the North."

Anjiad was the same wizened old man. He was short, but his sharp eyes gave off a feeling that he should not be trifled with. As he heard Garen's introduction, he stood up and forced a warm smile. He put his hands together and touched the tip of his nose, then sat down.

Master of Eight Realms, Angel of the Night, Spellmaster. These were the three masters sent by the Seven Night Tower to support Garen.

They were all true fourth form elites. Because of the harsh conditions around the Seven Night Tower, it caused the top to be incredibly strong, but the middle and lower class were severely powerless.

Moreover, differing from Kovitan and other strong countries, Seven Night Tower was located in the Snowy Mountain range. They were the strongest force in the vast region, but a peak fourth form was already their strongest representative.

The strongest First Lord was also only a peak fourth form. The only difference from the other Lords was that he controlled the only ultimate heirloom in Seven Night Tower. Throughout all the elites in the Snowy Mountain range, there were no totem users who could withstand him. Those that were slightly weaker than him had to group together to even put up a fight.

However, in the central division, even Kovitan already had three out of the Four Gargantuans. They each had their own ultimate heirlooms and were peak fourth form units. Kovitan as a single nation already far surpassed the strongest forces in the Snowy Mountains.

Not to mention an Original Heirloom like the Ultimate Shelter, people from the Snowy Mountain would never even have heard of it.

After understanding the frightening strength of the central region, an internal force in the Seven Night Tower instantly had some thoughts to leave Snowy Mountain. The three Lords were the representatives of that force.

Fortunately, Anjiad and Garen had crossed path multiple times and were familiar with each other. During his journeys to the North to kill monsters to recuperate potential points, Garen would meet Anjiad every single time.

The first time was a coincidence, but for the past few times, it was evident that it was Anjiad that took the initiative to approach Garen. Garen's Blackfire Palace was also currently lacking elite forces. Hence, the two sides hit it off well.

After a few interactions, the friendship began to grow.

Anjiad was a man of capricious nature. He was soft and conflict averse. Although he was a peak fourth form, he didn't like taking an enemy heads on, instead using his trained mutated beasts to do battle for him. After testing Garen a few times through their interactions, he realized his opponent was the type that countered his abilities. Since he couldn't defeat Garen, he was naturally convinced.

Garen relied on his frightening regenerative abilities. With his nine lives, he was never afraid of death and was incredibly ferocious. Within a few rounds, he broke through a huge wave of mutated beasts and headed towards Anjiad. Anjiad could see him regenerating from the wounds he had just obtained.

After two tests, Anjiad was completely won over.

It was the first time the crowd below had met masters from the North.

They have heard of the Snowy Mountains. After Garen mentioned the Seven Night Tower, some of the elderly faintly remembered. Before the mutation epidemic, the North and the central region had some relations. Representatives of the major business remembered a little clearer.

At that time, the kingdom's business alliance would go to the North to re-stock from time to time. Their fur and rare herbs were decent and of high quality. People from the North were not exposed to the world; a hundred-year snow ginseng only needed a hundred gold. It was incredibly cheap.

For other countries, the market price would at least be fifty thousand gold or above.

Gold was a common trade commodity. To convert to Rumbs, it was 10 to 1. Fifty thousand gold would be able to convert to five thousand Rumbs. It was abnormally cheap.

As time passed, some people from the business alliance looked at the North as a deserted land. No one thought that now the strongest force in the North, the Lord of Seven Night Tower would appear.

The crowd below were whispering, but the people on the top didn't care.

Next the servants made the announcement to bring the fighters from the audition.

The participants were brought up in batches. For this opportunity, they were selected winners out of tens of thousands of participants. Although it was merely one week of auditions, the things they've faced were already more than their previous years of lives. They were also much more complicated.

Noble businessmen played dirty tricks. Bribery, scheming, blackmail. Some noblemen fighters secretly hired totem users to severely injure other participants.

There were some used little tricks such as hidden tools to obtain victory.

Fortunately Garen requested for Ivycius' three disciples plus Lala's supervision, and also a few professors from The Grand Duke Benoc's institute to settle the various problems.

This successfully put an end towards most of the unhealthy competition.

As they winners were brought up, Garen asked people do place a giant jade-like stone in the middle of the court. All the winners would place their hands on the jade stone. For those who qualified for the Black Water True Technique, the jade stone would faintly blink in black. Using this testing tool that Garen created himself, he could identify the most suitable fighter to train his Black Water True Technique among the sea of participants.

One by one Garen pointed out the participants. The rest were brought away.

For the people that were brought away, although they failed this test, there was another one waiting for them. It was a determination test by using special methods to simulate the pain of during the infestation of the Green Vine Sphere. It started from mild to extreme, as it got closer to the actual level.

This was the achievement of the forgers that the Trejon's Household recruited recently.

If they couldn't even pass this test, they only could become the lowest level sentry in Blackfire Palace. Although the Blackfire Palace's sentry had benefits far above other forces, but it was nothing compared to the Blackfire guard, one rank higher, and the core disciples.

As the participants went up and down one by one, Garen only selected five people out of seven or eight crowds. These five people made the jade stone blink in black for the longest period of time. The test ended when there was no longer anyone to bring up.

Garen furrowed his brows and looked at the five men before him. There were three females or two males. One of the females was already over forty years of age while the rest were still very young, not more than twenty three. Two of them were dressed as nobles.

Five of them stood at the furthest end of the court. They were already considered core disciples of Blackfire Court. Garen would personally take them as disciples. Although they were still standing, many seated representatives gave them gazes of admiration.

"Bring in the top three!!"

The final moment had arrived. The three strongest men from the auditions would definitely be discipled by Garen. To be able to stand out among the sea of paricipants, their abilities were unimaginable.

Very quickly, three middle aged people with outstanding auras walked into the court. There were two males and a female. All of them looked around thirty forty years of age.

At they entered the court, Garen instantly let out a smile.

"Indeed…." It was exactly as he had expected.

The three of them were Master-level elites!

If they were placed in the Martial Arts World, they would at least be at fighter level. The fighters of Totem World were different from the Martial Arts World. They did not have any aura, nor would they use their own essence to suppress the enemy's abilities.

They chose a different path - heightened self-condensation.

They kept all their essence in their body, sealed. It was like a living sealed can, trying to prevent essence from leaking out. The purpose was to increase lifespan and strengthen the body. This caused Garen to think of one of the highest realms of Earth's martial arts, Secure Golden Body.

As the three people walked in, they gave off an extraordinary feeling. They had strong temperaments, causing people to fix their eyes on them.

People like that stood out among the crowd. They were clearly visible, like oil on water.

The three master-levels stayed solemn. As they stood in the court, there was a certain pride and grace in them.

"Good!" Garen slapped the armrest. The smile on his face intensified.

The three of them had trained their essence in their body to a terrifying level. The firmness of their body was at an unimaginable level, as if they were evolved beings.

If they were placed in the Martial Arts World, the three of them should at least be at peak fighter level.

The three of them wore the issued black Chinese robes. They bowed towards Garen and the surrounding people.

"Are the three of you willing to join me? Label me your master?" Garen was, in fact, young, but as he spoke, others could see that he had strong momentum on his side.

No one in the crowd thought it was awkward as if it was natural.

"I, Bale, am willing!" The first man finally couldn't control his joy and quickly answered.

The remaining two had equally strong reactions. Uncontrollable joy could be seen on their faces.

"I, Kamar, am willing!" The girl answered loudly.

"Saloma greets the master!" The last one bowed to the ground. He was shaking as tears came out uncontrollably from his eyes.

He looked simple, and evidently was from a peasant background. He thought about something at the moment and acted so intensely.

In fact, the three of them as the top three were the first to touch the big jade stone. But the jade stone's reaction was incredibly weak.

They initially thought they had lost all hope.

The audition was just the first stage. If they couldn't pass the second stage, all hope would be gone.

They never thought as they were brought up to the court, Garen would directly take them as disciples.

Chapter 457: Elder 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Bring the rings!"

The herald on the side shouted.

Three beautiful ladies had long been prepared. They brought up three silver plates in their white dresses.

In the middle of the plates were three small, pitch-black rings. A simple pattern resembling the Nine-Headed Hydra was carved on each of the rings.

The emblem of Blackfire Palace was instantly displayed on the court. This allowed the crowd to gauge Garen's value towards the three people.

The three masters took the rings and placed them on different fingers on their respective hands.

The servants then brought the three of them down, and next was the group that was just selected. They went up to receive the rings. This time, they were black-red rings to signify a lower level than the pure black rings.

This not only signified the difference in benefits and status, but also represented the different levels of teachings that would be bestowed upon them.

Lastly, the people that passed the third determination test were brought up. Dark red rings were given, representing their third-ranked status.

Almost everyone in the kingdom knew that Garen had seized control of the largest royal treasury, then equally divided the resources with the Silver Palace. He also controlled large amounts of land in the palace, even the eldest princess and the four princes didn't dare to return to the palace in order to avoid conflict.

Moreover, for the two Grand Dukes, one of them had a good relationship with Garen; while the other one would not start a conflict with Garen over some wealth. Although at first glance, they did not obtain the royal treasury, but they obtained a more secretive royal warehouse.

Both parties had an understanding. It could be considered as the both of them taking what they needed.

The candidates at the determination test were different from the first two batches.

They were treated significantly worse, except those that had fully passed the test. Those that endured more than half would be given a pass as well, but they had to pay a significant fee every year.

The meaning behind this measure was that only those with top talent and determination would qualify to be trained by the Blackfire Palace. Those with slightly lower talent and determination had to pay a price to obtain what they desired.

It was equivalent to school fees.

Garen wasn't unaware that other forces would definitely send people to try to learn his techniques, or they might even have other motives.

However, that did not matter to him.

After his contest with Ivycius, he realized that there were many fourth form totem users with martial arts in this world, but only a few could enter the fifth form.

Martial arts was only one of the criterias to enter fifth form, but it wasn't the full requirement.

To reach fifth form, he initially had no clue as well, but after fusing with the first head of the Nine-Headed Hydra, he finally had some rough idea.

Fifth form was combining the totem and totem user into one. The ultimate totem would be absorbed by the totem user using martial arts to completely fuse both of them, reaching the goal of the evolution of life.

In simple terms, totem users and luminarists were both ways to fuse external forces into the body to achieve evolution.

The trained totem would grow, step by step, to drive the evolution of the body, before finally arriving at a strange new level. This path was far deeper than mere martial arts development. It has even suppressed the path of science.

In other words, the development of totem was a science.

There are many types of martial arts and totems, and even more types of human bodies, each had differing talents.

Martial arts, the totem, and the body. These three must reach an unprecedented alignment to undergo the ultimate fusion.

In other words, if the martial art wasn't suitable, fusion was out of the question. Similarly with an incompatible totem. If the body had some issues, then that would be even more unthinkable.

If there was an issue with any of the three, form 5 was out of the question.

Garen could now understand better the thought process of the peak fourth form masters who were about to enter fifth form.

The period before leveling up was the most important period. If it's long, it could take years, and the shortest would even be a few months.

In this period of time, one had to meditate to continuously adjust the state of the heart, body and totem. Then, using the most suitable form of martial arts to fuse. He cannot be disrupted nor severely injured.

Any problems out of the three would result in wasted efforts. Once one was disrupted and then resumed, it would take multitudes more effort and time.

A compatible totem, suitable martial arts and fitting state of the body. None of the three could be lacking.

Even if the martial arts was given, it wouldn't create a scene among fourth and fifth form elites. Only a compatible martial art would suffice.

Ivycius took more than a hundred years before he completely understood the relationship between the three. It wasn't until his battle with Garen that he was enlightened. Only after that could he develop the perfect sword skills that he was lacking, fulfilling the condition of the most compatible martial art.

It might partly be because of his perfectionist behavior, or his deformed feelings towards his totem, but to be able to make him stay at this level for more than a hundred years naturally wasn't a joke.

From the beginning of time, fourth form totem users have had various unique abilities. There were techniques to lengthen the lifespan of men. However, the main reason so many fourth form totem users have perished throughout history was due to the inability to regulate their body to perfect compatibility, failing to reach the level of the three becoming one. This level required large amounts of time. Most of them tried to quiet down and regulate the body, but countless have died in the process. Only a handful have successfully broken through.

Too many people were stuck at this level. It wasn't the lack of martial arts and totems, but the process of regulating their body. It was, in fact, a state of the mind and cannot be forced using resources. Breakthrough also could not be achieved by talent alone. It needed experience, perception and seizing of the opportunity when it came by.

Improving the state of mind was the biggest stumbling block to entering fifth form.

Both Garen and Ivycius had entered this final stage.

As the Nine-Headed Hydra and White Rose were the totems most suited for them respectively, they've passed this test.

Garen had mastered many different martial arts. After some mild tweaking, he combined the essence of his martial arts into one, inventing the Black Water True Technique that suited him the most.

Fortunately, his martial arts was on the level of the King of the Century. It naturally gave him a huge advantage in regulating his body. His control and regulation of his body far surpassed other totem users.

Hence, Garen had in fact already fulfilled the two hardest items - body regulation and the most suitable martial arts.

Unfortunately, as God Cloud has said, his biggest limitation was his totem.

The Nine-Headed Hydra did not have sufficient potential. After all, it wasn't from a perfect genetic bloodline. It was evolved from the imperfect gene of the Dual-Headed Salamander. Its congenital deficiency became a key restriction for him to progress.

God Cloud was not just saying it for fun.

He calculated that after completely fusing with the Nine-Headed Hydra, he should be able to barely reach lower fifth form. However to progress further would be incredibly difficult. Even with his strong batting ability, the furthest he could go was being able to compare with a peak fifth form.

However in the eyes of the old men who had secluded themselves from the world, to enter fifth form was already the pinnacle of achievement. It was sufficient to bear the top missions of the Three Departments.

Garen refocused and gazed at the middle of the court below. The last batch of self-paid disciples was led down. Today's ceremony would soon come to a close.

"Alright. Since there are so many friends who came and supported me today, I have another major announcement."

Garen suddenly spoke loudly.

The crowd that was about to leave stopped instantly. They had no clue as to what Garen planned to announce.

Some of the people below started talking among themselves, but the most of them looked focus and fixated their gaze on Garen.

Garen nodded in satisfaction.

"I invented the Black Water True Technique. The original name of Blackfire Palace is no longer suitable. With so many friends here today, I announce that from today onwards, the Blackfire Palace will officially change its name!"

He paused for a moment.

"To Black Swamp Palace."

As the Nine-Headed Hydra was originally the king of the swamp, changing to "Swamp" was suitable indeed. Moreover, for the disciples who were trained in Black Water True Technique, due to the nature of the martial art, they would definitely choose totems with water attributes. Due to this fact, "swamp" was also very suitable.

With his own forces, Garen no longer had to do everything himself. He could even ensure the safety and benefits of his own family and also gather more information and resources easily. It would also be very beneficial for his future purpose.

"Black Swamp Palace?"

"The name is simple enough."

"The Lord had originally not used a fire attribute totem. Naturally, changing the name is the normal thing to do."

The crowd below echoed their approval.

Garen smiled then diverted his gaze towards the three tower lords on his left.

"Of course, this is not the major announcement. The major announcement is, the three Lords from the Snowy Mountain's Seven Night Tower in the North will officially become honorary elders of my Black Swamp Palace under my invitation. They will be subordinate to only me."

Honorary elders. This role was not unexpected.

Traveling thousands of miles to Kovitan and facing dangers and troubles throughout the journey, naturally it would not have been just for a simple celebration.

Only a minority of the people had not expected it, and let out surprised expressions.

Among the three Lords, the strongest, Second Lord Blizzard, stood up.

"To be invited by Lord Garen to this historical nation Kovitan and becoming an honorary elder of the Black Swamp Palace, is a great honor to me." He bowed slightly to show respect.

"You're welcome, Lord Blizzard." Garen nodded.

The other two tower lords also rose to their feet for some kind words.

"Hahahaha!"

Suddenly, a loud, fierce laugh came from outside of the palace.

"I heard the Nine-Headed Hydra Garen has extraordinary strength. I traveled over a thousand miles for this challenge. I'm sure the Lord will not disappoint me?"

The voice was terrifying. It shook the whole ground, numbing the soles of the crowd.

At the same time, all heads turned towards Garen.

Since Garen gained fame, this was the first time a strong opponent had come to challenge him. Each famous strong master would have experienced countless challenges before finally reaching the peak.

Garen gained fame in a short time. Due to his elusiveness and the continuous major incidents recently, this had not happened for a while.

Until now, he permanently resided in the kingdom. He had even started a clan and controlled an organization like the Black Swamp Palace. This gave people an opportunity.

Riding on another elite to gain fame was the fastest path to fame. Some of the elites had been training for multiple years. After coming out of training, they were eager to prove themselves to set up a foundation for their future generations. Naturally, they relied on their strength to find the fastest path.

Garen sat on the throne while both of his eyes were almost closed, as if he did not hear any sound.

It was the Angel of the Night on his left who slowly stood up and let out a clear laugh.

"It just so happens my Polar Flame is still lacking two major drugs. I'm really borrowing the master's fortune." Before she finished speaking, the figure on the Angel of the Night's seat slowly dissipated. She had already left as she was speaking, leaving a blur on the seat.

She was incredibly quick as even Garen and Ivycius did not notice.

Suddenly, a loud wave of thunder came from the sky outside the palace. Within the thunder was a seductive laugh. The clear ringing of bells came directly into the heart of the crowd. It was like a lover's grudge, causing the people around to itch.

"Who are you!!!??? The person I want to challenge is the Nine-Headed Hydra...ahhh!!!" The man's voice came to a sudden halt.

In an instant, a white blur of lightning shot into the court onto a seat on the left of the throne. It was the Angel of the Night, who had just left.

In her right hand, between her five sharp fingers was a bloody heart which was still beating.

On the seats below, some of the ladies let out faint cries. Most of the men turned pale. Within a few breaths, this lady tore out the heart of a strong totem user.

A murderous act like this was shocking for someone as beautiful as the Angel of the Night. Her white skin and the red blood formed a clear contrast.

The Angel of the Night laughed as she passed the heart in her hand to her disciple, then sat down. Her hand was not stained with blood at all.

Chapter 458: Elder 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Good going, Angel." Garen finally spoke. "To finish a Form Four fighter within five breaths, your reputation does not deceive."

"You are too kind, Palace Master." The Angel laughed lightly. The three of them were the elders Garen had spent a fortune to invite here, if they didn't show off some of their power, how could they earn everyone's obedience.

In an area with so many powerful fighters such as the Central Region, both sides survived side-by-side, fighting for benefits. They showed their power, which was also the Black Swamp Palace's power. To shock everyone present.

Garen understood that too, so he purposely asked the new arrivals to show their power.

His own battle achievements were right there, so the large man here to challenge him definitely wasn't here to kill him, probably only planning to retreat in one piece, and that would be enough to make his reputation. After all, Garen was currently one of Kovitan's four heads, his position was not to be underestimated.

This man had definitely investigated everything beforehand, and had prepared defenses specifically to protect against Garen's powers before he came for this battle.

But he didn't think he would meet the Angel of the Night who had mysterious powers. It was extremely rare for totems from the Northern Region to show up in the Central Region, and whilst both sides were unaware of each other, his Totem Light was destroyed as soon as they met, and his heart dug out.

As expected, the expressions of all the guests and witnesses below changed drastically.

Before this, they never had a clear impression of Garen's power, but now after seeing the Angel of the Night kill a Form Four fighter of the same level with her bare hands, and still be so respectful to Garen, they finally understood how terrifying Garen was.

"Come! Bring out the Elder Ring!"

Garen ordered directly.

Three young girls came up timidly, and presented the three Tower Lords with their Elder Rings, black with a bit of silver in the center.

Just as the three of them were about to pick up the rings.

"Wait!"

Another voice spoke up,

The one who spoke was none other than Ivycius, who sat alone on the right side.

Seeing the three of them opposite him glaring at him, Ivycius' expression remained unchanged.

"I just happened to have invited two of my best friends here. I myself am also interested in becoming a Black Swamp Palace elder, which also makes three of us, so may I know if Palace Master Garen is willing to accept us? Then all of us can be elders at the same time, wouldn't that be better?"

Garen smiled slightly. This was the process they had planned way in advance, so he wasn't surprised in the slightest.

"If the Silver Palace Master is willing to join, with our relationship, is there anything else that needs to be said?"

Ivycius nodded. His right hand gripped the sword hilt lightly.

Clang!!

Amidst gasps of surprise.

A rush of pure snow white shot out of nowhere, forming a white bridge of light as it flew out of the hall, shooting into the sky.

From the door of the Black Swamp Palace's main hall, a white bridge of light several meters wide shot straight into the sky. Forming a straight road several thousand meters long.

Whoosh-whoosh!!

Two flashes of black lightning descended, falling onto the surface of the shadow, instantly becoming two black-robed figures, a man and a woman.

The two of them steadied their footing slightly, and walked down the white sword-light bridge, but strangely, each of the steps the two of them took could cover more than ten meters of distance at once.

"Island Master Wukang, Island Master Skyharp(1), it's been a while." Ivycius stood, his usually ice-cold face actually smiling with some warmth.

The two on the sword bridge entered the palace hall quickly, and only then could everyone see their faces.

The man was clean-shaven, with one of his ears unnaturally large and fart, wearing a huge circlet of pearls that had more than ten large white pearls through it. His figure-fitting black silk robes did nothing to hide his firm and supple muscles.

Hearing Ivycius' voice, he chuckled.

"Little Vivi, after all these years, you still look so girly."

The crowd had just woken up from the awe from the moment, and upon hearing those words, some people nearly laughed out loud, hurriedly clapping their hands to their mouths out of fright.

Ivycius' expression didn't change, as though he hadn't heard that at all.

The other woman had plain features and dark skin, staring at Ivycius resentfully as soon as she got off the bridge.

"Vivi, for all these years, how could you be so cruel as to not visit me at all?" Her voice was unnaturally melodious, like the song of a kingfisher, clear and sweet, completely untainted.

A woman with a face like that made a huge contrast with Ivycius' handsome features, but to everyone's surprise, a hint of guilt flashed past Ivycius' eyes.

"I have let you down."

"The two of you, please sit." Garen hurriedly spoke up, so that the two old lovers wouldn't ruin the whole atmosphere with their exchange of gazes.

The two island masters bowed towards Garen slightly.

"Well met, Palace Master Garen."

Led by the maidservant, they walked to the seats beneath Ivycius and prepared to sit.

"Wait!"

This was the third interruption today.

But this time, nobody was surprised.

The one who had spoken was the Second Lord of Seven Night Tower, Blizzard, dissatisfaction flashing in his eyes.

"If it was the Silver Palace Master, the White Rose Sword Sage becoming an honorary elder, we have no opinion. The White Rose Sword Sage's abilities were trained through true battle since many years ago, we have heard of him even far away in the Northern Region." His Kovitan language was unnaturally fluent, "But has anyone heard of the two so-called island masters?"

The female disciple behind him instantly laughed lightly on cue.

"Teacher, I heard that the East Sea's Seventy-two Islands were more or less destroyed by the destructive battle back then, and most of those islands are now deserted. These two island masters… aren't the only people on their respective islands, are they?"

"How could you say that? No matter what, they're still your seniors, you have no right to speak here. When we get back, go into the Tundra Cave for three days and repent!" Blizzard scolded her, but his expression didn't look unhappy in the slightest.

"Yes, that is my mistake." The female disciple acted upset, lowering her head and apologizing.

The man with the large ear chuckled coldly, and turned around to look at Blizzard.

"The Northern Region's Seven Night Tower? You guys aren't showing off in the Northern Region, and came instead to the Central Region, don't slip up and get knocked off now, that would be bad." He laughed again coldly, "As for the situation on my Wukang Island, it's not up to you to worry. No matter how rundown, I can still call out a couple hundred Sea Dragoons."(2)

As soon as he said that, the contempt of Blizzard's face receded somewhat. Other people might not know what Sea Dragoons are, but they had interacted with the East Sea before, so they knew perfectly well.

On the seas, Sea Dragoons were a title only Spiritualized totem users could ascend to. They had true top-level power. Unlike their home in the extreme cold, the East Sea islands had ample produce, the supplies from the sea allowing those on the islands to live in relative surety. Perhaps due to the geography there, the place produced many totem users, but their flaw was that they had too few peak-level fighters, and Form Fout was their highest. Form Five required the steadiness of both heart and body, and was a level that was extremely hard to reach without a background of deep history and culture.

"Looks like they were limited to Form Four and couldn't advance as well, so they ran here to the Central Region looking for a chance." The Angel of the Night communicated quietly with the Spellmaster Anjiad.

"I have never really heard of Wukang Island, but Skyharp Island is one of the large islands among the seventy-two, with decent overall power, but I didn't think they would have such a young island master." Spellmaster nodded.

"Do you want to go or shall I?" Angel of the Night asked directly.

Spellmaster chuckled, and didn't continue, just giving the Second Tower Lord's direction a glance.

Angel of the Night harrumphed, didn't say anything more.

"Whether you're strong or not isn't something you just say. Palace Master Garen's honorary elders are not a position just anyone can take." Blizzard said word by word, his gaze on Wukang growing sharper.

"I seem to know you." Next to him, Skyharp suddenly turned her head, staring at Blizzard hard. "More than thirty years ago, in the battle to obtain the Heart of the Snow Demon, weren't you the Blizzard that my father grievously injured with one palm hit?"

Blizzard immediately looked unhappy, that battle was the deepest scar of his life, and he still had that clear red palm print on the center of his chest right now, he couldn't dispel it no matter what he tried.

He had that old wound reopened to his face, and he was never a generous person to start with.

The killing intent flashed in his eyes, and countless pitch-black spots appeared on his skin, crowded and dense like that of a leopard's spots, instantly covering his entire body.

The left side of his face abruptly began to fade, while half a white owl's head appeared instead.

Boom!!

Blizzard shot out a palm, a pillar of black air spinning as it rushed towards Skyharp opposite him.

As expected, he was at the peak of Form Four, where he was about to merge with his totem. This sort of power could only be controlled by a totem user at the borderline, just like Garen right now, every move carrying the power of nearly one dragon, without him needing to waste totem power to activate the totem. Such terrifying power was completely his own, as long as he had enough stamina, he could use it for several days and nights without any problem.

The black pillar spun and shot, morphing into a black disc that spun and sliced in mid-air, whooshing as it flew towards Skyharp.

Island Master Skyharp's expression grew serious.

She waved her right hand, and a beam of blue light shot out of her sleeves, meeting the black disc head-on.

In an instant, the blue light came into direct contact with the black disc.

Wooo!!!

A piercing vibrating sound rose in the large hall.

The black disc and the blue light froze in mid-air, neither giving way as they were suspended in mid-air.

The black air and the blue light that had been shot out sprayed everywhere, and then returned back to the black disc and blue light, without harming their surroundings in any way.

The whole hall was dyed black and blue.

After a short while of tug-of-war, the black disc began to press the blue light down slowly.

Psst!

Just then, a white thread shot through between the two of them, piercing right through the center of the black disc and the blue light, cutting them apart like a knife.

The white thread nailed itself into the palace wall with a thud, and was revealed to be a clean white rose. There were even some drops of crystal dew dripping off of it.

"Hmph!" Blizzard snorted coldly, and called back the black disc. He glanced at Ivycius.

Skyharp also called the blue light back into her sleeve. There was a slight sheen of sweat on her forehead, however, proving that just now hadn't been easy for her.

"Both of you are my esteemed guests, so please don't mention the previous generation's conflicts, for my sake, from now on we're all part of the same camp, so we should support and help each other." Garen finally spoke.

Both sides were powerful fighters that his Black Swamp Palace used their funds to support, so naturally he wouldn't want them to fight each other before he even had a chance to use them.

"You're right, Palace Master." Blizzard nodded, and used that excuse to end the conflict. Ivycius' power was obviously slightly over Form Four, he didn't say anything, but inside he was growing more and more wary of him.

Skyharp also smiled at Garen apologetically.

"Bring out the Elder Rings!"

Garen sat on the master seat, watching a few girls come up and give away three similar silver-dotted rings.

The six peak-level fighters all put them on.

In that moment, everyone underneath the large hall hurriedly clapped to support them, their applause thundering.

While Veska was grievously hurt and healing, Garen's power was boosted by this and continued growing.

The immense value of the Royal Treasury was enough to sponsor these fighters for a hundred years.

And that was setting aside the underground hall in the Royal District, and there were still some hidden department secrets. Garen himself wasn't the type to spend without earning.

With the help of these six fighters at the same level as him, right now, even if God Cloud came again, Garen was confident he could make sure God Cloud wouldn't able to leave!

Right now he was buying time, to merge the totem himself and achieve a new level of power, he needed time. In this period of time, he must not have any weaknesses, must not get injured, and his emotions cannot get too extreme. Until this period was over, and he had utterly merged with the Nine-Headed Dragon. Meanwhile, he naturally needed enough power to protect himself.

Translator's notes:

空琴岛主, the 空 could mean 'sky' or 'empty'.

海龙师, lit. Sea Dragon Master / User, see what I did there?

Chapter 459: Development 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Deep in the Black Swamp Palace after it was renamed, on a newly created training arena.

The family’s Guard Captains, Maxilan and Edney stood at the sides, and there were eight newly-recruited disciples standing in the middle. They all wore identical extravagant black fighting clothes, so be it the men or women, they all looked extremely handsome and sharp.

Garen stood in front of them, his hands behind his back, his gaze almost solid as it swept across the many disciples.

He said nothing at all, and had been standing like that for a long time already, his gaze just kept staring at these newly-recruited disciples.

Rather than calling them his disciples, they were more like the experimental subjects he had chosen for his invented exercises. He needed practical applications to test whether or not the Black Water True Technique could truly allow normal people to overcome their limits, and different people had different bodies, so naturally the effects of their training would be different as well. This was also in preparation for that thing that might happen in the future.

The three average Masters stood at the very front, and made no sound whatsoever, in complete contrast to the impatience on some of the others’ faces. To be able to train themselves until the Master-level among the normal humans, they would naturally have exceptional patience.

The sunlight of dawn fell lightly on everyone there, reflecting a black-ish silk light.

Garen finally spoke.

"Other than myself, nobody has ever learned my own Black Water True Technique, so even I don’t know what will happen when I teach it you all." He told them frankly that this was an experiment.

"There’s still time now if you want to turn back."

The three masters, two men and one woman, were the three Garen favored the most, while the disciples behind them were a level behind, who didn’t get such a high ranking, they were just particularly suited to the Black Water True Technique.

As for these second-level disciples, there were more women than men, three to two.

Upon hearing Garen’s words, nobody reacted much, since they had defeated the odds to get here, of course they would have made all the mental preparations.

"Great, now I’ll teach you the first level. After you’ve achieved that, then come to me for the second level." Garen didn’t say any more, and passed down the first level of the Black Water True Technique secret technique directly.

After structuring the Black Water True Technique, there were four levels among the normal people, and then was the critical point, once they broke through that, it would be a new world for them, enabling them to activate totem power.

Garen explained each of the thousand words regarding the first level, word by word.

And then came the time to answer everyone’s questions.

The time ticked by.

The three Masters didn’t have many questions, they had long since obtained utter control over their own bodies, even though the first level of the Black Water True Technique didn’t suit them particularly well, they still understood it in no time.

He glanced at the three Masters, satisfied.

"From today onwards, there will be an internal competition every week, and the top three would get certain rewards, these three would be the Black Swamp Palace’s strongest disciples, if you can maintain your position consistently, your reward will be steadily increased. There will be unexpected surprises in store."

Garen said with a smile.

After the large-scale recruitment drive just yesterday, the influx of people into the Black Swamp Palace was extraordinary.

The small families and merchants who wanted to kiss up to him provided vast supplies and riches, just the money from the external self-sponsored disciples had reached a terrifying figure of several tens of thousands of golden rumbs, and this wasn’t a one-time-only profit either, but their annual study fees. There were other expenses too, like accommodation fees and such.

These disciples stayed inside the Palace District, and every day these eight disciples would set up a platform, waiting for Garen to teach them the Black Water True Technique.

This was Garen especially letting his disciples form their own forces, each of them would create their own groups of interest, and as it went down, those would band into more groups. This way, the influence of the Black Swamp Palace would achieve extreme heights.

As for whether or not the spies from the other forces would learn his technique, Garen was not worried in the slightest.

Because the Black Water True Technique had a special characteristic, which was that he had invented it completely based on his own body, and it was the secret technique exercise that suited him best, so nobody could beat him at it.

The Form Five fighters from the other powers all had special techniques that suited them, it just wasn’t convenient for them to spread it.

The only key difference between the Black Water True Technique and their secret techniques was that little bit of crucial technique required to transcend limits

This method was so that they could only transcend under Garen’s own hand, and it was only theoretical too, without any practical precedent.

With his micro-control ability as the King of the Century, he needed to touch that most crucial point, and this was basically unreplicable. Because there wasn’t another King of the Century here in this world.

Of course, maybe many, many years from now, someone would be able to discover the mysteries of it, but understanding its mysteries did not equal to being able to practice it. Because that was a hand technique from another world, and wasn’t something that could be overcome with just imagination, it still required some immersion in another world’s Secret Technique system as well as their style and influence.

In order to prevent the secret exercises leaking out, Garen had used all sorts of methods.

Other than this crucial hand he kept to himself, he also embedded all sorts of smokescreens and obstructions into the exercises. By putting in some useless hand techniques and training steps, he made it seem like a half-lie, half-truth.

And the Black Water True Technique was divided into two versions, one simple version that was only one of the moves from his Northern Capturing Hand plus a little bit of content from the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, this simple version couldn’t activate totem power, and its function was to allow the learner to be more suited to the Black Swamp Armor, so they can get used to the Green Vine Sphere’s power.

Garen divided his Ten Thousand Mammoths Battle Skills into individual moves, and each move was made into a simplified version as well, merged with the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, to form the four Palace Districts, North, South, East and West.

The four Districts trained in different types of the Ten Thousand Mammoths Battle Skills, and once one had learned them all, the result would be a totem user’s version, the Four Directions Battle Skills.

East King Hand, West Phoenix Fist, Southern Double Fist, Northern Capturing Hand.

Garen himself was quite curious, he didn’t know how strong these simplified versions of his own martial arts essence would be once they were totemized.

He called the simplified versions the Four Direction Ten Thousand Mammoths, and he had listed out a Four Directions Sky Warrior for each district, in a throwback to his title from the Secret Technique World.

The Four Directions Sky Warriors had the same status as core disciples, or even higher, as they had to right to mobilize a certain proportion of the Black Swamp Palace’s external powers, which basically meant he had gathered the influence of the external self-sponsored disciples and divided it among the four of them.

This was a very formidable power, because as more people swore allegiance to the Black Swamp Palace, the more totem users and forgers they had. After the collapse of the war, many totem users and forgers ran back to the Kingdom, and practically all the large powers were madly absorbing manpower right now.

The position of the Four Directions Sky Warriors came from battle, the four districts fought their own internal competitions, and the strongest one had the right to become a Sky Warrior, which would earn them Garen’s personal bestowal of the Black Swamp Palace’s four strongest suits of Black Swamp Armor.

That was the elite armor belonging to the four strongest guards.

This was the external side.

As for the core disciples, it would depend on what level they could reach.

If they were suitable, Garen would personally choose a totem from the Royal Treasury and bestow it upon them.

There were many totems in the Royal Treasury, even the rare and precious ones numbered up to at least several hundred. As for the regular totems, now that Garen had more and more forgers under his own wing, it wouldn’t be too hard just to create them himself.

They could also choose the totems they liked, or ask the Black Swamp Palace’s forgers to customize one for them.

After teaching the first level of the Black Water True Technique, Garen discussed the family’s situation with Maxilan and Edney for a bit, and at the same time he advised them on some of their Black Water True Technique before he left the plaza, heading for the Palace District’s Technique Hall.

On the way, he saw that many of the destroyed areas within the entire Palace District had been fixed, and in some of the places the forgers were concentrated on setting up Alarm Tactic Formations, while several teams of patrolling Black Swamp Guards occasionally wove their way through the surroundings, their footsteps resonating in unison.

When he walked past the Garden District, from a distance, Garen saw Kid talking to a little girl.

The little girl was trying hard to practice the West Phoenix Fist’s basic moves, her black hair tied into a short ponytail, her little face full of determination as she ignored Kid’s jokes and laughter beside her.

Kid was sprawled on a swing, and would occasionally say something, as though teasing the little girl.

Garen was just slightly surprised that he had accepted such a young self-sponsored student, and then he walked away directly.

That girl was no more than ten years old, give or take, but she seemed surprisingly determined. Perhaps she was a promising talent, but right now Garen had more than his fair share of promising talents, so he wasn’t too bothered.

Nobody could fight him for genius disciples with a talent for secret techniques in this world.

Going past the Garden District, he went past a few areas of the Plaza District, which had the sounds of training coming from them.

Soon enough, he went into a small garden forest, and a white palace hall deep inside appeared in front of him instantly.

The palace hall was triangular in shape, like a pyramid, and had small round entrances on all four sides. The whole palace was divided into three floors, the lowest floor being the largest, a full fifty or sixty meters wide.

There were Silver Palace Guards and Black Swamp Guards standing guard at the entrances. Upon seeing Garen approaching, the guards all lowered their heads and bowed.

A young pretty girl walked out quickly from the small palace hall, it was Lala.

Her long red-brown hair was tied into a stupa-like shape at the side of her head, and she wore a black dress, a dark-red waist belt tied around her waist, the black-red colors creating a sharp contrast with her clear white skin.

"Palace Master." Lala had also changed the way she addressed him, lowering her head slightly at Garen.

"How’s the situation?" Garen walked into the small palace hall, and asked casually.

"We’ve already recruited eighteen forgers, each of them at least Form Two. There are also two Form Three ones, they were professors from the destroyed Calm Bay City." Lala replied, following behind him.

Inside, the first floor was completely empty, all the forgers were doing their research on the upper floors, and they all lived nearby as well.

The construction here wasn’t completely done yet, and some materials had yet to arrive either.

"Are there no Spiritualized Masters here?" Garen asked mildly, sweeping his gaze over the people leaving and entering the first floor’s main corridor.

A forger was only a Master after achieving Spiritualization, it was much harder for them to level up as opposed to totem users, and most of their time was spent on their research.

"We did invite some, but putting aside the other two, there was one Master who had agreed at first, but some reason changed tack again." Lala was frowning slightly too.

Without a Master-level forger in charge, it would be very hard to customize and create high-level totems, and they wouldn’t be able to create many excellent totems either. It was very detrimental to the development of the Black Swamp Palace as a whole.

"Changed tack?" Garen narrowed his eyes. "Investigate the reason, if there was some interference, finish them off."

"I suspect it’s…"

"Don’t need to tell me the reason, my Black Swamp Palace does not fear any power." Garen interrupted her. "Since they have intercepted, they should be ready to face our wrath. If you don’t have enough manpower you can mobilize twenty Black Swamp Guards, if that’s still enough then go apply from the Silver Palace, he won’t refuse you."

"If a high-level totem user appears…"

"It just so happens that the Elder Angel is still missing some medicines and main ingredients, if they make a move just once, they’ll reap plenty of rewards." Garen replied, walking to the door to a sealed room on the left.

"While I’m not around, you settle any problems on your own, if there’s a problem you can’t settle, then go ask the elders, if even the elders can’t handle it, then only do you come to me."

"Understood." Lala replied crisply now, after following Garen for so long, she had long since gotten used to handling all sorts of matters."

Bam.

Garen pushed open the door and entered the sealed room.

The sealed room was utterly pitch black from top to bottom, there was a simple drawing of huge salamander dragon head carved into the center of the floor, its two blood-red eyes narrow, long and vicious, and they just happened to be the only source of light in this sealed room.

Garen closed the door, walked to the area in front of the dragon eyes, and sat down cross-legged.

In the darkness, soon enough, the three scarlet dots on his brow lit up slowly, emitting the same bloody red glow.

*****************

The Kingdom’s Cloud Light District

Hathaway stood in her own garden, pruning flower branches, ever since she came back from the hospital last time, the conference was held, and Garen became one of the four main heads, the whole long line of changes catching her off guard.

And her position now had also become somewhat in the air.

Recently the Black Fire Palace was renamed into the Black Swamp Palace, and recruited six peak-level elders at once, causing its power to skyrocket. It had become a power that the entire Kingdom feared terribly.

The other powers were feeling threatened as well, so they hurriedly looked for strong fighters to join them. As a result, the situation in the Kingdom now was that everyone was peacefully developing on their own.

The First Princess and the Fourth Prince were both developing themselves hastily, faced with the terrifying prospect of Garen and six elite fighters at the same level as him, they were all feeling that sense of danger.

It was just that all these were quite distant from Hathaway.

At first she had hoped that Garen would be able to make a name for himself, develop and strengthen the family, and now that he had reached this target, as a member of the Trejons family, even if only a side branch, she could still feel the attitudes of those around her changing. Everything seemed to be changing for the better.

Picking up the watering can, she sprayed the clean water onto the pruned bushes lightly.

The early morning sunlight scattered onto the flower bushes, causing the drops of water to reflect the crystal clear sunlight.

"Little Sofie~~ Are you home?" Sylvia started yelling again.

In the end she hadn’t left after all, and her family didn’t leave either, choosing instead to stay, mostly because of Garen’s influence from back then.

"Sylvia, are you done with today’s work as well?" Hathaway turned around to see Sylvia attempting to ambush her. The voice had seemed so distant just now, but she had suddenly run up so close to her in such a short time.

Chapter 460: Development 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"There you go again!" Hathaway glared at her mildly.

"I don’t have work today either, so I got the day off. That’s why I came to see you." Sylvia was all smiles.

"You sure are free." Hathaway shook her head.

"Where’s the little girl?" Sylvia looked left and right, but still didn’t see Dani.

"I don’t know either, recently she’s still been the same as ever, going out early and coming back late, playing like crazy." Hathaway’s gaze was slightly helpless.

"She’s still young, c’mon."

"But you sure are lucky now, with such an impressive cousin." Sylvia said enviously.

"What’s so lucky about that? My life still goes on the same every day." Hathaway smiled sweetly. Now she had achieved everything she wanted to, the family business was on Garen’s shoulders, and she didn’t have to worry about that at all. Her only aim now was to raise Dani properly.

The Trejons’ branch families had just come to visit her a few days ago, Garen was the Trejons family chief now, and these branches really wanted to return to the main family.

Speaking of which, these few branch families had been doing pretty well for themselves, and when Garen’s reputation hit rock-bottom before he actually achieved anything, they didn’t kick him while he was down, and instead they all reached out a helping hand, it was just that Garen didn’t respond to them back then.

All their invitations had been ignored.

Hathaway was mulling over when she should mention it to Garen, there were two people from the Silver Palace standing right outside her door, she could easily pass any messages to Garen through them.

Hearing Sylvia’s chattering voice next to her, she suddenly felt as though life was extremely peaceful. A calm taste of happiness began to spread in her heart.

******************

Three days later…

In the sealed room--

Garen abruptly opened his eyes, the red light in eyes shooting out far, leaving two streaks of red behind them.

The red strings stayed in the air for a few seconds, before slowly fading away.

On his brow, the scarlet dot on the furthest right was vaguely becoming slightly darker.

Raising his arms slightly, the red shadows of two salamander dragon heads appeared on each of his palms.

Roar…

The deep dragon’s roar reverberated slowly in the sealed room.

"The second dragon head."

Garen murmured, his gaze once more falling onto his attribute pane.

‘Black Water True Technique (Originally Myriad Water Jasper Technique): Sixth Level (six levels in total). Forcibly controls all liquids.

Poison Enhancement level two, Recovery Enhancement level two.’

"I knew there would be a change, at first five levels was the limit, but after merging in the second dragon head, it actually automatically reached the Derivation’s sixth level. The Poison Enhancement and Recovery Enhancement were both originally my abilities, it doesn’t really make a difference if they get stronger."

Garen frowned slightly, the Black Water True Technique was the technique he himself trained in, it was the true full version, and not the one he was teaching others. At first he had created and merged this secret technique, only he had used the simplified secret technique as the base, but he was surprised to find that it successfully merged with his own martial arts essence, forming this peak-level secret technique.

But now, after merging the second dragon head, the final result wasn’t what he had expected.

The Nine-Headed Demon Dragon had lost two dragon heads, both merged into him, but all he got in return were some not very efficient enhancement effects.

After absorbing the Nine Headed Dragon, his secret technique shouldn’t have been that weak.

He fell into deep thought.

He absorbed his totem in order to advance his secret technique, and then he meant to merge his totem and secret technique so that he could reach the peak of evolution.

Could it be that something was wrong with my secret technique?

But according to theory, there should never have been a problem.

"Since I’m already on this road, I don’t have to worry anymore, I might as well walk to the end and then see how it works." Garen settled his heart.

After that, it was time to go out and check how the forgers were doing with their research.

Right now, he was forging Obscuro’s crystal ball Derivator, he had quite a few on hand, all gained from the Silver Palace’s elite warriors’ recent raiding of Obscuro everywhere. But they were all Field-Level.

The forgers were trying to decipher the secret locks inside, but unfortunately, without a truly substantial researcher on board, their progress was minuscule.

If he could forge this thing, Garen’s potential point problem would be happily settled. Using the Derivator to control the Silver Totems, he could hunt monsters and totem users, obtaining large amounts of potential points. To Garen, that was an irresistible temptation.

Upon leaving the sealed room, the maid waiting on call outside hurriedly offered up some drinking water.

Garen drank some clean water, went to freshen up, hurriedly finished his meal, and then went to check on the progress of the forgers, but instead he saw an old geezer with white hair surrounded by a large crowd among the forgers’ experiment tables on the second floor, he seemed to be person-in-charge here, it was no longer the fatty from before.

The old man’s expression was solemn, and when he saw Garen arrive, he was stunned for a moment before he came up to greet Garen of his own accord.

"Palace Master Garen."

The others also wanted to bow and greet him, but Garen waved his hand and stopped them.

"Your work is more important, don’t mind me. I just want to ask a few questions, then I’ll leave." He said with a smile.

After the second floor gradually calmed down, the geezer finally led Garen to a sealed crystal greenhouse.

"Master Calingan, after sending people to invite you so many times, I finally managed to get you over here." Garen smiled.

"You exaggerate, Palace Master, I also meant to join the Black Swamp Palace, it was just that something came up on the way, so I was blacked, but the problem has been solved now." The old man, Calingan, waved his hand. "I know why you are here too." (1)

He walked into the middle of the greenhouse, and the floor there began to make a wailing sound, as three white cylindrical pillars rose from the ground in a spiral.

In the middle of the cylindrical pillar, there was a hollow crystal container, and three pitch-black crystal ball floated inside.

"This is the success of our forgery, thank goodness there was some residual information and progress left behind from the royal family, it’s just even so, the Crystal Derivator that we forged still lacked the core techniques. Even I can’t do anything about that. So our progress now is only at about eighty percent."

Calingan replied, frowning.

Garen, however, looked slightly happy. "Very good, not bad at all! As expected of a Master, before you came, Master Calingan, our forgery progress was not even at the halfway point, but now we’ve reached eighty percent in no time!"

"You flatter, Palace Master…" Calingan was slightly guilty, he had planned to really buck up and gloriously display his own worth and importance, but he hadn’t expected to fail at the very first step.

"This is not your fault." Garen shook his head. "At the center of the Crystal Derivator, there is a core made with a special mineral, the principles involved here are more complicated, and really hard to decipher in such a short time, there are principles involving resonance, and high-level transmission equations may not work here, you guys need to change your mindset. Perhaps it might help if you research the structure of the hideouts."

"Hideouts?"

"That’s right." Garen began to explain some of the information he knew to Calingan in detail. These were the Obscuro techniques and systems he had learned from Windling and Reylan.

He also had quite some expertise in this field, with the encouragement of his potential points, he could match what others took a decade or two to learn in one year, his natural capital was extremely considerable. He was a Master at all sorts of subjects.

The two of them discussed a bit in the greenhouse, and it was Calingan’s first time meeting such a knowledgeable research sponsor. This made him even more excited, and he was starting to feel as though coming here was, without a doubt, the wisest decision of his life.

A researcher’s biggest hope was to meet a boss who provided the funds but also knew the field, and not just an outsider who only wanted to see results.

Only then would the other party understand your research to the largest extent.

After the two of them exchanged some ideas, Garen noticed that it was getting slightly late, so he ate an employer’s meal together with the researchers while encouraging them to continue their research without worry, ensuring they had no psychological pressure. Only then did he slowly leave.

When he left the Technique Hall, the sky outside was already turning vaguely red. A warm breeze blew past, feeling all warm and cozy, and there was the crisp chirping of the sparrows in the surrounding trees. Some of the researchers’ families and children were taking strolls and resting nearby, some of them even leading pets like puppies and kittens.

On the way out of the garden forest, there were some elderly gathering together and playing chess, while others played with their little birds in cages. There were even two old geezers sparring energetically.

This was the biggest source of income for normal people Masters in the regular world, teaching the elderly to train their bodies and prolong their lives. Here, the power of martial arts seemed unbelievably weak.

Garen sighed inwardly, not saying anything, and many people around here didn’t recognize him at all either, thinking he was just another researcher’s family member.

When he left the garden forest, he saw Maxilan waiting outside. Once he saw Garen approach, Maxilan went up to him first.

"What’s the matter?"

"The First Princess’ side sent a message over, they’re inviting you to a banquet." Maxilan paused, and continued, "Her First Highness also sent a letter."

He handed Garen a red envelope that he had already prepared beforehand.

Garen accepted it, and saw the very high-class Totem Light seal on it, unless you knew the password order and method, there was no way you could open it safely, to prevent others from peeking at the contents.

Garen tore apart the envelope sealed by Totem Light directly.

On a piece of white paper inside, there was just one line of small elegant writing.

‘The thing you’re looking for, is here with me.’(1)

Garen snorted coldly. With a pinch of one hand, the letter paper instantly became powder, that flew and scattered with the wind.

"Looks like I really do need to make a trip there."

The First Princess had obviously already guessed his intention, the forgery of Caeserton should probably be in her hands.

Garen wouldn’t dare hope for the real Caeserton, after all it had already merged with the previous emperor’s will, and was activated now too, so the situation now would be that anybody without a royal bloodline couldn’t even think about controlling it.

And the next-level forgery would at least be an Ultimate Heirloom, if he could obtain this heirloom, then his abilities would rise by a huge leap. The Black Crow Formation pocket-watch from back then could already display Form Four power, and even that was a lower level Ultimate Heirloom forgery.

Now, a true Ultimate Heirloom would most probably achieve Form Five power.

Translator’s note:

Both instances use the respectful word for ‘you’.

Chapter 461: Obtained 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clang...

"The light of the world comes from far away, the light of the sun is like the moon, O Dream, when will you return to my heart… The sky is no longer blue, the clouds are like grey granite…"

The melody of a stage piano wafted over from the performer nearby.

Garen stood in front of the window, dressed in white casual clothes, playing with a pebble that looked like red jade in his hand.

This was the First Princess’ vacation palace, the room he was in had rows of black bookshelves, a soft medium-sized bed, and a short coffee table to greet guests. It felt like a bedroom, a study, and even more like a living room.

The room was very large, and there was a black stage piano with gold etchings at the empty space on the right, it was an instrument like a piano. The performer was a pretty, cute young blonde girl, her long curly hair falling over her shoulder, singing softly but emotionally.

Her singing reverberated through the room together with the sound of the piano, the volume was just right, not too loud nor too soft, as though someone was whispering by your ear gently, her voice reaching the very depths of your heart.

Garen leaned on the window, looking outside from within.

It was the third floor, and beneath him, there was a small open-air courtyard between the buildings, where several girls with nice bodies were fighting over the swings, their cheerful laughter reaching him continuously.

He had already been waiting here for some time, but the First Princess just happened to be bathing right now, so she couldn’t come for now.

After an unknown period of time, the red sunlight outside was already shining on the floor, slanting more and more.

Garen did not feel impatient at all, even the girl’s forehead began to sweat after she played for a while, so she got up, bowed slightly at Garen, and then left on her own.

After that, a girl in a white dress with a waist-belt walked in, she was holding a small violin, and after bowing respectfully at Garen, she began to perform without a word.

The pure music of the violin was like the soft chirping of insects, soft and gentle, sometimes there and sometimes not.

Psst!!!

All of a sudden, the sound of the violin explosively grew higher, giving the listener a feeling of panic, instantly hurried, it was a performance like a storm, the girl’s hand quickly sliding, trembling.

The sound of the violin was like a thunderstorm, the rain cascading down, until even Garen’s heart gave a little jolt, this change from gentle and soft to extreme explosiveness was too sudden, until even he was somewhat dazed and late to respond.

Just then, a pair of small hands covered his eyes from behind.

"Guess who?"

A woman’s voice, purposely suppressed, came from behind him, and at the same time two soft mounds pressed against his back lightly. The faint fragrance of a woman’s body entered Garen’s nostrils.

"Your Highness, stop playing."

Garen wasn’t surprised in the slightest, taking one step forward expressionlessly and then turning around.

As expected, the First Princess was behind him, dressed in a white-gold skintight dress, she pouted slightly, as though blaming Garen for not understanding the atmosphere.

She wore a skintight dress, perfectly showing off the curves of her chest and waist, while the hem of the skirt at the bottom was like that of a cheongsam, with a long slit all the way up to the roots of her thighs, so that all it took was a soft flip for everything to be revealed.

Garen didn’t want to get too close to her. The First Princess had used her own body to seduce and control too many strong fighters. Even though his body made him unafraid of regular poisons, and was even resistant to particularly powerful poisons, but it was still his basic principle to avoid whatever he could.

"Liv knows, I have no right to hope that I could get too close to you. But do you know, milord? In this deep palace, whenever I feel unbearably lonely, Liv will always think of you, Palace Master, you are the only man who truly has no desire towards Liv’s body." The First Princess walked up to the window with an expression of wistfulness, and looked down as well, but her gaze was slightly lost.

"You are the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon, so powerful that you are terrifying, you are immune to all poisons, and your reputation is enough to scare away countless villains. Could you still be afraid of a weak little woman like me? Why is it so hard for me to even get a little closer to you?" The First Princess’ eyes gradually filled with tears.

Garen’s expression was calm as he continued to play with that red jade pebble in his hand, his gaze staring straight at the First Princess, as though admiring a mild show.

A succubus like this would always say every line and make everyone think she was divulging her true thoughts to them, this sort of honesty mixed together with aggravation, as well as her naturally wonderful body, would be enough to ignite a certain desire in her listener. All together, it was the most intensely wonderful poisonous wine, with both temptation and danger.

Although Garen was confident that he wouldn’t be controlled by her, but he didn’t need to take a risk just for his own bodily impulses, that was not worth it at all. Especially after last time, when he just had a meal with the First Princess and was already drugged, this experience made him completely disinterested.

By then the sound of the violin had slowly grown softer as well, gentle and tender like a woman’s sighs, especially teasing for the imagination.

The tears in the First Princess’ eyes finally fell, her eyes reddened, and she took out a white handkerchief to wipe away her tears lightly.

"How unsightly of me."

"It’s fine." Garen said calmly, "To be honest, I envy those who can cry. Because I myself find it so hard to accomplish."

"True." The First Princess recovered some of her previous mischief. "Someone said that tears are the exclusive right of the weak, huh." She smiled slightly. Clapping her little hands, the performer immediately pulled back her violin bow, bowed once, turned around and left.

"Alright, all that aside, let us talk about the serious matters." The First Princess’ face finally grew serious.

She walked to the right of the piano, and sat down on a high stool, crossing her beautiful legs, putting one on top of the other, so the mysterious place between her legs peeped in and out of view.

"Oh my, after crying out loud, I sure feel a lot lighter~~" She threw her head back, and really stretched her body.

This pose could make any male with desires itch, ninety percent of men would probably give in and take advantage of when she couldn’t see them to peek at the scenery between her legs.

When others weren’t paying attention, people would always let go of their wariness, and reveal their basest selves.

Unfortunately, Garen sat calmly opposite her, one hand placed on the armrest and the other massaging his temple, as though he was meditating.

"Tell me, what are your conditions? I need to get Caeserton’s forgery." He stated his aim calmly, without any hiding.

The suggestive atmosphere in the room vanished without a trace.

The First Princess returned to her previous graceful sitting position, finally a hint of helplessness in her eyes.

"Fine, fine… Looks like in your eyes, I can’t even compare to a forgery…"

Seeing that Garen wasn’t moved in the slightest, she stopped beating around the bush.

"Caeserton’s forgery, we call it the Flash Screen." She arranged her thoughts, "First, let me tell you its pros and cons."

After clearing her throat, she said with a straight face.

"The Flash Screen can release a hemispherical invisible barrier in an instant, blocking all attacks with enemy intent. Be it Totem Light or regular material attacks. The defense level depends on the power of the user. It’s just that the screen can only last for a split second, about two seconds, and then it would disappear automatically. Although this screen only lasts for a short while, but…"

She paused.

"But, it has a very important ability. That is, it can form explosive crystals."

"Explosive crystals?" Garen touched his chin, there wasn’t such a function in the information he had about this forgery.

"That’s right, the explosive crystals are formed by absorbing the opponent’s Totem Light attack. Any attacks that go through the Flash Screen and don’t destroy the screen face-on, would have part of their Totem Light absorbed. When there is enough of this absorbed Totem Light, it will form a powerful explosive crystal. You can throw it as an explosive, it should be very powerful." The First Princess explained.

"Should be? You guys never tried it before?" Garen was slightly surprised.

"Naturally we did, but the Flash Screen that we activated could only block a Form Four attack at the most, any higher and it would fail." The First Princess said helplessly, "The Flash Screen may seem strong, and its effect seems great as well, so that it can attack and defend, but don’t forget the most important part."

"The most important part? Is it the energy source required?" Garen furrowed his brows slightly.

"That’s right… Grand Duke Benoc commented on this Heirloom before: its very powerful, but too bad it can’t be used." The First Princess sighed, "Otherwise why would I be willing to give it away?"

"Give it away?" This was the second time Garen got taken off guard, but he quickly recovered. "The energy source required is life energy, isn’t it?"

The First Princess nodded, "After a Form Two totem user tried to use it, all his life energy was sucked away."

"No wonder you want to give it to me." Garen understood. "Other than me, no one else would dare to use it. Alright, tell me, what conditions do you have?" He didn’t think that this succubus would give him a treasure for nothing.

The First Princess looked at Garen wistfully.

"Am I really such a calculative merchant of a woman to you?"

Garen was unmoved, and just stared at her calmly.

"Alright, alright…" The First Princess stood up, pressed one hand on her chest, and lightly pulled out a white-gold necklace out from between her breasts.

"This is the Flash Screen."

She pulled down the white-gold necklace, there was a lightning bolt-shaped pendant on the end of the necklace, its surface was a pale blue silver color, and there was a circle of tiny vine engravings around it.

"I only have one condition." She said softly, and suddenly stuffed the necklace back into her cleavage again. "If you want it, you reach your hand in here to take it."

The pendant sank into her cleavage in an instant, and disappeared immediately.

Garen was speechless. To think he would do something like this.

"Do you dare?" The First Princess snorted lightly, and stuck out her chest, her expression sardonic as she looked at Garen. "The great Black Swamp Palace Master would actually fear a normal weak girl, I plan to properly broadcast this fact, y’know."

Garen fell silent, stood up slowly. Walked up to the First Princess.

The other person raised her face mischievously, and looked at him with a challenge in her eyes.

Garen smiled slightly, reached out his right hand, and flicked his fingers.

Psst!

A gust of invisible air shot out, and hit the area between the First Princess’ breasts.

Instantly, that necklace bounced out from her cleavage, and landed firmly in Garen’s palm.

Smack.

The white-gold necklace still had the First Princess’ body fragrance and warmth.

Chapter 462: Obtained 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You…!!" The First Princess started tearing up again, and in an instant, she actually turned around and ran.

The door opened with a ker-chak, and then was pulled to a booming close. The First Princess’ sobs and upset voice reached his ears, but grew further and further.

Garen returned to his seat quietly, and carefully observed the Heirloom in his hand. Before long, he began to frown slightly.

This Heirloom couldn’t be activated at all, it felt just like a normal necklace. There wasn’t anything special in it at all.

"I’m still missing an activation password." He remembered suddenly. He wanted to get up and call the First Princess back, but he had just made her storm away, so the problem was whether she was willing to answer or not.

Soon enough, the room door was opened again lightly. Two maids walked in, lowered their heads and bowed, and then spoke.

"Her Highness has a message for you, Palace Master."

"Speak." Garen was still playing with the necklace in his hands.

"If you want the activation password, then you need to agree to a request from Her Highness."

"What request?" Garen raised his head.

"If you are afraid that I will sully you, then how about an absolutely pure girl who has never been touched before? I hope you will treat her as though she was me." The maid took out a pink box and opened it, the First Princess’ voice came from inside as though she was right there.

"If you don’t accept her, I will never tell you the activation password." The First Princess continued, her tone determined.

Garen was stunned, he hadn’t thought the First Princess would do something like this.

After musing over it for a while, he still couldn’t figure out what her plan was. A normal girl wouldn’t affect him all that much either.

"Fine, I’ll accept her."

Smack.

The box was closed.

"Please wait."

The two maids retreated.

Garen nodded.

Although he didn’t know what trick the First Princess had up her sleeve, but since he was already here, then he would surely need to bring the Flash Screen back. If it weren’t that Grand Duke Benoc had the First Princess’ back, and there was his relationship with Prynne there too, he would have made his move and taken it by force by now.

After waiting a little longer.

The door opened again.

A familiar figure walked in slowly, head lowered.

It was a girl no older than twenty-three or -four, her grey-brown hair tied into a ponytail, wearing the silver body-fitting armor from the Royal Guard. There were only a few pieces to this suit of armor, which only showed off the parts of her body that she was proud of, especially her long and full legs, white and smooth, their proportions extremely eye-catching, and at the same time they stretched upwards, sketching out the tight and perky lines of her butt.

The door closed with a smack.

"You’re… Sylvia!?" Garen finally recognized this girl’s identity.

Sylvia looked up, and her dazed eyes instantly cleared up as well.

"Cousin… Garen!?"

She opened her little mouth wide, and nearly couldn’t close it.

At first she had been told that the First Princess was planning to give her to a powerful person, and she was asked if she would be willing.

Sylvia always wanted to make a name for herself with her own power, but reality was cruel, and without the totem ability or any other special power, no matter how hard she worked, the position she had reached now was already the limit. And her best friend Hathaway’s sudden change had provoked her pride and ego even more.

After she considered it for a while, even though she had heard about those powerful people’s fetishes, she still clenched her teeth and agreed.

The two of them looked at each other, neither thinking that they would meet the other under these circumstances.

All of a sudden, the room had gone utterly quiet, there were only Sylvia’s hastened breathing and intense heartbeat. She never thought that Hathaway’s cousin would be…

Just thinking that she would soon become his female slave, her heart immediately felt unspeakably weird.

The girls sent out by the First Princess almost all went voluntarily, and their status would always be the other’s female slave, this was a secret almost everyone in the upper circle of the Kingdom knew.

It was only, if it had been someone else, Sylvia might still have been able to accept it, but to think it was Garen…

She bit her lower lip, and didn’t know what to say, her face growing hotter and hotter.

After a long, long time… she finally remembered what she had been told to say.

"The password… that password… is on…" Faced with this man, her best friend’s cousin, she just wanted a slit in the ground that she could crawl into.

Garen was slightly awkward too, but when it came to the password, he had no choice but to carefully listen to what she had to say.

"The password, phew…" Sylvia took a deep breath, "The password is written… on my body, and only your Totem Light can reveal it, sir."

After that, even her neck was so red it burned.

There were five parts to the password. To be more precise, it was purposely divided into five parts by the First Princess, and written on five parts of her body with a special technique.

These five places were all the most secret places for a woman. Her twin peaks, the insides of her two thighs, and slightly lower than the most secret place between her legs. Out of these places, she could look at four of these places herself and record it down once they were revealed, but the last place was very inconvenient… And the condition to reveal them was that a totem user had to touch them with Totem Light, while the only way to have one’s Totem Light activate on an outsider would be to have bodily contact…

Sylvia’s face was completely red, and she didn’t know how to say it.

Garen just smiled, though.

He knew that the First Princess purposely did this, she purposely chose Sylvia, purpose wrote the password on extremely private places.

Since the First Princess had already gone to such lengths, and tried so many ways to achieve her goal. Then as a normal man, he no longer had a reason to reject her at this point.

But even if he wanted to play, he had the self-restraint to not pounce on her right now, as for the First Princess’ manipulation methods, he still wanted to truly study them for a while.

Sylvia’s body might have been treated specially. After going back, with the proper preparations, Garen planned to figure it out himself.

As for the fact that Sylvia was his cousin Hathaway’s best friend, that was fine too, after all Hathaway would belong to him eventually, their engagement wasn’t just for show.

It wasn’t that Garen didn’t touch women, there were just many types of desire, and the body’s sexual desire was just the basest desire, he didn’t have much interest towards it. While he was in the Secret Technique World, he had already learned how to control this desire, especially after that time at the Behemoth Gate meeting, he had started putting more of his effort in other areas.

"Let’s go, follow me back."

"We…" Sylvia couldn’t help but speak, but she couldn’t finish her sentence.

Garen opened the door instantly, and walked out of the room, Sylvia following behind him.

The First Princess seemed to have guessed that he would come out. There was actually someone outside to lead the way, taking him outside.

Whether or not Garen was willing, once he had checked Sylvia’s body, as a virgin who had never been touched, she could only become his person.

Sitting in the carriage the First Princess had arranged, neither Garen nor Sylvia had any intention to speak.

The sound of the carriage wheels rattled, the afternoon sunlight somewhat dim, as there was the fragrance of baking oat biscuits floating in the air.

There was the sound of iron-smithing in the distance, this was the vacation palace on another mountaintop, if they wanted to return to the Palace District on the first mountaintop, they still needed quite some time, and had to cross a bridge over a deep valley on the way.

They could occasionally hear the sound of children playing from the windows, and the barking of puppies.

Sylvia was sitting on Garen’s right. Although her position was now as one of Garen’s barter items, but in her heart, she still couldn’t quite accept it, after all the man next to her was her best friend’s cousin. How did things end up like this?

Garen didn’t really care about this relationship, though.

He needed to study the trick on Sylvia’s body eventually, which meant Sylvia would belong to him eventually, so he had obtained Caeserton’s forged Heirloom and got a pretty little lady for free, without paying any price in the meantime.

What he was thinking about now, was what the First Princess’ aim could possibly be. Even if the Flash Screen was a useless Heirloom, she still wouldn’t just give it to him.

Nothing much happened on the way, and neither of them was in the mood to talk.

The carriage went past the street, crossed several plazas, and half an hour later, finally arrived at the large suspended bridge between the mountaintops.

The black bridge was just like a stone slab, with a circular hole underneath, while birds occasionally flew through the hole.

There were even several bluebird houses built on the right side of the bridge surface, these little black stone houses were like square boxes, with little bluebirds flying out of them and shooting towards the distant sky.

Although these fast creatures had started falling behind as a communication device after radios and the like became more popular, but there were still people who preferred to use the birds to send their messages.

Before they got onto the bridge, there was a speed bump, so when the carriages entered and exited this way, they would jolt a little, making a slight ‘bump’.

Garen’s carriage followed the one in front, and also gave a little ‘bump’ like that.

Sylvia was still feeling dazed, and was caught off-guard, so this jolt caused her body to slant slightly, until she just knocked straight into Garen, her not-too-considerable chest knocking hard into Garen’s right arm.

Her face instantly got even redder, and she hurriedly straightened up, not even daring to look at Garen’s face.

On the other hand, Garen smiled slightly, and didn’t say anything.

After more than ten minutes, the carriage finally reached the Palace District.

There were already some people waiting outside the palace walls, greeting Garen and company respectfully.

Followed by a host of subordinates, the two of them quickly returned to the Black Swamp Palace, with Garen taking Sylvia directly into the tightly-guarded Inner Hall.

Walking into his own bedroom, Garen led Sylvia to the left side of the room, in front of a huge oil painting covering the whole wall.

The oil painting was of a scene of a castle by the mountains and a lake, between the green mountains and blue water, surrounded by countless dense forests, there was a white castle with pointy turrets. Black eagles circled in the sky, and there was a dark blue flying dragon settled on the top of the castle, its eyes emitting a sparkling green light.

Garen reached out his hand and tapped the area between the dragon’s eyes.

Whoosh…

Amidst the soft sounds of friction, the large wall behind the oil painting actually started to sink inwards, and then it moved to the right, revealing an arch-shaped hole two meters wide.

The cave was well-lit, it was a pale yellow arched underground tunnel, that kept going downwards, who knew how deep it was. The floor of the tunnel was lined with smooth black stone bricks, with an illuminating lamp every so often on the right.

"Let’s go." Garen led the way inside, while Sylvia followed him nervously, by now, she had no other choice.

In truth, when she signed the contract the First Princess gave here, and when the password was written on her private parts, her future had already been sealed.

The two of them went one before the other, advancing slowly in the tunnel, and soon they turned into another branching path, after too many such detours to count, the two of them finally stopped in front of a black wooden door to an inner room.

Garen pushed open the door lightly, and walked in.

Sylvia stopped hesitating as well, and followed him inside.

Chapter 463: Test 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Sylvia walked into the room, a simple affair with tables, chairs, decorations and a bed all made of white stone. There were no complicated designs, with the exception of the round testing table in the middle. On top of it was a notebook, lab equipment, and a simple unit Factory used buy Luminarists.

Garen walked to the sink in the right corner, turned on the tap and washed his hands.

"Lay down on it." Garen commanded, still facing the basin.

Sylvia blushed and stuttered in her step, before walking over to the testing table and She seemed to be hesitating about laying on top of it.

She looked at Garen’s back. He was undoubtedly an elegant man. In another time and place they might have been lovers of a sort, but in a place like this, such a cold room..

Garen finished washed his hands and saw that she was still standing, dumbfounded, with a lost expression on her face. He smiled.

Without saying more, he walked over to her and extended his index finger, gently touching the nape of her neck.

"Aah! "

Sylvia moaned and she lost her strength and crumpled onto Garen.

She felt her strength sapped from her in an instant, as though her entire body felt weak, However, her senses were still as acute as before, or, to be more precise, they became even more sensitive.

After that, she felt herself being placed flat on the experiment table gently.

Garen’s hand pulled on her chest area.

With a snap, the decorative white chestplate on her loosened, and then was taken away; revealing a white bra underneath.

Her entire body was flushed rosy red; she’d rather cover her eyes and choose not to look.

Garen, on the other hand, remained as stoic as ever; the lust in his eyes dissolving hastily.

With a wave of his fingers.

Grack!

The white bra was snapped in the middle and fell away to both sides, revealing her pale, red breasts.

They weren’t incredible in size, but would easily fill the cup of a hand. Garen was looking for something situated on the edge of the nipple.

On both sides were black, alphabet like imprints.

Garen extended his hands, and rubbed against the two alphabets gently.

Tsss…. Both symbols bent and morphed, forming two completely different words from the two black alphabets.

Garen recorded both symbols in his mind with a single glance.

Next, he spread Sylvia's legs. In the similar way that he opened her chestplate, he snapped open her armor on her thighs, releasing a pair of long, slender legs with a flick of his finger.

On the inside of her thighs were also two similar black alphabets.

Garen used the same way to caress it.

Sylvia tensed up at his touch and shuddered slightly. Garen’s finger brushed across her thigh, making her so sensitive that her body ran red with heat.

Yet another two alphabets were decoded, and then recorded in the same fashion.

Only one remaining.

As she thought about where the last one would be, Sylvia’s cheeks flushed so deeply it would have warranted both her hands covering her face. She would need to be on all-fours, before the symbol could be seen from her rear.

Her heart was wrenching every which way; her friend’s cousin was handling her body at his own will, and what a near-perfect man he was. She felt within her an awkwardness and shame, but at the same time, a hint of excitement.

Yet, Garen remained composed and without lust, his eyes cold.

As he flipped Sylvia over, he placed her in a crawling position, her hip lifted up high. With a tap of his finger, the entirety of her lower body armor and garments were torn apart.

Behind her secret areas, Garen hadn’t bothered with another glance at the alluring scene, instead taking his fingers and brushing the center.

"Aah..!" Sylvia was pushed over the edge. Her entire body shuddered with sensation, and liquid burst forth from her nether region as she lost control.

With the splashing sound of water, the entire experimentation table and floor was covered in a puddle of water, and a lewd scent filled the entire room.

Meanwhile, Garen has recorded the final symbol and retrieved a white cloth with an expressionless face to protect Sylvia’s modesty.

"I’ve finished recording the codes. Next we need to..."

He gazed at Sylvia’s hips on the experimentation table; a bowl-sized beaker was placed at just the right spot to catch slightly less than half a beaker full of liquid. The colorless liquid flowed down the side of the container.

Garen took up the beaker and shook it without any change in his expression.

Both his eyes lit up slightly red. This was the activation of the Shackles of War. The Primordial Eyes after its evolution were stronger than the original Isaiah’s Eyes, and enabled him to observe things many people could not.

This slimy liquid had nothing out of the ordinary, but still Garen remained his cold expression. Although his eyes hadn’t picked up anything, he felt that there was something wrong with the liquid.

If say man and women were to have intercourse, then the easiest to hide would be this kind of liquid. Humans, at the peak of their passion, when their guard was at its lowest, would fall for this 9 out of 10 times.

Garen put Sylvia at the back of his head, instead taking some liquid from the beaker using a straw. He put a few droplets on a petri dish, and then introduced different types of dyes onto the petri dish. Lastly, the petri dish will be placed into a Totem Light Simulation Box.

This box could simulate weaker versions of different totem light. Just by inserting the appropriate totem power, one could simulate totem light, albeit a very weak one.

Garen chose three different natures of light. Being put beneath the totem’s light, Garen would like to see what kind of reaction would happen in the petri dish.

Soon, over some time, three analog time files gradually alternated between each other, and then came to a rest.

After opening the box, even Garen; who was so composed, couldn’t help but feel surprised.

Looking into the petri dish, he was surprised to see a fat black beetle. This banana-shaped bug with tens of little legs, swinging its head left and right in the petri dish, it was is almost as big as a palm.

"You mean to say, a short span of ten-odd seconds was enough to grow a bug to this size with the supply of totem’s light?" Garen could not believe his own eyes.

Looking at the fat black bug in the petri dish, Garen only felt more disgusted.

Looking at Sylvia’s current sexy body again now, she had lost all attraction in Garen’s eyes, and replacing it was an odd sense of disgust.

However for Sylvia, it was as though she hadn’t seen anything, but instead was filled with a sense of confusion as she saw Garen take out the petri dish from the box.

Garen deactivated his Primordial Eyes, and the black bug in the petri dish indeed disappeared.

He reactivated the Primordial Eyes again, and the black bug could still be seen laying around lazily in the petri dish.

"No wonder so many Totem Users have been controlled subconsciously, these kind of tricks…" thinking about the Grand Princess’ youthful body, Garen seemed to understand something.

He looked at Sylvia, with a stern face.

"There may have some issues with your body. You may have been messed around with, and are in slight danger. In the subsequent period of time, please remain in this underground chamber. I will look for some high-end devices to fix this completely. But before that, please don't go anywhere."

Sylvia couldn’t move at this moment, she could only blink her eyes. However, judging from Garen’s lack of lust, she felt that there were was some hidden meaning behind his instruction.

"From now on, you’re one of mine. I’ll get someone to serve you in a moment. You can have anything you want, besides getting out of this underground chamber."

After he had notified Sylvia, Garen immediately left the room and slowly tapped the bell on the right side of the wall. Soon, a few head maid servants rushed over.

"Palace Master, what are your instructions?" asked two head maids who were in charge of the cleaning department’s personnel.

This area was half public, and was connected to the Technique Hall underground.

"Send two people here to serve this young lady. Whatever that she wants, just grant it if it’s within your jurisdiction. Just, don’t let her leave the chamber."

"Understood." the two head servants bowed in respect.

Garen nodded, after all, Sylvia is cousin Hathaway’s friend. He couldn’t just stand by and watch her get controlled. About this ploy on the Grand Princess, if it weren’t for his Primordial Eyes, all the converging circumstances, and Sylvia's orgasm, he might very well have never discovered the truth.

Speaking of which, passing this to that bunch of researchers should uncover the secrets of Sylvia’s body in no time, but as his own woman, how can he simply pass her along to some other employees for research?

Garen could not do things like the nobles of this world did; exchanging their partners, the lust of the upper echelon and their lewd lifestyles definitely carried more than even the vilest pornographic material.

He was very possessive in nature. As long as it’s his, no matter if they were people or items, he found it hard to tolerate the thought of someone else owning it.

After he sent the black bug to the Technique Hall for analysis, he talked to the forgers and researchers, who were very interested in the existence of the black bug. Among them was the leader, Master Calingan, who was an avid researcher. As he heard Garen’s explanation, his interest grew and he immediately began conducting multiple probing and experimentation analysis on it, trying to collect more data.

After dumping it to a bunch of researchers, Garen couldn’t care less anymore.

He immediately returned to Black Swamp Palace to begin his Secret Technique training for the day.

At this point of the training, by delimiting the Secret Technique’s level threshold by combining the Nine-Headed Dragon, this process is more similar to using a totem as a nutrient, and then evolving the Secret Techniques after absorbing it, then using the evolved Secret Technique to evolve himself.

However, now Garen is plagued by the lack of totem potential points. Only his core totem was eligible to be used as raw fuel for the evolution. If it was insufficient, the Secret Technique would have a hard time evolving too.

By then, he could only forcibly evolve into the early stage of Form 5. To improve any more would prove to be troublesome.

Garen was estimating that, for Hellgate to be able to overcome Form 5 and become the world’s strongest; that sort of level would have a sizeable gap compared to all other Form 5s.

Even if he used the extreme control of the King of the Century and was able to use 120% of his power, it might not be much help either.

After Form 5, everybody had their own Secret Technique. Then, his own trait of possessing a Secret Technique would get less grandiose and unique..

Even if he did break through to Form 5 with its early stage, of which had an insurmountable power, all top totem users wished to have a control over an Original Heirlooms’ existence…

That was to say, Hellgate had never lacked in that department.

The wheels of history continued moving.

No matter if it were to protect a family’s heritage, or to guarantee that Goth will not suffer an unsightly death in the end, he still needed the ultimate strength and power.

Obscuro and Terraflor were all direct opponents of the Trejons Family. In having these two strong enemies, the only way through was to increase his strength.

He recently began to pay a bit more thought on building his influence, all with the aim of actually changing the future.

**********************

Three days later

At the rear courtyard of Black Swamp Palace.

Garen was kneeling in meditation, his eyes closed. The three dotted mark on his forehead was glowing blood red.

An unknown swirling power was surrounding him

The morning air was cold and humid, dampening a few of the white stone’s surface in the courtyard, presenting a somewhat black glow.

"Palace Master, Elder Blizzard wishes to meet you." A guard walked in from the courtyard entrance and informed respectfully.

"Let him in." Garen did not open his eyes and remained seated. Had his voice not echoed off the courtyard, nobody would have realized that he had spoken.

The guard retreated, and soon, Second Tower Head Blizzard walked into the courtyard in white robes and looked at his surroundings.

In the corner of the courtyard was a small patch of red plums. This species blossoms in the autumn, as it was currently. They were bright red, like a patch of red clouds, spreading the faint fragrance of red plum.

Blizzard walked in and laid his focus on Garen.

With a light smile, he walked near him in big steps, and stopped around ten meters from Garen.

"Palace Master, I’ve realized something two days ago. Coincidentally, after reading some books from the palace archive, I have gained new knowledge in the use of totems. People around me have been occupied and away, and I thought of training with you after some consideration." Aside from Blizzard’s arrogance and aggressive temper, he is indeed a maniac who improves through actual brawls, and had indeed allocated most of the time to improve himself.

It is probably due to his nature that he could rise to be Seven Nights’ Tower’s strongest man, aside from the first tower head.

"Training?" Garen opened his eyes. He surmised that it musn't have been that others were unavailable, but were scared of getting beaten up. This guy had been going around looking for sparring partners, not being able to work his body must have made him uncomfortable.

Coincidentally, he had imitated Caeserton’s Flash Screen, and having not found anyone to test it on, this Blizzard came waltzing in instead.

After all, if Garen himself went around to look for a sparring partner, with his position, it may be seen as a threat and warning and could be easily misunderstood. If others were the ones who looked for him, however, that’s a different story.

"Sure."

Garen reached for the ground with one hand. His entire body began rising up, and eventually stood steadily on his legs. The transition from sitting to standing was natural.

Pa pa!!

He clapped his hands, a white stream of water vapor appeared and shot straight onto a piece of white crystal.

Vrmm…..

A square platform was raised in the middle of the courtyard. On the stone floor were inscribed complex tactical array symbols.

"Please."

Garen jumped up first. Blizzard snickered and followed suit.

He gauged Garen in front of him, even though he heard from Anjiad about Garen’s strength but he believes that he can take on Garen just as easily as Anjiad, so he always thought to try out this rumored vicious Nine Headed Dragon of the outer world.

The two of them were standing on the platform, over ten meters in width. Neither of them made the first move..

At the pinnacle of Form 4, to the totem users, as they face experts of similar level, their totems actually possess a fatal weakness.

The defense of a totem is almost half as weak as its original body. Once the opponent caught the weakness and launched strong attacks, losing was a very real possibility. Hence, the totem users of this level rarely bring their totems into a war, but instead relied on their body.

Garen wasn’t aware what secret techniques that Blizzard practiced, but he did not bring a single weapon with him. Instead he was barehanded, like Garen.

Unknowingly, a white silhouette unexpectedly appeared at the top of the courtyard, it was actually Ivycius’ friend, Island Master Skyharp.

This lady was looking at the two men on the arena without blinking,

Following which, was Island Master Lightless appearing next to her unexpectedly.

Chapter 464: Test 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"It’s rare to see Palace Master Garen in action. Skyharp, who do you think is stronger?" Lightless touched her chin and asked.

"Hard to say. Among the experts of the Central Region, if leaving aside the of use any Heirlooms, he should be slightly weaker. So I guess Blizzard is slightly stronger. As powerful as Palace Master Garen is, he is still very young and lacks in experience." Skyharp said slowly.

"Indeed, relying on his exterior power would be insufficient. These folks from the Snowy Mountains are indeed very strong." Lightless agreed and nodded.

Mid-conversation, the two men on in arena engaged in battle.

With a single wave of his hand by Blizzard, a circle of white ice diamonds appeared next to him and revolved around his person.

Blizzard roared, and a suit of ice armor instantly formed around him.

The armor got thicker and thicker, amplifying his height as it went.

From over a meter, he quickly became two meters, three, four, five meters!!

After he is done, Blizzard himself couldn’t be seen. Instead, an ice golem towering at five meters stood in front of Garen.

The ring of rapidly rotating ice diamonds had also slowly dissipated. What was left was a crystal white ice golem on the arena.

"My Extreme Ice Technique has a total of three levels, this is my first, Palace Master, you have to be careful." Blizzard who was within the golem snickered, the blurry face of the golem also forcefully smiled.

Before he was finished speaking, the golem lifted his fist and has hammered towards Garen.

The white golem’s fist was about a meter wide, on it were dense spikes of intimidating ice diamonds. Oddly though, before the punch connected, a white ice mist swiftly spread itself across the arena, covering the entire area.

The two spectators nearby frowned.

"Blizzard’s Extreme Ice Technique is not a simple brute force technique." Skyharp said slowly.

"Indeed." Lightless nodded, " the ice breeze can affect the environment without notice, and I think it can affect the opponent’s agility. This technique is somewhat troublesome, but we can easily handle them."

On the arena.

Garen’s face remained unfazed. He intended to put Totem’s Light after combination to the test.

Against this punch, he’d rather not move, and he extended his left arm to face the punch. His palm carried no momentum.

Form 4 was already the pinnacle of a regular Totem user; they had completely discovered the totem’s abilities and potential, so there will be no openings during its usage. Uniform in movement, and extremely powerful.

Every Form 4 has completely unleashed their core totem’s power to the maximum, and should not be taken lightly.

Bam!!

Both people took a step back, Garen’s brows twitched, even though his power is slightly stronger than his opponent, the totem’s light on his body already showed signs of collapsing.

"Too weak." He can’t help but sigh, Nine-Headed Dragon Totem’s Light was so fragile in front of the experts of the same level. The opponent hadn’t even unleashed half of his full power, but the totem’s light was already at its limit..

Blizzard seemed to realize Garen’s situation too. He laughed, and then rushed over again. He put his hands together and then separate them.

Suddenly, a white ice ring was shot towards Garen. At the same time, his entire body jumped up high.

"Extreme Ice Explosion!"

Blizzard roared, and intend to crush Garen along with the golem.

Looking at the incoming golem, Garen lifted his head slightly, and his mark on the forehead lit up.

Suddenly, he took two steps backward, and raised his right leg in a single stroke.

His legs turned into a whip-like afterimage, and a loud sound of thunderous explosions was heard. It was the ice ring being destroyed, directing towards the golem midair.

Bam Bam Bam Bam!!!

The impacts rang like pellets of rain.

Countless ice shards were scattered across the arena, blocking their lines of sight. The spectators were unable to see what was going on.

Somewhere in the meantime, Garen walked to the sides of the arena with his hands in his pockets, as though he hadn’t done anything at all.

If it were a comparison of totem strength, he would naturally be unable to compete on a level field, as Blizzard’s totem was no ordinary totem, but if it was martial arts, even ten Blizzards wouldn’t be his equal.

With his level equal to King of the Century, his understanding towards Secret Techniques and strong combat prowess, he was beyond the league of this world.

Jii!

An icicle shot out from the cloud of ice, like a white lightning. Garen happened to moved his head and evaded it easily.

Following it closely, was a second, third, more and more icicles. The salvo was dense, much like a school of flying fish. It curved its trajectory and surrounded Garen.

Garen relaxedly pressed his chest in with his hand. The Flash Screen extended out into an invisible hemisphere around him.

With a loud thump, all the icicle concentrated at one point and violently shot towards the screen.

The hemisphere flash screen stayed completely unaffected.

"Huh?" Blizzard’s surprise could be heard from the other side of the arena. He was so surprised to see Garen still standing in his original position, with his Icicle Rain being one of the pride and joys of his repertoire. These icicles have a level of automation and carried the Blue-eyed Cold poison, which could continuously corrode the opponent’s Totem’s light. He never expected that his opponent could take on these techniques without any damage.

"Again!" He roared. The ice golem enveloping him expanded once again, growing even larger than before.

After Garen blocked the icicles with the screen, he wanted to speak, but realized something, and was slightly surprised as he looked at the southeastern sky.

Just as he spaced out, Blizzard had a gleam in his eyes, he viciously swung out another punch. A violent cold breeze rushed outwards to his surroundings, and the entire arena was almost covered in a layer of thick ice.

The large fist almost instantaneously reached Garen. The large amount of power brought forth terrifying, explosive energy, making this punch viciously quick.

At the same time, thick layers of ice crystals began forming on Garen’s feet, spreading upwards around his legs, immobilizing them.

"I refuse to believe that I cannot move you!" Blizzard got excited, all the power in him have been unleashed without reserve.

"Huh?"

Garen seemed to only just realize the attacks in front of him

He raised a lazy hand towards blizzard.

Bam!!!

The entire arena shook violently.

Blizzard’s fist was stopped in front of Garen. It with a distance of no more than half a meter, but it felt like heavens apart.

His entire body turned blood red and fell into a status of unbalanced vigor. His energy previously was released violently causing the imbalance. Now he could only quickly recover and recalibrate his vigor.

"Black Water True Technique. Whiplash!!"

With a twist of his body, and a right kick, suddenly clouds of water vapor condensed on his right leg, accumulating rapidly, becoming a water pillar several meters thick and tens of meters long in just half a second.

The large water pillar was like an extension of Garen’s leg and was launched towards Blizzard in an instant.

Bam!!!

The splash from the attack scattered, and Blizzard was sent flying from this kick, having been lodged into a palace wall nearby. The entire courtyard vibrated slightly.

Garen’s sweep was like a giant axe. The one hit brought with it a pillar of water. From a seemingly unimpressive side kick, water quickly condensed as his leg was swinging, accumulating into something bigger and longer!

In an instant, it became over ten meters long!

The two spectators stood unblinking, their jaws slightly ajar. A stunned expression was on their faces, gawping at this form of strong, and impossibly accurate control. This was no longer a battle, but instead was an art form worthy of fascination.

Only unleashing such explosive energy at one key point, meanwhile presenting no threat during peacetime, almost like he was an ordinary man.

Cough cough…

More than half of the layers upon layers of defensive tactics that were placed on the walls had also been obliterated.

Blizzard removed himself from the dent in the wall he was in, thoroughly wet, with a terrible-looking face, and couldn’t stop coughing.

"As expected of Palace Master Garen!! How could I have not thought of this move? Such control! This level of control….!!" He couldn’t care less about his looks, with lit eyes, naught a care in the world about his image.

"I’m sorry, I got carried away and dealt a heavy hand." A hint of guilt was heard in Garen’s tone. He had also completed the necessary objectives.

Even though Blizzard hadn’t unleashed his full power, Garen had only used about 10%.

Blizzard’s power should be below Ivycius’ power from before, but stronger than Anjiad. Compared to the rest, he should be the strongest out of the sex elders.

Garen thought to himself. His usual powers, combined with the Black Water True Technique and Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills he should be able to suppress Blizzard, but there wouldn’t be many stronger than him.

However, if he used the Troll Grip’s ring, he should be able to end the battle in one minute. There would be consequences; perhaps heavy injury, or even the loss of life.

If he used the heirloom’s Flash Screen, he would be able to end the battle unharmed.

Black Water True Technique could control all liquids in a certain radius, but due to the barrier of totem’s light, its effect wasn’t great, and could only be used as a distraction.

Just like that, after distracting the opponent, he used the opening to slam the opponent off the arena.

Black Water True Technique’s real selling point was that it could condense water literally out of thin air, but it would depend on the surrounding humidity. Plus, it may look strong during the condensation process, but its actual damage is very little. After all, it was not dense, and water is soft in nature.

Overall, this technique is not considered strong at all

At this point, a reddish-purple light was emanating in the sky faraway in the southeast direction.

Garen looked towards that direction again.

"That’s…."

Jii!!

A white light was shot from the reddish purple light. And it soared through the sky of the entire kingdom.

Island Master Lightless gave a cold sigh, as she extended her arms and grabbed.

Countless clouds and smoke became a large hand, and tightly gripped onto the white light. In an instant, the white light broke through. Lightless were no longer able to catch it, and let out a sound of confusion.

"Let me do it!" Skyharp’s fingers immediately drew out a tactics symbol, and in that instant where the symbol was completed, a purple light flashed. The white light midair was finally blocked, falling straight onto Skyharp’s hands.

"This is?!!" Skyharp saw the main body of the white light and bulged her eyes.

"Alice’s Mirrorstone"! Garen spoke without restraint.

This is a dispatched item for Angels of the Night currently out on a mission, which was a tool used to request for reinforcements. However, this item’s trajectory power is so strong two people were required to stop it.

In the regions protected by the Kingdom, there were many abandoned mines waiting to be distributed, Garen had the Angels of the Night take charge of the Black Swamp Palace, to ensure everyone’s benefits.

In just a few days, this Form 4, at her peak, actually sent out a reinforcement signal?

"Looks like that reddish-purple light spells problems," Skyharp said, "There may have some sort of precious minerals appearing, and Angel alone cannot control the situation."

"Let me take the trip" Lightless proactively suggested.

"I’ll go with you." Skyharp also said.

Angel’s mining area primarily produced black gold crystals. Now that there’s a pillar of reddish purple light…" Garen had a guess. "For this to happen, there can only be one reason."

Blizzard approached at this point, all three of them looked at Garen and awaited his answer.

"Glittering Water." Garen closed his eyes, " It’s definitely the appearance of Glittering Water!"

"Go… all three of you, the Glittering Water has to be ours, and only rightfully so. Anyone who interrupts, kill them all."

Even though the three other people do not know what Glittering Water is, judging from Garen’s vicious tone, they realized the severity of the issue.

The three took his orders, each releasing a giant black bird, rushing southeastward with incredible haste.

Garen, who was standing in his original position, rubbed his forehead for a period; the veins on his skin showed, as though he was enduring some unbearable pain.

Chapter 465: Departure 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Glittering Water…

This name seemed to have fished out some memories from the deep recess of his brain.

Garen only felt immense pain in his head as image after image kept flashing in his mind.

These scenarios seemed far and blurry, like they weren’t actually his memories.

"The Nine-Headed Dragon’s genetic message…" He walked to the plum bush nearby and placed himself down.

The Nine-Headed Dragon’s memories occasionally affected Garen, but they were much better compared to before, reduced to some occasional headaches.

Garen reached out to touch the ice-cold stone table. The cold tabletop was smooth to the touch, its tough body gave Garen a firm sensation that he was touching something real.

After some time, the pain gradually subsided.

Garen put down his hand, and took a deep breath.

"The Glittering Water has appeared… looks like we are nearing the destruction of the Royal Alliance. Glittering Water is capable of boosting low level totem users’ evolution and extreme healing prowess, but its production was also alarming low. Based on the original history, Kovitan had a Glittering pool, Daniela had two, Ender had one, and the other regions sporadically had three. This was the real cause of the RAL’s fall."

On the original timeline, the Glittering Water had strong special effects, and even though a pond could only produce enough for ten people a year and was only effective for these low level totem users, it still caused massive internal conflict among the alliance.

Due to the ravaging monsters, the internal conflict in the RAL, factored in with the Glittering Water’s ability causing internal conflict.. Perhaps there were Obscuro’s plans inside, but it was undeniable that the Alliance’s wobbly structure was to blame for the most part.

And during this time, Daniela was also undergoing massive change due to Glittering Water. Having been dethroned by this generation’s King of Daniela and becoming an incomplete version of the Cthulhu Totem, and then healed by Glittering Water, resulted in an inclination for wounds to heal.

During the King of Daniela’s pursuit of absolute power, he challenged experts everywhere, and constantly challenged the Cthulhu Totem. Originally Cthulhu King paid no heed to him, but his improvements were too rapid.

When the Cthulhu King realized something was wrong, it was all too late, the King of Daniela had immense innate talent, and reached an unimaginable strength. Within the next of century, he would fight the Cthulhu King ceaselessly, eventually gravely wounding him, gaining the chance to stabilize the country and develop it.

However, due to Cthulhu's’ careful management over thousands of years, the Cthulhuism Society had an immense foundation, so both sides forcibly maintained peace.

The appearance of Glittering Water expedited the Cthulhu King’s recovery, and Daniela’s new internal war will begin once again.

Garen thought carefully. The current Kovitan was but an empty shell; with such a small area of control surrounding the Kingdom left, it was considered heavily injured. Next would be Daniela, and then finally Ender.

Daniela was different compared to Kovitan, the Cthulhuism Society and RAL’s powers were both second to none in the current standings. Even Obscuro would not simply take action against the big characters if Hellgate weren’t awakened.

With the appearance of the Glittering Water, Garen realized that he had a very good opportunity.

Glittering Water is much more important to the Cthulhu King compared to anyone else. His need for Glittering Water was massive, and so long as Garen owned a pond, he would have the necessary bargaining chips to negotiate with Cthulhuism Society and gain some benefits.

Plus, Garen could faintly feel that this Glittering water may be beneficial to help him recover the Nine-Headed Dragon’s memories. The headache that occurred just now had no indication it was coming at all, there must have been a reason behind it.

Garen lightly tapped on the table with his fingers. He thought about ways to maximise his advantage before the Alliance fell. In order to expand his abilities, even if he doesn’t win against Hellgate, he should at least be able to ensure his safety.

Fuuu...

He let out a long sigh. Just as he prepared to stand up and return to the palace, he suddenly realized that someone was sitting to the side, in the corner of his eyes.

It was Kid.

He was holding onto a red plum, and kept rubbing the twig in a rotational motion, he looked like he was enjoying himself.

" What are you doing here?" Garen was almost used to Kid’s mysterious appearances.

"I had nothing to do so.. I just found something new, so I came over." Kid answered with boredom.

"New discovery?"

"Yeah, you have to remember to protect me though." Kid smiled as he said.

Garen Was speechless. This Kid had never done anything proper, instead opting to play all the time, and his own abilities remained a mystery. What kind of protection does he need? Seeing that he didn’t want to talk about it at the moment, he didn’t ask any further.

As he walked towards the inner hall, he had a short chat with Lala, who just had lunch with Prynne, who was strolling around. By the evening, some news came through about the Glittering Water mine.

"You mean to say, even though we occupied the mine, half of the Glittering Water in the pool had been taken by others?" Garen asked as he frowned at the Black Swamp guard who reported to him.

"Yes, Elder Lightless and Skyharp have already begun the hunt, while Elder Angel and Blizzard is guarding the Glittering Pond." The Guard answered immediately.

Garen glanced at the experts on both sides of the hall.

Ivycius was emotionless with his sword on his knees, silent, eyes closed, as though he was meditating and didn’t bother with the guard’s report.

Anjiad from the Seven Nights’ Tower on the other hand, was yawning, his eyes full of dark circles. Who knew how long had it been since he slept.

Beneath it was the supervisor of the Black Swamp Palace, Lala, as well as the family’s head guard Maxilan and Edney, and the White Silver Palace’s three pupils under Ivycius. Not to mention Master Calingan, who just rushed over from the Technique Hall.

Garen frowned, and he looked at Master Calingan.

"Master, about the Technique Hall…"

Calingan nodded and stood up. "We can dispatch a Forger and rush over with the latest Tactical Array. We have just finished researching an ambush bramble array, which was based off the original Royal Palace’s illusionary array, modified and simplified to form 2. The alert radius is about two kilometers.

"A form 2 array?" Garen nodded, " that would suffice for an alert array, plus it is a portable item, but what if I wanted a higher level array?"

Calingan shook his head.

"I’m sorry, Palace Master, but any arrays above Form 2 would exhaust large quantities of rare materials, and you would require at least ten forgers. With the current capacity of the Technique Hall, the research progress would be severely impacted.

"That’s fine then." Garen shook his head.

"Palace Master, in the singular tactics warehouse, don’t we have three large area Spiritualized arrays?" Calingan reminded.

Garen thought about it, the most valuable and practical thing in the Royal Palace’s warehouse was indeed the three sets of large area Spiritualized Arrays. Its area of effect was more than ten kilometers in radius, and it was strong enough to deny entry to any totem users beneath Spiritualized form. It was indeed a great defensive array. These three sets were also the most valuable items in Kovitan, aside from the heirlooms that Garen carried all the time.

"Among the three arrays, the Ten Circular Ring was planned to be placed in the entire compound of the Royal Palace." Calingan explained. "Out of the remaining two, I intend to use one to be an inner array to protect the Technique Hall and the residential inner halls. And the final one can be used to guard the Glittering Pond."

Garen nodded after some thought.

"This is a good idea."

Calingan continued.

"If we can get more help and resources, our Technique Hall’s abilities could be increased by a margin too. I heard that Ender’s Master Raphael possesses wonderful skills in terms of Tactical Arrays…" He began giving a list of names.

After all, he was not an expert in researching arrays, and not strong in this aspect.

"Raphael from Ender huh?" Garen stroked his beard. " Lala, try to establish communication with this master, see if you can invite him."

"But the situation in Ender is very stable, this master is also considered a national treasure, I don’t think it would be likely." Lala explained.

"That’s fine, just reach out for now." Garen said coldly, he immediately looked over to Maxilan. "How have my apprentices been?"

Maxilan stood up and answered respectfully.

"Three apprentices have already entered the first level. I have already passed on the skills for level 2. The rest of the apprentices have also been recorded and rewarded according to their entrance period."

The living conditions in the Palace area had been harsh, and was to train their willpower. All their diets have been specially made to be exceptionally nutritious, with terrible taste.

Whoever could endure it was basically a palate genius.

To design this specifically unpalatable food, Garen specifically got Lala to recruit chefs from all over the kingdom who could cook the worst without losing nutritional value.

The sleeping environment was also made of the toughest rock available, and there were only ten blankets. Only those who performed well had the luxury.

Now that the study improvements have been produced, according to the records, only those who did well will be given the reward of a slightly less terrible daily meal. Of course, to get a normal tasting nutritious food, they had to put in more effort.

Perhaps someone had tried not eating, but being barred in the palace with no chance of going out, he could only live in starvation. Plus, such a balanced combination of nutrients was beneficial to the body, and this diet allowed a person to improve slightly faster than others.

After hearing the progress of the three apprentices, he was rather satisfied. As for the rest of them, he didn’t really mind. Only the top ranked ones are worthy of his attention. Plus, level one doesn’t really mean much; the Black Water Pure Technique was the easiest of first levels, but level two was different, to reach level 2, one needed to go through a session of attack endurance trainings, special medicinal baths, and depended heavily on the person’s willpower and strength of body. In a short span of two to three months, there would be no need to consider the possibility of a breakthrough. It would only get harder as the training progresses. The second level was an entrance test. To achieve breakthrough wasn’t bad, but for those who failed, they may take up to tens of years.

Garen thought for a while

"How is the recruitment for totem users going along?"

"There are already two Spiritualized Totem Users who registered. The rest include 15 form 3s, and thousands of form 2s." Lala replied.

"Dispatch the form 2s to maintain the operations of the arrays in the palace. Spread the form 3s out, and have Maxmilan and Edney lead them for now. A ranking match is to be held after a month’s adjustment period. The one who rises above everyone else will be promoted by default to a leader of the guards’ unit.

The palace area was divided into male and female guard units, which were responsible for the security of some of the public areas. However, due to the lack of personnel, they were temporarily commanded by Maxmilan and Edney. Since they are the head guards of the family, and have their own sets of responsibilities, the Trejons Family is growing was size by the day, and its properties along with it, so they were also caught off guard.

Hence, Garen gave them the rights to choose their personnel, after the recommendation of some helpers, it got less hectic.

"Then what about the two Spiritualized Totem Users?" Lala asked

"Let them be in charge of the elders’ living quarters. Independently create a management office of the Elders’ Hall, so that they can expand in the future.

Chapter 466: Departure 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Following that, reports of minor matters flooded in. The management of the palace grew increasingly complicated and troublesome along with influence and power.

Garen would rather wash his hands off at this point, leaving these administrative matters to Ivycius’ three apprentices, fully utilizing all the manpower he can get.

After settling those, he could put his mind at ease for a good amount of time. Even the plans for the next two years have been laid out.

His main goal was to improve his own abilities, not to expand his influence, so these were all secondary in comparison.

After a week, three out of four elders from the Glittering Pool returned, leaving Elder Wukang alone to guard the pool.

In the battle at the Glittering Pool, Elder Wukang used seemingly limitless clouds to engulf the entire region surrounding the Glittering Pool, forming a Wukang area of over ten kilometers in radius. No light was able to penetrate. In that area, Wukang’ totem abilities increased threefold, his vision unaffected by the mist. Also, any enemies who entered his realm without his permission would fall into a limbo realm, where they couldn’t use their totem abilities.

This ability lasted 20 minutes, but within these 20 minutes, Elder Wukang subjugated thirteen Form 4 experts and monsters, taking down all the miscellaneous external influences who are there to take the Glittering Pool.

All the subtler forces around Kovitan, and the Form 4s that were vanguards of those organizations had all been killed by her alone. Among them was even an Obscuro Elemental General who was accidentally engulfed in that radius.

The monster lairs in the surrounding had also been subjugated by him.

In a few short days, Elder Wukang single-handedly established himself as a vicious killer, and was given the honorific of Master Wukang.

Perhaps, aside from the three great forces, there was no one else who would challenge the Black Swamp Palace in the Caeserton region.

The remaining three forces did not try to fight for Black Swamp Palace, as they lacked the understanding of the nature of Glittering Water, staying at the sidelines. In their opinion, it was unwise to go against so many other organizations for a medicinal water that possessed healing properties.

Soon, the negative consequences of Elder Wukang’ monster massacre resurfaced.

The Glittering Pool was not within the area of protection for Ivycius. A large horde of monsters came swarming, among them were a few stronger leader of the lairs. They had already possessed some form of primitive sentience and had the capacity for vengeance, heavily surrounding the glittering pool.

After a single long war, the three elders mobilized and exterminated all the creatures, turning them either into treasures or resources. That war had completely restored the land around the Glittering Pool.

After a week, at the same time the three people returned, Grand Duke Benoc also launched a land reclamation operation. His White Rubber Tree Corps had grown swiftly, and reclaimed most of the mining locations outside the area of protection.

The remaining two forces began mimicking each other, starting to expand outwards. Since they had Caeserton as their backbone, they could always retreat if they were rendered ineffective.

Whereas for now, the leaders of the monster lairs were disbanded, and the density of lairs had also decreased. So long as the numbers didn't grow too large, these monsters will never be a threat to people.

After all, the high level monsters have already been controlled by the underground Elder Senate, while the masses were fighting due to the high density of monsters, most of them lacked basic food and water, and so was unsustainable.

In this period, the entire Kovitan spurred with enthusiasm, all wanting to reclaim the land for their empire.

After the three elders returned, Garen bumped into them, and after a small meeting, they passed a series of civilian development plans.

Among them was the most important clause; reproductive encouragement.

War and the creatures had made the original populous civilization lose a vast majority of its size, and a vast amount of documents were lost, along with the destructions of many tactics crystals. Civilization had lost more than half its heritage. Mankind had been largely exterminated due to the many bodies which weren’t duly disposed of in recent times, causing many forms of epidemics across the region.

Large amounts of hospitals and disease control centers were set up, Forgers and Luminarists were widely recruited, and the entire Kovitan have seemed to have forgotten about the struggle of internal power. Instead, they were busy consolidating the nation’s resources; whoever could rebuild more of the city’s mines, the more that person’s base income and power grew.

The inner conflicts have swiftly turned into a race of external resource collection.

On the other hand, after Garen’s arrangements, he left the kingdom and rushed over to the Glittering Pool.

He wanted to see for himself the source of his headache. As he brought his Flash Screen, his safety has gotten the largest guarantee, especially if it was Ivycius who was the one attacking, After condensing a piece of exploding crystal, there should be even fewer problems.

He had tried for himself the power of the exploding crystals. It was equivalent to a full power attack by the current Ivycius, who were in pseudo-Form 5; its power was immense. Safety was definitely not an issue. Garen could let loose and go out.

********************

In the morning, a swarm of blackbirds spanning over ten meters across their wingspans flew high above the kingdom, pulling a house-sized horse carriage below them.

Amidst the white sea of clouds, the black birds which carried the carriages looked like ink stains on paper; clearly visible.

The wheels on the carriage went round and round, and if one looked from afar, it would appear like the carriage had a bunch of golden bells attached.

Kring….. Kring

Every few minutes, the faint sound of chimes can be heard from the outside of the black carriage.

Garen was sitting in the carriage, holding a goose egg that looked like red jade, sitting in a half-reclined position.

A breeze could be heard from beyond the carriage, occasionally accented by the chirps of some birds.

The carriage was decorated with a set of black tables and chairs, a red bookshelf, and a washroom that was separated, as well as a bedroom.

A portrait of Vanderman could be seen on the wooden wall, with a metal easel as a support. On top of the frame was a black vase. The green plant in it smelled like daffodils, and its fragrance wafted throughout the carriage.

Skyharp was sitting opposite him. The female elder held a cup of tea in her hands, slowly tasting it. She seemed to be at ease, as though she was enjoying the fragrance of the tea.

Garen was playing with the rock in his hand while he quietly channeled the route of his Secret Techniques without rest.

"Why are you free to come out with me? Hadn’t you just come back recently?"

Skyharp took a sip of the tea. She didn’t reply immediately, instead quietly observed the floating flower petals in her tea.

"I just felt that staying back was boring." she replied slowly after a while.

"During this trip, I hadn’t alerted anyone, and just came out quietly. Such a rare chance, I naturally wouldn’t turn back so easily. Do you have any plans?" Garen asked.

"Plans?" It seemed like Skyharp was thinking, and then she shook her head, and no longer spoke.

After observing this, Garen estimated that she had faced some issues with Ivycius, and looked saddened. He therefore held his tongue.

"I’m pregnant"

Puu!!!

Garen almost spat the tea in his mouth.

"It belongs to Ivycius…" Skyharp said, indifferently.

"Are you sure you’re not joking?" Garen was speechless.

"It is Ivycius’ child." Skyharp nodded in confirmation.

Both people fell into silence, and neither of them chose to break it.

Garen had yet to completely digest this breaking news, while Skyharp was unsure of what else to say.

After a long while.

"You guys….move really quickly.." Garen was unsure how to judge it. By Ivy’s temper, it was definitely not his initiative, then it would most likely have been…

"Indeed, I assaulted him." Skyharp let out this shocking fact without much expression. "One dose of the secret summoning potion from Namus, calibrated for Ivy’s body. I could do it easily."

Yet she looked blue.

"Don’t forget, I am a bona fide potion brewer."

Garen’s heart chilled, and he now looked at this iron lady in a different light.

"Then, this journey is for you to give birth to this baby?’ Potion Masters naturally had their unique way to take out the embryo for further nurturing elsewhere. This sort of small surgery was very simple in the Luminarists’ World.

"Yes.. "

Skyharp nodded nonchalantly.

"My body is different from a regular person’s. I will take the fertilized ovum and turn it into an egg, which is what you call an embryo, so long as it is nurtured successfully, it can be grown slowly as I inject my blood in every once in a while.

Garen was lost for words, facing such a devious women, Garen could only mourn for Ivycius.

"Does Ivy know about this?"

Garen finally asked after a while.

"No." Skyharp shook her head. "Such is life, I originally planned to ruin his totem, let him be a normal person, that way he could stay with me forever and never leave. Unfortunately, he combined his life force with his core totem, and cannot be separated."

Garen was speechless again, this person had some twisted logic.

Thank god Skyharp wasn’t paying attention to Garen’s expressions; she only needed someone to talk to.

"Back then, when he came to the island in search for treasures, he was caught by me…. Coincidentally I needed a lab rat, so I kept him. Then I slowly fell in love with him over the course of the experiments, and I could see from his angry eyes that he loved me too, so we got together in Skyharp Island."

Weren’t his eyes angry eyes? How did you conclude that he loved you?

Garen was stunned by Skyharp’s logic.

"Back then, I touched all of his body, he was indeed a cute little kid…" she slumped into her memories. "He was so cute when he was young, he became less cute when he grew older…. It had only been twenty years on the island, yet he already wanted to leave. Such a lack of patience. There’s me to accompany him, what else was there to play with in the outside world?"

She mumbled alone, as though she was immersed in her own memories.

Twenty years. Anybody human enough would want to run after being experimented for so long….

Garen wanted to speak, but he held back, he also wanted to hear more of the later parts of the story between Skyharp and Ivy.

Obviously, Skyharp was just a big bully. A young handsome Ivy who just arrived at the island by accident was violated for 20 years, it was straight up the Totem User’s version of mistress keeping.

Garen had no idea what kind of face he should be showing to Skyharp, who was speaking of her past.

To Ivy, it should all be a traumatic past.

By Skyharp’s attitude, it should be obvious that the story was her delusion, all the feedback and behavior of others could be twisted in any way.

It was likely that because of these years of violations, Ivy lost all hope on women, and fell in love with his own core totem

Chapter 467: Glittering Pool 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"That was the best time of my life." Skyharp said calmly, as though she was immersed in the past, her mouth curled into a smile.

Garen didn’t say anything. He recalled Ivy’s reaction when he met Skyharp, and it seemed that he didn’t have any feeling towards her at all.

Could it be that Ivy had been violated for far too long, so long that he got addicted himself?

Garen rubbed his chin in thought.

"What embarrassing things are you thinking now?" Skyharp suddenly reacted, and stared at Garen as she spoke.

"Nothing" Garen firmly denied. "I was just thinking, perhaps Ivy did have some feelings towards you. Who knows if he was half hesitant about it, he might get used to it after a few times."

Skyharp had a face filled with realization.

"When you said so, I felt it too." she nodded her head slowly.

"Then it all checks out." Garen smiled. "Pursue your love bravely, that is the world’s best thing! After all, Ivy is the shy kind."

Skyharp licked her lips, a glint of lust within her eyes.

In the instance Skyharp’s attention got diverted, he picked up his cup and pressed it against his lips.

"Speaking of which, you are knowledgeable, possess incredible abilities, and are also a Potion Master. About looks, isn’t it simple enough to swap your face? What’s there for Ivy to be dissatisfied about?"

Skyharp nodded in strong agreement.

"Indeed, he is the kind that wants things but never says it." she had a lusty smile as she spoke.

Her true nature was exposed…

Garen looked at Skyharp in disgust, the kind of female gangster nature in her had been fully exposed.

"Speaking of which." Skyharp snapped back and stopped smiling, looking at Garen.

"You’re not too bad yourself, Palace Master."

"Eer…." Garen never expected that he would get caught up in this.

Skyharp touched her chin as she checked out Garen.

Silky smooth white skin, a handsome appearance, a mysteriously evil mark on the forehead, shoulder length blonde hair. He looked extremely stern, and perfect, as he sat on the throne.

"Not bad at all… I still have a few sisters, perhaps I can introduce them to you. My daughters from the sea had been the one that’s picky; they love and hate proudly. Even though they aren’t the most capable, but quantity can make up for quality."

"About this, I already have a fiance...so it’s fine." Garen rejected immediately.

"It’s okay, so long as it’s not a shotgun marriage." Skyharp waved her hand, and the issue, off altogether. "My sisters wouldn’t mind."

But I mind….

Garen was speechless.

Looking at Skyharp's attitude, he could guess what kind of people would interact with her.

"Alright, let’s not talk about this, I have no plans for marriage for now." Garen took out his luggage, opened it, and took out the map for this journey.

"Let’s confirm the location again.." He had already memorized the map and whatnot, he was only looking for an excuse to change the topic.

**********************************

Fuuuu…..

Fuuuu…..

Fuuuu…..

Beckstone’s eyes turned purple as he staggered into the dense forest. The bushes under his feet were uneven, and a swarm of grey bugs had been flying around him relentlessly.

The long robes on him had already turned grey, and the original color could no longer be recognized. Instead, it became a hard, crusty and greyish-yellow from the mud.

As he looked up, he could see towering trees; he didn’t know where he’d ended up in.

"Eleven and the rest should have fled successfully, right?" he mumbled.

As was according to plan, he would distract the poison lady alone, whereas Beard would escort Eleven to safety, as well as those who were caught for experimentation purposes.

Poison Lady was indeed the rare expert of poison in the Three Departments. As he stumbled and fumbled, Beckstone had relied on the antidotes brought from the Society and barely managed to escape to this place.

After all, he was only a Form 4. He was never close to Poison Lady’s abilities. Even though Beard was slightly stronger as a fellow Form 4, but due to his heavy injury that he had barely recovered from with the totem in the same state, he had to return to the Society to fix it.

Suddenly, he turned back and caught a green flash at the corner of his eyes.

"She caught up!" It was Poison Lady’s Searchlight, a special Tactic; being caught in the light meant revealing your position to Poison Lady.

He had to pick up his pace and rush forward.

"Soon….. Almost there" Beckstone looked ahead and his face seemed to be complicated.

The seconds and minutes passed by. He dared not use Totem’s Light or Totem’s Power. Once he did, his location would be pinpointed by Poison Lady, and there was only a single dose of antidote with him, Whereas Poison Lady’s poison only got stronger every time. He wouldn’t know if he would be able to get through the next attack or not.

As the forest came to an end, he occasionally had to leap over the roots above the ground and avoid slanted trees. Soon, the sound of armored troops marching could be heard faintly, sounding very uniform.

Beckstone staggered over, as dried leaves and twigs crunched beneath his foot.

"Who’s there!!" the soldiers at the side of the forest shouted.

Beckstone swiftly took out a green seed and lightly threw it forward.

Bam!!!

The seed suddenly exploded, turning into smoke the shape of a skull.

Suddenly, a few wails could be heard from the side of the forest.

"Enemy ambush!!"

Dumm!!!

A straight black line was shot to the sky, and suddenly exploded into an unfolding image; it was a ferocious black dragon head.

Beckstone once again took out his last simultaneous movement seed.

"Once again, this is…." His face seemed bitter. He squashed the seed and his silhouette slowly disappeared.

The ring of light from Poison Lady had also spread from where he was, also engulfing the soldiers in the forest. The few soldiers didn’t even make a sound, and all died immediately.

"People from Nine Dragon’s Palace? Beckstone, you’re courting death!" Poison Lady’s nervous and angered voice could be heard from behind, but it was no longer approaching. Instead, it began sounding further away.

She hadn’t bothered to stay to watch the ending, instead fleeing from the area.

"That’s Poison Lady!! Report in Immediately, Poison Lady was spotted in this region!" a cold voice of a lady was heard from the forest.

"Division Three of the Special task Force has already received the news, and are rushing over now!" someone answered.

"She shall not escape this time!" The lady said with anger.

This sentence traveled into Beckstone’s ears before he completely disappeared.

The Nine Dragon Palace was the name people commonly used to refer to Black Swamp Palace. As Garen had a conflict with Poison Lady before, after its establishment, Garen ordered the establishment of the Special Task Force which totaled four divisions, and only recruited totem users with extreme poison resistance. All were at least Spiritualized, and specialized in a joint attack tactical array.

After a few fights with Poison Lady, she was heavily wounded a few times and escaped.

Her abilities relied mostly on poison. After being suppressed, her power was cut by more than half, and when these Spiritualized people grouped up, they had actually completely suppressed her.

The four divisions completely surrounded her. These totem users were all recruited externally, and each of them were bounty hunters possessing extreme amounts of experience. Among them, two leaders held old grudges with the Poison Lady, and after being recruited into the task force, these Spiritualized totem users had a desire to bring Black Swamp Palace to the next level.

The Nine-Headed Hyrda’s growth was too quick and too powerful. he controlled vast amounts of power and influences’ resources; enough to sustain large amount of external totem users. At the same time, the benefits for these totem users were exceptionally good.

Adding on the insane bonus for killing Poison Lady, a totem inheritance that is enough to reach form 4, this was the foundation which one would build a family upon!

Then, the task force doubled down on the effort

Beckstone knew this, which was why he led Poison Lady to the Black Swamp Palace personnel’s territory, latching on Garen’s power to successfully escape Poison lady’s hunt.

He owed one to Garen, by this incident.

However, the reason they were heavily wounded was indeed because of Garen. Plus, he was crossed by Garen the other time, so Beckstone himself didn’t know what to feel about Garen.

In essence, his vengeance primarily stemmed from the death of Vanderman, and Beckstone’s first love.

The main reason for Vanderman’s death was primarily himself, and also the Obscuro. In the end, the entire manor had been destroyed by them.

But because of his self-experimentation, Vanderman’s days were already numbered, so in the end, he released all the energy during the battle against Obscuro’s secret weapon.

He was a pioneer, who had offered his life to research in the name of breaking through the limits of one’s talent.

In the end, the Green Vine Sphere was not a let down either. Garen used it as a foundation to enhance the Black Swamp Palace.

Whereas Leian, whom Beckstone adored, had resolved part of the grudge after Vanderman’s death and regrets.

Garen’s actual target was Obscuro. Be it Vanderman Manor’s destruction, or the death of Dragonhawk King of the three heroes, these were all due to Obscuro. Which was why he kept expanding his influence and power with the intention to make up for the time where Goth died; by pulling all the strings possible and continuing to strengthen himself, gaining power from every huge incident and waiting for a good time to move.

Beckstone actually felt that Garen had a laxed attitude towards him, as his real target was Obscuro.

There will be a war between Obscuro and Black Swamp Palace one day.

Which is why he planned this; to use Black Swamp Palace to fight the Obscuro’s spy Poison Lady. In the end, he did succeed.

The special task force had all started pursuing Poison Lady. There should be another large-scale battle that ensued. Like experienced hunters, slowly ensnaring the Poison Lady, who was only good with poison.

*************************

In the outskirts of Caeserton.

The night sky was blanketed with stars.

There was a thin, white, hemispherical screen covering the entire compound of Kovitan, like a toppled bowl, clear beyond comparison.

Under the night skies, a mountainous region spanning tens of thousands of kilometers laid to the screen’s southwestern direction

Within a black mountain valley.

A large lava ball emerged in the middle of the valley.

The lava ball kept rotating, and the lava inside moved along with it, radiating large amounts of heat and light. Just like a giant volcanic whirlpool, it emanated a faint rumbling sound.

Chapter 468: Glittering Pond 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The sky was suddenly filled with hawks’ cries.

More than ten Giant Hawks with faintly glowing yellow eyes slowly descended from the sky.

Their sharp claws were carrying a black horse-drawn carriage with four wheels.

The carriage was the size of a small house, and it was unusually wide and neat.

Bang!

A dull noise rang out, and the carriage landed on the ground. Its four wheels shook, then rolled on the ground for a moment, before being obstructed by a few protruding stones on the floor, and ceasing all movement.

A crashing sound could be heard as the carriage door was pulled from left to right, finally opening before two figures jumped out.

Garen looked at the Lava Ball that cast the surroundings of the valley in a fiery glow, while a look of admiration appeared on his face subconsciously.

"Looks like this place has been arranged pretty well."

"There are a lot of monster nests in the vicinity, so we have no choice but to be alert at all times. However, there will be slightly more of the crystals for consumption here," said Skyharp, nodding. "Let’s go."

Garen nodded, clapping his hands lightly. The Giant Hawk pulled the carriage immediately, and flew upwards again, before flying towards the road.

He took big steps towards the Giant Lava Ball, and after a few strides, he had quickly crossed a distance of more than ten meters.

Garen walked directly towards the Giant Lava Ball, before colliding into it harshly.

Whoosh!

After the soft noise rang out, his entire body suddenly entered the Lava Ball.

This sequence arrangement was extremely natural, as Garen had only felt a faint gust of hot air throughout his surroundings, very mildly, as he felt that his body had only become slightly warmer.

A sea of red appeared before his eyes, and he realized that he had already entered the interior of the Giant Lava Ball.

In front of him was a cylindrical passage, and the bottom of the walls were completely made up of lava that was still rolling around continuously, emitting terrifying heat and red light.

The passage extended towards the front continuously, and Garen found himself walking on the passageway unconsciously, while Skyharp followed behind him closely.

Both of them seemed to have an invisible protective layer that separated them from direct contact with the lava, and made walking through the passageway as simple as taking a normal walk, without any differences at all.

Garen happily looked at the lava wall surrounding him, unconsciously nodding his head slightly.

"This Tactical Formation is not bad, worthy of Master Calingan. A simple arrangement that was enough to integrate the local environmental requirements and allow man-made work to meld into nature."

He outstretched his hand to touch the right wall surface, and red lava stuck on his hand, releasing endless puffs of white smoke.

"Master Calingan excelled at Heirloom research, this was the work of one of his old friends, and this lava is not actually real, but merely an illusion," Skyharp explained. "After these passages, Glittering Pond will be right inside."

Garen nodded.

Both of them sped up their footsteps, and continued walking down the middle of the lava passage.

They passed through many turnings, and soon, the black exit finally appeared in front of them.

Garen’s toes stepped on the ground lightly, before he dashed out of the passage all of a sudden.

Before his eyes was a sea of purple and red.

His eyes quickly got used to the constantly changing light rays, and as Garen stood at the exit of the lava passage, and looked at the scenery before him.

Between the valley, the entire floor had been submerged by purple-red colored streams, forming a purple-red lake. It looked like a large purple-red mirror, and the lake reflected the night time moonlight, forming purple-red halos, even dyeing the night sky in red as well.

The reflection of the purple-red moonlight shook in the water, causing the large black silhouettes that were swimming in the water to be faintly seen.

The lava passage was at the bank of the purple-red river, and at their ends stood the stone walls of the valley.

Initially, at the entry point of the valley, there was a large circular depression in the ground, and now it was filled with water, forming a large circular purple-red lake.

The purple-red water inside the lake flowed slowly and silently.

Garen walked towards the side of the lake and crouched down, before outstretching his hands and cupping some water.

Strangely enough, when he cupped the purple-red lake water, it suddenly turned into normal clear water, and was incomparably clear.

The cool lake water dripped out between his fingers slowly, and flowed back into the lake.

Garen stood up, looked at the deep part of the lake from afar, faintly noticing a small isle there.

"Hold on for awhile, the garrison in this area will come and meet us soon, since we have yet to release our arrival instructions," Skyharp said behind him quietly.

Garen nodded.

Both of them waited quietly, but before half a minute had passed, two little ferries floated towards them slowly on both sides of the surface of the lake. On the black ferry stood three Totem Users and soldiers in black wooden armor.

The ferry docked beside the bank quickly, and the soldiers hurriedly disembarked onto the bank, bending on single knees on the ground in front of the two people.

"Welcome Palace Master and Elder!" Their voices were unusually orderly, an obvious sign that this was due to prior training.

While they spoke, dark clouds floated up from the lake suddenly, quickly forming a human figure that landed beside the bank.

"Palace Master? Sister Skyharp, why have you arrived suddenly?" Elder Wukang still remained in his old ways. He wore a black robe, his ears adorned with large pearl earrings that were unusually eye catching.

"Barney, you resume arranging people to patrol. Fiona, since I’m here, you return to the replenishing tower, and be alert about your surroundings at all times," Wukang commanded the Totem Users that had disembarked onto the bank earlier.

When both of the Totem Users saw that Garen did not object, they followed their leader and left.

Garen had transferred his authority to Wukang to manage everything here, so naturally, he had no objections.

"Go directly to Glittering Pond," said Garen softly.

"Alright," Wukang nodded, and walked towards the lake immediately, while a thin layer of dark clouds floated beneath his feet, lifting his body up instantly, not allowing him to touch a single drop of lake water.

Dark clouds appeared precisely below Garen and Skyharp’s feet as well, supporting both of them, displaying Wukang’ powerful control.

The three of them immediately moved towards the isle in the center of the lake.

"This entire valley is Glittering Pond," explained Wukang simply. "At first, we didn’t believe it either, but after we collected water from Glittering Pond, we finally understood the relationship between these places."

He paused. "There is an isle in the middle of the lake, on the isle is a wilted purple tree, with many purple-red peach shaped holes growing on the tree top."

"Since they are holes, why do you say that they’re growing?" Garen asked.

"I don’t really know how to put it." Wukang thought for a moment, as if he was thinking of words to describe it. "There are a lot of peach shaped holes on the trunk and branches of the wilted tree, and there is a purple-red membrane layer inside that lights up. It also resembles frosted glass, and cannot be broken easily. When the time comes, you will understand once you see it."

Soon, the isle at the center of the lake gradually became clearer.

There was a single lonely black wilted tree on the isle, and from afar, it looked like purple-red eyes were growing on the trunk of the dead tree. They released faint purple-red glows.

Excluding the top of the trunk, the purple-red eyes covered the tree branches and tree top, as if they were embedded inside the wood, and were there naturally.

Garen and the two others reached the isle quickly, and soon stepped onto the ground of the isle in the middle of the lake.

The wilted tree was nearer to them now, and after stepping on the uneven ground, Garen stood in front of the wilted tree instantly.

The ten-over meter tall wilted tree appeared threatening, like the sharp claws of a demon in the dark, looking somewhat ferocious.

Garen’s toes moved slightly, before his whole body leaped forwards and floated upwards, while a gush of purple-red lake water appeared below his legs in midair at the same time, supporting him as he floated through midair.

He floated in front of one of the purple-red eyes in the middle of the tree branches.

Garen halted his silhouette, and stretched his hand out to gently touch the membrane inside the hole.

Some of it was hard and cold, and felt like touching frosted glass. It was not as weak as it looked.

He retracted his hand, and suddenly realized that there was a sticky purple-red liquid on his fingers.

"That’s Glittering Water," Wukang explained behind him from the bottom.

Garen looked at the liquid on his fingers slowly, and true enough, dots of purple-red light were faintly glowing there.

"How much Glittering Water have we collected?" he asked softly.

"About ten people’s worth, according to the rules, I have one portion, so there will be nine portions inside the storage. One portion should be about one liter’s worth," Wukang replied.

The Elder in charge of guarding the mineral resources had the authority to distribute the mineral resources into tenths, and this was one of the benefits of being the stationed Elder. This rule was decided by Garen.

Garen nodded but did not say much, since it did not matter how much Glittering Water Wukang took, because for normal people, although it had healing abilities, as for evolving effects, it could only be used for the bodies of low-levelled Totem Users. This thing was not allowed to be taken outside, and in the end, if it was not used inside the palace, it would be substituted for other resources or knowledge.

It was just like how Blizzard spent so many consecutive days inside the hidden book collection hall borrowing books and doing research, when the price he paid in exchange for reading was only that his Contribution Points were depleted.

Contribution Points could only be obtained by contributing inside the palace. It could be exchanged for knowledge, riches, Totems, and resources, among others.

Now, the only person that knew that Glittering Water was useful to the Cthulhu King was Garen, as for the Cthulhu King himself, it was unlikely that he knew how useful this thing would actually be for his wounds.

Thus, now was the best time for him to obtain Glittering Water.

"Currently, there’s only one Glittering Pond in Kovitan, which is this one, and we have already occupied it. If other people acquire the Glittering Water from the Glittering Ponds in other areas, Elder Wukang you are in charge of purchasing some of it, and any price is acceptable as long as it is not too extreme," Garen instructed him quietly.

"Understood," nodded Wukang. "I’m holding a banquet there, Palace Master and Sister Skyharp, let’s go together."

"Such a coincidence that I need a portion of Glittering Water for experiments," Garen continued.

The three of them passed the lake again, and walked towards the left side of the lake.

Soon, the stone walls of the valley on the left side of the lake floated up again, and the passageways inside the caves had already opened up, while people stood guard inside, and many material boxes and wooden buckets were also placed inside. Some of the wooden buckets were lit with piles of candles and oil lamps on top, while torches were hung on the walls inside. They illuminated the entire cave in bright candlelight.

The three of them walked into the largest cave inside the passage, and on the right side was the purple-red lake water, while bright moonlight shone on the ground of the cave. The scenery was extremely pleasant.

The cave was already filled with beautiful maids that were serving food and wine, quietly waiting for the arrival of the three people.

"I’ve already prepared Red Flying Dolphin meat. If it weren’t for the arrival of Palace Master, we would not have normally eaten this," Wukang chortled and said. "This thing can make up for many things! Mm hmm… It will greatly increase one of our manly abilities!" He rushed towards Garen, while a wretched smile that all men understood appeared on his face.

"Aren’t these just a few pieces of Red Dolphin rashers? They taste alright," Skyharp said simply.

"That’s true, that’s true. Big Sis, you are an expert in this field," Wukang quickly smiled apologetically.

"I’ve tasted various types of rashers ever since I was young, they don’t taste like much, but are just quite chewy, and are not as tasty as Mimi," replied Skyharp in a tone of trained indifference.

Chills suddenly ran down Garen’s spine, this woman, Skyharp looked quiet, but was within her cold exterior hid a surprising amount of experience.

Chapter 469: Information 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The three people sat down to begin the feast, while a continuous supply of dishes were served onto the table.

Having a meal in such a simple environment was a first for Garen.

Cold wind gushed inside from the cave opening, and the dishes that were just served quickly became cold.

They did not hold back, and began to place the dishes on the warming jar in front of them, using the chemical reaction of the warming stones to reheat the food. It was as if everyone had their own personal hot pot.

The Red Flying Dolphin flesh was very soft, but also chewy at times and tasted like beef, while its surface was soaked in a dark red sauce, making it taste slightly sweet.

Garen ate a few pieces, then took some fresh vegetables, before putting his knife and fork down.

One of the Totem Users who stood on the side, now came forward with the Glittering Water they had collected.

A thumb-sized crystal bottle was placed in front of Garen, and the clear bottle was filled with sticky purple-red liquid, faintly reflecting a silver sand like glow.

Garen picked it up and shook it, while the liquid inside flowed slowly, but did not make any shaking noises.

"Currently, how many powers around us are also seeking the Glittering Water?" he asked immediately.

"Most of the powers are out of the picture already." Wukang smiled, before he took a cup of blue alcohol and sipped it. "If I had yet to secure the situation even after Palace Master’s arrival, wouldn’t that just mean that I’m useless?"

Garen was struck with a bout of sudden realization, when he remembered Wukang’ terrifying battle record.

During the conflict on a cloudy day, he had single-handedly killed more than ten professionals, and although they were all inferior Form 4’s, without any specialized Ultimate Techniques or strong Totem abilities, this still showed that he was truly amazing.

More than half of Kovitan’s Form 4 citizens had been massacred instantly, and many powers would reorganize their strategies after this massacre.

The citizen Totem Users were not strong in the beginning, but now for some reason, it seemed as if Wukang was enough to repress all the citizen Totem Users.

"Actually, Palace Master had arrived at a great time, because I’ve just received some news here." The smile on Wukang’ face disappeared while his true expression came through. "Daniela has now reached its key moment, as the war between Obscuro Society, the Cthuhuism Society, and the Daniela Royal Family has already turned fiery. For now, they don’t have the time or energy to focus on us or Ender over here."

"What do you mean?" Garen picked up his glass and sipped it slowly.

"I have friends in Daniela, and they pass messages for me, so if Palace Master wants to occupy the Glittering Pond, now is the best chance," Wukang nodded and said.

Garen muttered and hesitated to himself.

Frankly, he was clearer about the situation in Daniela compared to Wukang, as the Geometry Service of the Three Departments was currently standing behind the King of Daniela, contesting with Obscuro Society and Cthulhuism Society that were getting stronger each day.

The Geometry Service was facing off with Obscuro Society, while the King of Daniela went up against Cthulhuism Society, and this was a violent, bloody Totem war. According to the original historical events, the death toll caused by this war could not be estimated as well. Countless inheritances, research results, and technical information were all destroyed in this major war.

As for the other two remaining main departments, they were currently containing the monster nests that were reproducing rapidly, their professional collectors were continuously raiding these monster’s nests, and were soon completely dragged into the mud.

When the Nest Leaders found out about the underground entryway, the balanced energies underground would surely be disrupted. The underground Elder Parliament was actually barely balanced, and the endless sea of monsters would surely be a large consumption towards the Elders.

Thus, the professionals of the two remaining main organizations were probably at the end of the world, refusing to budge with the monsters.

"We must seize the Glittering Ponds… It just depends on the timing," said Garen softly. "We want to occupy Glittering Pond, but our strength is still insufficient. The locations of the Glittering Ponds are too divided."

"There are three Glittering Ponds that don’t belong to any country. However, there are too many nests in its surrounding areas. If we cleanse them carefully, there should be no problem," said Wukang quietly. "As long as we’re careful, there are two Glittering Ponds nearby that we can occupy."

"In this aspect, Wukang, please arrange the necessary manpower," Garen nodded. "It’s not convenient for me to show myself, so you can request for extra support directly from the palace."

"I won’t need that many Totem Users, only Totem Users who are able to support Tactical Formations will be sufficient," replied Wukang in a slightly arrogant tone. During this Great War, the Form 4’s in their surroundings had almost been cleansed completely without the use of high-end threats, as those were only used as preparations for surprise attacks by ignorant monsters that only lived by basic instincts.

"How long do you need to complete it?"

"Within half a month’s time. There should be no problem."

"I’ll live here temporarily as well then," Garen nodded.

Skyharp stood on the side and opened her mouth to speak. "You didn’t come all the way here just for this right?"

Garen smiled but did not answer. Other than coming here to look at the Glittering Pond and Glittering Water for himself, he still had other plans, or perhaps, things he was awaiting.

The Cthulhu King would soon realize the importance of the Glittering Water to him, and by then, he would definitely come for his head.

Although Garen himself was standing on the same stage as the Three Departments and the Royal Alliance, the ones that the Cthulhu King was opposing was not just the King of Daniela, because compared to Daniela, they disliked Obscuro Society just as much.

Garen would just wait, wait for the Cthulhu King’s invitation.

All the powers that occupied Glittering Ponds would receive the Cthulhu King’s invitations to exchange Glittering Water with them.

As long as his Glittering Water was sufficient, Garen would be able to exchange it for Cthulhu’s Origin from the Cthulhu King. That was one of the core items of the Cthulhu’s strength.

Cthulhu’s Origin was an item that Garen absolutely had to obtain, and according to original historical events, Cthulhuism Society had exchanged its one and only Cthulhu’s Origin with Obscuro Society. For everyone else, it could increase Totem potential, and upgrade the effect of evolution levels.

As for Garen himself, although he did not know its uses, he absolutely could not let Obscuro Society obtain it, because when Obscuro Society’s two main Marshalls obtained the Cthulhu’s Origin, their powers increased greatly, and they achieved terrifying peak levels.

Meanwhile, after the chaos at Daniela, Hellgate had finally awakened. Then, the situation regarding the war was completely reversed.

The main opponent of the Royal Alliance had changed from monsters to the Obscuro Society. Hellgate would use his temporary strong powers to launch a surprise attack on the Three Departments. After the siege, he would finally be established as the strongest in the world.

Since it was effective against the Obscuro Society Marshalls, it would definitely be effective against Garen as well.

Therefore, they definitely could not lose the Glittering Water. Hellgate would awaken soon, reducing the time Garen had left.

After their meal, Garen stayed beside Glittering Pond.

While researching the Glittering Water, he waited for the arrival of the Cthulhu King quietly.

As time passed, he gained new knowledge about the special abilities of the Glittering Water as well.

*********************

Inside the pitch black stone cave.

Garen sat cross-legged while the sticky purple-red liquid wrapped around him like a snake, swirling around his body in a slow dance.

In the darkness, this liquid gave off a faint purple-red glow, and was unusually beautiful.

Surrounding Garen’s body were sharp, bright red crystal spikes, and all these spikes extended out of the walls towards Garen. The spikes glowed with faint white light, and reflected off the spikes onto the walls of the stone cave.

After an unknown amount of time, Garen opened his eyes slowly.

He looked at the purple-red Glittering Water that danced around him.

"Is the analyzed conclusion ready, Saiah," he said softly.

"The analysed conclusion is ready. Would you like to proceed with second level deepening?" A cold male voice echoed throughout the stone cave. This was the latest Forger system that had been installed recently, the Saiah System, which was an intelligent management system that Master Calingan had hurriedly installed. It was equivalent to intelligent computer technology, and could manage the entire Glittering Pond’s defense and internal systems.

Almost two weeks had passed since Garen’s arrival here. He would constantly practice his Secret Techniques every day, and at the same time, he would research the contents and uses of the Glittering Water. After undergoing various experiments, the contents and uses of today’s Glittering Water would reach a conclusion soon.

"Send out the report then," Garen sat on the floor and instructed softly.

"Acknowledged, please hold on…" Saiah paused, and soon, countless white halos moved along the spikes, and gathered towards Garen’s direction.

Shh shh shh…

More than ten sharp points of the red crystals released white light at the same time.

The white light expanded instantly, and formed translucent screens of various sizes. Rows of experimental statistics and possible analyses and conclusions were quickly displayed on top.

Garen’s eyes continuously scanned across the experimental statistics and conclusions. While his brain processed all of this quickly, as he analyzed and calculated the results once again.

After an unknown amount of time, the ten screen of various sizes in his surroundings shrunk and disappeared, while Garen let out a faint sigh of relief. The probable conclusions were already out.

"Extremely strong poisons that can withstand corrosion, displaying strong bone regenerative abilities. Glittering Water…" Looking at the purple-red liquid that danced around him, Garen nodded faintly. "After dilution, it could be used to create natural wound healing medications, and if we sold it, the effect would be pretty good."

Suddenly, the red dot on the left side of Garen’s forehead darkened again.

But a look of joy appeared on Garen’s face suddenly.

While he closed his eyes and experienced the dark spaces of his mind, the Nine-Headed Hydra that was occupying the space inside currently only had six heads left, and looked unenthusiastic.

Three hydra heads had already been consecutively refined by his Secret Techniques, and even though the Nine-Headed Hydra had strong Life Force, it would still feel abnormally weak.

Furthermore, the extreme rejection reaction that he faced from the Nine-Headed Hydra made it impossible for Garen not to pause the transfer road map of his Secret Techniques.

He looked at his Attribute Pane carefully, and noticed another breakthrough in his Secret Technique Pane.

‘Black Water True Technique (Originally the Myriad Water Jasper Technique): Seventh level (Seven levels in total). Powerful control over all matter in liquid form.

Poisons have been strengthened by three levels, regeneration abilities have been strengthened by three levels.’

Once his Secret Techniques had absorbed the Nine-Headed Hydra completely, Garen would properly enter Form 5 then.

If the situation allowed it, Garen’s best method currently would be to find a place to hide, so that he could allow the Nine-Headed Hydra to fuse into his Secret Techniques completely, and then only come out. Unfortunately, Obscuro Society’s development would not give him so much time.

He murdered so many of Obscuro Society’s people, and destroyed so many of their bases, so obviously both sides would be as incompatible as fire and water. Once the Royal Alliance collapsed, he would be implicated as well.

Before Hellgate awakens, he needed to place his feet firmly on the ground, and even if he was unable to successfully defeat Hellgate, he had to protect himself, and the safety of those around him at least.

According to original historical events, Hellgate was killed by grown up Beckstone and others, and obviously this happened after the Great War between the Royal Alliance, the Three Heroes, and Hellgate, and the Three Heroes had been injured with serious wounds by Hellgate, and finally, Beckstone, who had been neglected this whole time, would step forward for the last blow.

Stone would also lose all of his powers here. It was the price he had to pay in exchange for the final battle.

Chapter 470: Information 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

However, the premise for all of this was that Hellgate first had to massacre and destroy a large number of the Three Heroes and Stone’s friends, relatives, and power, provoking them so that they would gather, and finally siege Hellgate together.

Meanwhile, the Elder Parliament did not show up from beginning to the end, for unknown reasons.

"There isn’t much time left…" Garen’s eyes twinkled. He held the crystal bottle that was filled with Glittering Water, and screwed on the bottle cap.

"How do I speed up the fusion, while breaking the bottleneck at the same time?"

While thoughts swirled in his mind, Garen merely exhaled in the end.

"Looks like this will still depend on the Cthulhuism Society…"

"There is an external incoming communications request, should I accept it?" Saiah’s voice rang out again.

Garen was slightly shocked. "Accept it."

There was a crackling noise.

One of the spikes in front of him immediately lit up with a dot of white light, and expanded to form a translucent crystal board, before Lala’s face was displayed on top.

"Palace Master, large scale Totem Power rebellions have appeared in the Southern areas, the Blackfield Hawk King and Obscuro Society’s soldiers have waged war against each other."

"Goth?" Garen’s eyes narrowed. "How is the situation there?"

"The Hawk King commanded his Black Shadow Army, which they claim has three thousand men, to directly confront the twenty thousand soldiers of Obscuro Society’s Annihilation Ring Army. They are winning by a landslide, and are currently enlisting people to join their army," explained Lala simply.

"Three thousand against twenty thousand? Tch tch…" Garen could not help but praise him slightly. Goth was probably Form 4 now, and although he was not Form 5, Form 4 was sufficient to suppress certain aspects of peak strength, and although it was not as important on the larger scale of the battle situation, when going up against larger powers such as facing thousands of Form 2 and Form 3 joined forces at least, it was still beyond the reach of their power.

Only Form 5’s could ignore the changes brought on by an increase in numbers, while becoming the most important power in the entire war situation.

As for Form 4 strength, three thousand against twenty thousand, this was definitely a typical example of winning a battle with fewer numbers. That would surely be recorded in history.

Lala continued speaking. "Two of Obscuro Society’s commanders are currently confronting the royals of Daniela and the Geometry Service at Royal Star Court and cannot be separated. Meanwhile, there are five armies on Obscuro Society’s frontlines, each army has at least ten thousand Totems, most of them being Silver Totems controlled by Crystal Derivators. They’re extremely powerful. This time, the Royal Alliance is probably firing back at the Kovitan siege incident." Lala took out a stack of intelligence papers and flipped through them. "Three out of Obscuro Society’s five main armies encountered frontline attacks simultaneously. The three areas seemed to move out at the same time. Even the National Service, Silver Knights, Elvart Knights, and two main armies were sieged simultaneously. This time, the strength of the raids were too strong, and although Obscuro Society was prepared, they still suffered huge losses."

Garen smiled. He already knew that according to the personalities of the department ministers, they would not just accept the assassination of the Kovitan King.

All of God Cloud’s clones suffered serious injuries, and his main body had been dragged by the Geometry Service to Daniela. No one could confirm whether the current opportunity was just a situation planned by the Three Departments. Obscuro Society had suffered serious loses this round, and their five main armies had probably accumulated many years of experience.

The mouse that was hidden in darkness assumed that it was strong enough, but when it jumped out baring its fangs and claws, it did not expect that the old cat that was playing dead would scratch it violently instead.

The Three Departments and the Geometry Service’s two strongest lords were in Daniela, while the National Service’s two commissioners, perhaps like the Secret Service’s minister and vice minister, were at the cracks of the world, engaged in a fierce battle with the highest ranking Nest Leaders. But they could also be in Ender, investigating the origins of the Giant Angel Stone Sculptures that raided Kovitan.

"Is there anymore new information?" Garen cleared his thoughts and continued asking.

"There’s one piece of information that I personally think will be of interest to you, even though I don’t know the probability of its authenticity or falsehood." Lala’s hands quickly passed a piece of information over.

After a series of crackling noises, a translucent screen expanded on Garen’s right side, and a black instrument with white words was displayed there.

‘Nest Leader’s ranking list’

After scanning through the list, Garen’s was one of complete focus on the ranking list.

All this while, when Obscuro Society had accidentally released the Black Copper contamination resulted in the formation of Aberration monsters and terrifying nests of various sizes. However, no one had added them up as a whole. Thus, nobody knew the true number of these Nest Leaders, and they had little knowledge about them as well. As for those for had achieved Form 4 and 5 powers, no one knew about that either.

Although, now that someone had apparently released a ranking list of the Nest Leaders, it was likely that this would greatly impact the other powers.

This was a chance for him to understand the Nest Leaders fully through direct observation.

Lala took this time to retreat as well, leaving Garen to begin investigating this information alone.

The second page of the information marked the source that arranged the information: Elder Parliament.

"Of course, only that force would have enough power to clarify this kind of intelligence." Garen was aware that this piece of information was something that only the highest level of the Royal Alliance had the right to know.

Since he had become the Black Swamp Palace Master, one of Kovitan’s Four Gargantuans, he had naturally reached this level as well. If it was merely peak Form 4 strength, it would not be classified as such confidential information.

Garen flipped to the third page immediately.

The third page and the first two pages were completely different.

The page was filled with silver characters that resembled tadpoles that swam around slowly, as if they were alive, and these completely unrecognizable silver tadpoles drifted around constantly, and could not be seen properly at all.

But strangely, Garen’s eyes were currently looking at a completely different scene, he did not see characters that were swimming around, instead, he saw a beautiful painting that accompanied the written explanations and records above.

This was confidential information that only peak Form 4’s had the right to read, and their peak Form 4 Totem Light would be able to filter out the light that was reflected off this information, and after going through a specialised reaction sequence, it would form the information and words that were now displayed in Garen’s eyes.

‘Nest Leaders worthy of attention number seven hundred and sixty-two in total. This is the total number obtained from the ocean islands of the East and West Continents, and also includes the polar circles.

The Elders of the Elder Parliament, and their disciples, had spread out to various parts of the world to collect huge swathes of information that surpassed the expectations of each area in each country.

This number that currently exceeded seven hundred was constantly changing, as the Nest Leaders themselves would engage in internal strife and eat each other because of the food chain.

Out of the seven hundred over Nest Leaders, there were over a hundred that were sentient, and were mainly scattered around the West Continent, Antarctic Continent, oceans, and East Continent. The East Continent had the least of them, but because Obscuro Society tyrannically drove the Nests to battle against Kovitan, it caused dissatisfaction among the intelligent Nest Leaders in the other areas, and currently, two intelligent-type Nest Leaders had already reached the East Continent areas from the ocean. Thus, the correspondence aims to dispute the information that was released to the East Continent.

The information had already explained the situation clearly.

Garen continued reading.

‘The Nest Leaders that arrived in the East Continent naturally have conflicted feelings towards Obscuro Society, if it is possible, it could be used to our advantage.

Below was the information regarding the two Nest Leaders that arrived in the East Continent. Within the existence of over seven hundred terrifying Nest Leaders, they exist within the top twenty ranks, and this existence is the main force confronting the Elder Parliament. Obscuro Society’s unauthorized violations of the agreement caused their dissatisfaction.’

Below that was the main information.

Mud Mammoth: Tenth rank, Ten Thousand Mammoth Nest Leader. A prehistoric creature that was awakened from the deep ice layers by the Black Copper contamination, ability assessment: Higher level Form 5.

Abilities obtained ---- shapeshifting, Size Multiplication skill, Muddy Earth skill, Mammoth Howl, Earth Shaker, others unknown.

Height ---- Around 3 meters in its normal state, full size after shapeshifting is 36.2 meters. Weight ---- 124 tonnes.

Talents ---- Its entire body can turn into mud at any time, making it immune from attacks that are Form 4 and lower.’

Below it was a dark blue elephant that was standing upright on two legs like a person, clad in grey-brown leather armor, holding a large black hammer upside down in its hand, while the hammer was filled with sharp metal spikes.

This Mammoth had three elephant trunks that resembled tentacles and made threatening gestures in midair.

The painting was still moving, and it displayed the image of the Mud Mammoth perfectly, especially its three trunks, and the end of each trunk had the structure of a hand, while each trunk held a dark blue dagger.

This was a terrifying war machine.

Garen inhaled a breath of cold air; this type of monster was apparently immune to all attacks that were lower than Form 4! By looking at its size, its terrifying strength was already obvious. It also possessed strong abilities that could probably be effective in large ranges.

Upon flipping to the next page, he noticed that the Mud Mammoth’s battle records were listed there. In three major battles, one of which was with Obscuro Society’s Marshalls in the West Continent, the results were two losses with serious injuries, in which they were saved and taken away from the experimental area. The other two instances were single-sided mass destructions, and two of Obscuro Society’s Totem armies in the West Continent were destroyed by its hands.

It possessed the most terrifying attack ranges of all the Nest Leaders that existed.

Next was the second Nest Leader.

‘Psychedelic Demon: Fourteenth ranking, Illusion Demon Nest Leader. Terrifying existence of unknown sources, ability assessment: Lower level Form 5.

Abilities obtained ---- Phantom Teleportation, Spiritual Explosion, Spiritual Temptation, Puppet Control. Others unknown.

Height ---- Around two meters. Weight ---- Similar to a regular person.

Talents ---- Permanent Attack Deflecting Force Field, any attacks directed towards it will encounter its Deflecting Force Field, similar to Distorted Beads, except that its deflecting powers are not very strong. Immune to the majority of Totem abilities that are below Form 4.

Below it was a picture of the Psychedelic Demon.

This monster’s body size was similar to that of a regular human male, except that its body was shrouded in a layer of red-grey human skin, and even its face was covered completely, as if it was airtight.

Jester hat-like horns grew out of the top of its head, while it lacked ears, a nose, or even a mouth, making its entire face devoid of a normal human’s five sensory organs. The only thing there was a large ‘S’ shaped wound, where blood would occasionally flow out slowly.

The Demon assumed a squatting pose, while sharp red claws could be seen on both of its hands, making it look extremely strange.

Both of the Nest Leaders that had arrived in the East Continent looked like they were not to be messed with, making it obvious that their arrival was to counter the Obscuro Society’s nest luring incident.

Garen began to think deeply about the results that he would be able to gain from this, and the probable benefits as well.

He was currently about to enter Form 5, and if his powers developed enough to cooperate with the Flash Screen, he would probably possess enough power to withstand mid-range Form 5’s, but in comparison to the Mud Mammoth’s higher level Form 5, the difference was still too great. Moreover, only his explosive energy was strong, but during battles, after a long period of time, he would not be able to it anymore. Unless he entered Form 5 completely and fused the entire Nine-Headed Hydra.

But this was enough, as long as he had the right to stand in front of him to have a face to face conversation, that would be sufficient.

"Cthulhu’s Origin, I don’t know if it will produce any effect on me…"

This thing only required sufficient amounts of Glittering Water, which would probably be purchasable, except that Obscuro Society would not allow something that they had set their eyes on to escape so easily. The final result depended on which party possessed stronger powers.

God Cloud and the other Marshall would definitely not let the matter drop. This time, he would definitely need to stand directly before them. It would happen soon, once the Cthulhu King discovered the uses of the Glittering Water…

Chapter 471: Leave 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Somewhere in Daniela

Within the ruins of the devastated city, groups of figures with red scarves on their heads and black, sheer fabric on their bodies passed through quietly. They were completely silent with their heads bowed, while their lips were chanting unknown verses with sincerely devout expressions plastered on their faces.

The figures appeared occasionally from the underground caves on the borders of the ruins, which quietly observed the group that passed by. They looked on in awe while the group passed by their ‘gate’.

Within the ruined city, they were a few abandoned single-story houses that still remained; they were fortunate enough to still be in perfect condition.

A struggle between nest monsters had just occurred here, and the followers of the Cthulhuism Society were currently patrolling the area, cleaning the remains of the monsters.

Inside the empty space of a narrow single-story house, a black figure was currently leaning against the wall, panting heavily.

Pfoo… Pfoo…

It seemed as if he was about to spit his lungs out, as his entire chest rose up high, before deflating quickly.

In the darkness, this person’s eyes were unusually bright. Half a day had passed, and he was still leaning against the wall closely, except that his breathing had gradually become calmer, and he could begin to hear the movements on the other side of the wall.

"Is anything happening?" Another voice echoed throughout the darkness.

"No, pfoo… The patrol team just passed by," The man who was leaning against the wall shook his head. "Looks like it will be safe for now."

"Pfft! Those Cthulhuism Society brats! Sooner or later I’ll kill all of them!" The voice in the darkness had become much clearer, and it was apparently the voice of a very young boy.

"How is Elin?"

"Her condition is still not good, she’s currently sick with a high fever, so we need to find some anti-fever medicine soon!" The boy paused. "Have I lit up?"

"Just light it now." The man walked away from the wall, and came towards a deeper part of the house.

Shh…

A flame the size of a soybean appeared, and quickly lit up a white candlestick.

The pale yellow light quickly illuminated half of the little house’s space.

There was a little wooden yellow bed in the middle of the house, and a thirteen to fourteen-year-old girl was lying on the bed while a white-haired boy sat next to her. The boy’s eyebrows were slightly wrinkled, clearly forming three furrowed lines, making him look abnormally old.

Currently, he was looking at the girl on the sick bed worriedly.

"We need to go out and find some medicine!" The boy said in a resolute tone.

"There will definitely be people hunting for us outside. Going out right now would be looking for death," said the man with his eyebrows furrowed. "Even if you have Wing God Arms, you still won’t be able to escape from Havana’s grasp. There are at least two of Benla’s main chiefs have been sent to capture us, we cannot take any risks."

"Do you want me to see my little sister die?!" The boy’s face turned cold.

"I’m stopping your idiotic actions!" said the man, shaking his head, he began searching for something in his arms. "When I went out earlier, I found this."

He took out a little black circular box at once, and threw it at the boy.

The latter caught it with one hand and looked at the box, a puzzled look appeared on his face suddenly.

"What is this?"

"A Radio."

"Radio?" A surprised expression appeared on the boy’s face instantly. "So you’re saying.. "

"Of course. With this, we will be able to communicate with the outside world and receive messages as well," nodded the man confidently. "Perhaps we will be able to find a way to obtain anti-fever medicine, too."

"This time, as one of the main Eighteen Cthulhus, Havana will probably be summoned by the Cthulhu King. As long as he leaves this place temporarily, we have a chance," said the man in a serious tone. "Rumor has it that the people from Obscuro Society and the Three Departments have arrived, so if you can get closer to the Ancestral God Pillar, and inherit the Ancestral God’s strength, then…"

"It won’t be that simple," the boy interrupted him. "The Cthulhu King will not let us off so easily. He may not know that I can inherit the Ancestral God’s strength, but he will definitely not let any accidents occur."

"Then what do we do?" The man became impatient.

"We cannot rush this, when more forces arrive, the more likely it will be for our chances to increase. The Three Departments and Obscuro Society are both outsiders, they do not have great influence towards the foundation and arrangement of the Cthulhuism Society. Their thousand-year-old arrangements are not to be messed with, thus, this requires proper consideration…" The boy thought deeply.

*****************

Two weeks later…

Garen had spent almost a month at Glittering Pond, and besides practicing Secret Techniques, the only other thing he did every day was research Glittering Water, or take the radio and adjust it randomly, receiving noises from the outside world with different frequencies.

Occasionally, he would go out with Wukang to investigate the lower ranked Aberration Creatures in their surroundings, and although the Potential Points that they obtained were pitifully little, it was better than nothing. The higher ranked monsters in the area had been wiped out by Wukang, making it impossible for them to find stronger ones unless they traveled to further places.

Before long, the people from the Cthulhuism Society finally arrived.

In the afternoon, tiny raindrops fell outside the door of the main hall while slight breezes blew in, bringing coldness and dampness inside.

Two men in black bull horn helmets and red clothes sat upright on the right side of the hall inside the stone cave. Their gazes were focused Island Master Wukang, who sat on the throne.

"Our demands from the Cthulhuism Society are very simple. We must be given the authority to take over the Glittering Water and this Glittering Pond. This is the most basic baseline," said one of the barefaced, light green-eyed young men, in out of place Kovitan language. When he spoke, his pronunciation was a mess.

"Is everyone from the Cthulhuism Society so rude when they come out?" chided one of the female bodyguards beside Wukang.

"We’ve already been very patient, very polite," said the young man coldly.

"You!" The bodyguard became furious suddenly, as her hand reached for the handle of the knife by her waist. The other bodyguards in the hall also became sterner as well, and they, too, held onto the handles of their weapons, as if chaos would erupt at any moment.

Wukang raised a hand, signaling them to suppress their agitation. He was more aware of the Cthulhuism Society’s strength compared to anyone else, as each of the Eighteen Cthulhus were Form 4 or above, while the Cthulhu King had achieved the unparalleled peak Form 5 and was listed as the strongest master in Daniela next to the King of Daniela himself.

Unlike Kovitan that relied on Precious Heirlooms to establish its country, Daniela fully relied on destroying established governmental regimes, and their internal wars never stopped.

Perhaps, when Kovitan was the size of an iron plate, they would have been able to rely on Precious Heirlooms to be on equal footing with Daniela. But now, a big loss in strength had caused Kovitan to be divided into four powers, and now lost their right to have face to face conversations with Daniela.

Merely relying on the Black Swamp Palace’s strength would make it likely that they would be caught when they went up against the Eighteen Cthulhus, and more likely when it was the Cthulhu King, as well as the trump card they kept in the darkness.

From their opponent’s perspective, Black Swamp Palace was merely a small, remote power, and was not worthy to be paid any mind.

Wukang knew that although he was currently in charge here, in reality the true Palace Master on the throne was Garen, except that the outsiders were unaware that Garen and Skyharp had arrived already.

Although Garen had arrived, he had waited around here for such a long time, making it obvious that he was waiting for something. Perhaps he was waiting for the people from the Cthulhuism Society?

Wukang had some faint idea that perhaps Palace Master had expected this incident long ago?

"Both of you don’t have to panic, the Glittering Water is something I can provide you with. However, giving you the Glittering Pond is something I cannot do. This resource is something we losers obtained with a high price, so to allow you to have it with just a few words, do you really think that would happen?" said Wukang with a polite smile, because although his opponents were just two Form 3 Totem Users who were not even at the edge of Spiritualization, he was not angry at all, showing that his patience ran deep.

"Tch!" Unexpectedly, the young man sneered. "Of course, Lord Cthulhu had long expected that you would not give up so easily He will arrive soon; the both of us are merely vanguard messengers, and within two days time, the Lord and the others will arrive, and by then… Hehe."

Wukang faintly furrowed his eyebrows suddenly.

The Cthulhus power and his own were about the same and were at the same level, except that the Cthulhus possessed a shameless ability; the indestructible Cthulhu’s Origin. Thus, if they were considered to be killed externally, they could undergo sacrificial resurrection by the Cthulhuism Society. The Origins of the Eighteen Cthulhus were placed inside the Cthulhuism Society Teachings, and could not be destroyed at all. Thus, although the King of Daniela could once march over everything, he could not counter the Eighteen Cthulhu’s Origins. Moreover, being unable to completely destroy the Cthulhuism Society’s Cthulhu’s Origin meant that the Cthulhus were almost immortal.

The main difference between Cthulhu and most Form 4’s, was that they could not die. If they were not beaten, they would resurrect again for the second, then the third time, torturing one to death.

"Not that sentence again. Our Black Swamp Palace may not be a strong force, but a few sentences won’t be enough to force us to retreat," Wukang replied casually. "As for the Cthulhu’s in-person visit, we’ll talk about it once he actually makes a move." When he encountered these strong forces in the past, he would never have dared to say such tough words as these, but now that he was the strongest person on the island, and had joined the Black Swamp Palace, obtaining absolute protection, plus the Elders backing him up, adding on to the presence of the inscrutable Palace Master, his speech had become much tougher.

His opponent was not angered either, as the young man merely sneered twice.

"Since Elder put it that way, we’ll let the Lord bring this up on his own later. We’re leaving!"

Both of them got up, and left the hall of the stone cave quickly.

Not long after both of them left, Garen and Skyharp’s silhouettes floated up and appeared on the seats on the left.

"Palace Master, you heard it all earlier, the people from the Cthulhuism Society have no plans to do business with us at all," said Wukang, looking at Garen.

"Doesn’t matter." Garen was dressed in a black robe while he sat on the seat with an indifferent expression. "If you want others to face you properly, you need to show them enough power, if not, no one would talk about business matters with an ant."

"And what do you mean, Palace Master?" Wukang seemed to have guessed what he meant, while an excited expression appeared on his face.

"Since they want us to show them our power, we’ll do just that," Garen stroked his armrests and said calmly. "They wanted to rob us, right? It’s a coincidence that I have to visit Daniela for something as well."

"I’m with you," Skyharp nodded.

"All of the Cthulhuism Society’s bases, destroy all of them. Dispatch the orders to all of the powers under the command of the Black Swamp Palace, if they see anyone from the Cthulhuism Society, don’t leave any behind." A bloodthirsty smile appeared on Garen’s face. "It’s a coincidence that I also want to witness the true strength of the legendary Cthulhu King."

"Once the death toll rises, they will naturally face you properly…" Garen’s final words echoed throughout the hall faintly, but neither Skyharp or Wukang displayed the faintest sign of fear, as their faces were filled expectant expressions instead.

****************

One day later

Red clouds floated above the Glittering Pond slowly, the clouds rolled around and gathered together, before forming a strange blood-coloured luster. It resembled thick, sticky blood, as if it was about to drip down at any moment.

"The Almighty Cthulhu Beckenson has arrived, mortals, welcome the fury of the gods!!"

A magnificent voice echoed from the clouds in the sky, like rolling thunder. The Kovitan language spoken this time was much more fluent compared to before, allowing the Totem Users, bodyguards, and soldiers who stood below to be able to understand the speaker’s voice.

Tch!!

A ray of black light pierced through the valley of the Glittering Pond suddenly. It pierced directly through the red clouds, penetrating the golden pillar of sunlight in the sky.

A black figure floated in midair between the red clouds.

Garen scanned past the red clouds in his surroundings calmly. These red clouds that rolled past constantly permeated a strong rotten stench, while the toxic smoke continuously passed through his skin and pores.

Shh…

A loud, terrifying inhaling noise could suddenly be heard throughout the sky.

Garen raised his head, while his chest sunk in deeply, as if it was a deep pit had formed there.

Hiss…

Most of the red clouds around him seemed like waves that were returning to the ocean when he sucked them in.

Within the blink of an eye, all of the red clouds in the sky cleared out immediately, before a man in a long blood-red robe appeared floating in midair.

"You dare absorb my Ten Thousand Poison Blood Clouds!!" A furious expression appeared on the man’s face.

He opened his palm, while three blood-red diamonds spun in his palm before turning into a ring, and continued turning continuously.

"True Red Blood Diamonds!!!" The man raised both of his hands up high, lifting the ring-shaped blood diamonds, while an indescribably strong blood light was released from his body, and soon the halo became fuller and more powerful until it reached a blinding stage.

It filled the entire sky, temporarily covering the sun’s rays as well.

"Let me go…" Crash!!!

Before he could finish shouting, the man was suddenly suppressed by a large hand made up of black smoke, and the terrifyingly gigantic hand that was formed by black clouds smashed the man against the ground violently, until a gigantic clear handprint had appeared on the entire rocky terrain of the ground.

Loud, shaking noises continued echoing throughout the ground.

Garen returned his hands to his side slowly in midair, as he casually looked at the Cthulhu that he had just smashed into a coma below him.

Chapter 472: Leave 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Black Water True Technique had already started to develop its powers, and when the terrifying water vapor was constantly compressed, it formed a frighteningly dense giant water hand. In an instant, before its opponent could react, it would form in front of them immediately, rendering it unavoidable. Coupled with the incomparably terrifying strength of his right hand, the increased strength from the ring of the Troll Grip was not a laughing matter.

Instantly, Garen had smashed this Cthulhu into a coma.

He outstretched a finger again, before Garen pointed it downwards and touched something.

Shh!

A ray of black light pierced through the ground like a spike, stabbing through the Cthulhu’s chest clean through.

Garen, who had fused with three Hydra heads, was getting closer to Form 5. Now he had almost obtained God Cloud’s initial power. Upon encountering Ultimate Form 4 Secret Tactics, he remained calm and steady, as one hand was sufficient to easily counter his opponent’s attacks.

This was the difference between Form 4 and 5, and while this difference was too great to describe, once the Totems were fused, Secret Techniques would be pushed to unimaginable states, allowing one to reach almost legendary stages.

Secret Techniques that were once normal after the influence of peak Totems would be able to reach unparalleled terrifying effects.

In other words, Form 5 was basically the Secret Techniques that had been trained to the point where they resembled the legendary Gargantuans.

Every Form 5 stood at the peak of their own Secret Technique, but due to cultural differences, the Form 5’s did not establish a Secret Technique martial art, but schools of thought, organizations, or parliaments.

In simpler terms, by directly killing a legendary Cthulhu, Garen had no time to brag.

Although he seemed very much at ease, this was done by using the foundation of his Troll Grip strength on his right hand.

The Nine-Headed Hydra could not be used now; releasing the Totem that was only left with six heads would mean that he was looking for death.

Excluding the Nine-Headed Hydra’s own strength, Garen could only rely on the Troll Grip and Black Water True Technique, as well as the final Flash Screen.

The giant black hand from earlier was Garen using two types of Secret Technique powers, one of which was the Troll Grip. Such terrifying power meant that it had definitely exceeded peak Form 4.

The more times the Black Water True Technique fused with the Hydra heads, the stronger it would become. It had now almost become Garen’s final trump card.

After testing the current effects of his Secret Techniques, Garen floated down and landed on the ground gently.

Skyharp and Wukang waited beside the deep pit formed by the handprint, while the surrounding Totem Users and bodyguards had already been dispersed. Only the three of them had rushed here.

"That’s a Cthulhu? Seems quite weak." Wukang stroked his chin, a relaxed expression on his face.

"He wasn’t weak, it was Palace Master that was too strong." Skyharp had seen the true result of this battle from the sidelines. Her gaze was solemn. "The Cthulhu’s final move would not have left either you or myself unscathed, but Palace Master merely…"

When she mentioned this, Wukang’ smile disappeared, while he carefully felt the remaining Totem Light within the pit. Suddenly, his expression turned serious as well.

"Frankly, if every Cthulhu was that powerful, that would truly be quite troublesome…"

"Have the others from the Cthulhuism Society been taken care of?" Garen asked quietly.

"Of course," said Skyharp, smiling. "Those people hid inside a cave two kilometers from here, they’ve all been destroyed."

Garen nodded, while the Cthulhu inside the pit melted and quickly turned into fine red sand, showing that it had completely lost all signs of life.

However Garen did not notice any changes in his Potential Point Pane, which meant that he could not use this method to get Potential Points. This made him slightly disappointed.

Suddenly, the Cthulhu’s eyelid twitched, before his eyes quickly opened.

"Nineheads, you little snake! You’re dead! You dare provoke my Almighty Cthulhuism Society! The Cthulhu King will not forgive you! Hehe… Just you wait… Everything you own is cursed to be destroyed, will all be destroyed!!"

Bang!

Garen stepped on the Cthulhu’s head with one foot before red sand was sent flying everywhere, the remains of the Cthulhu’s body finally turned into red sand completely.

"These Cthulhu’s and their undead bodies, they’ve become too arrogant." Skyharp was speechless.

"This isn’t arrogance, it’s just slight insanity," Wukang shook his head. "This aggravating tone, even someone like myself with a good temper cannot help but want to kill them."

"It doesn’t matter, we’re on the side of the Royal Alliance anyway, the Cthulhuism Society would confront us sooner or later," said Garen indifferently. "Go get ready, we’ll leave at once."

*******************

"What? You still want to go to Daniela?! Are you insane?" Beard looked at Beckstone with an annoyed look. The moment this guy gathered everyone together, he began saying things that no one could understand.

"Do you know what’s going on there right now?! Chaotic warfare, okay! Chaotic warfare! Geometry Service, Obscuro Society, Cthulhuism Society, the King of Daniela, each of them would gladly kill you a hundred times over!" Beard could not help but groan. If his society had not commanded him to take care of Beckstone’s safety, he would not have cared about an idiot like this who would jump headfirst into a fire.

At night, within the forest, three people sat by the bonfire. Unlike Beard’s look of utter incomprehension, Eleventh Royal Daughter Tina’s expression was unusually calm.

"You want to find Hannet, right?

Stone nodded slowly.

"The Cthulhu King will not forgive him."

"Will we be able to save him if we go there?" asked Tina calmly.

Stone did not reply, but continued looking at the bonfire with his head lowered.

"Since you look calm now, why do you always become frazzled during the key moments of important situations?" said Beard impatiently. "My suggestion is to return to the society immediately. I’ve received news that two important individuals have arrived at the Nest Leader’s area, and if we encounter them, it will be troublesome. Also, our Kovitan is unlike the past anymore, currently our country has been terribly divided, and has become a second-rate country instantly. Compared to Daniela and Ender…"

"It doesn’t matter, we just need to stay hidden carefully…"

"Moreover, you don’t know that our Terraflor Society had an encounter with the Cthulhuism Society once," said Beard distractedly. "If they find out that both of you have plant-series Totems, you will definitely be killed."

"There will definitely be a way," said Beckstone softly. "I cannot bear to see my friends fall into dangerous areas."

"I’ll support you," Tina nodded sincerely. "If you didn’t have this resolve, you wouldn’t be the Beckstone that I know."

"Uncle, please take Tina back to the society, I’m going to Daniela alone," said Stone suddenly.

"No way!""No way!"

Both of them said at the same time.

"If you want to go, we must go together, don’t just assume that I’m useless! If it weren't for my premonitions this time, we would not have been able to escape from the palace, right?" said Tina frankly.

A forced smile appeared on Stone’s face, as he already knew how the situation would develop.

**************

Daniela

"Recently, Totem Users from different countries have been gathering in Daniela by the masses. These masters that have gathered from Ender, Sudan, West Hong Hall Alliance, Kovitan have all increased. Before the situation reaches a more complicated stage, the designated safety departments are currently taking positive measures to maintain a balance between each group’s powers to decrease the possibility of weapon-related incidents…"

The female news reporter’s gentle voice echoed out of the radio constantly.

In the darkness, the weak girl on the bed was currently using all her energy to listen to the news.

The white-haired boy who sat beside her was carefully cutting an apple for her.

"Big Brother, listen, our people from Kovitan have arrived as well…" the girl suddenly said happily.

"I know, I know." The boy continued cutting the apple determinedly, as if he only had two indifferent replies.

Kovitan’s Totem Users had probably arrived because of the Ancestral God Pillar. It was one of Daniela’s legendary divinities, and it was rumored that any Totem User that could inherit its power would be able to instantly achieve the highest Appraisal.

For the Totem Users that had unsatisfactory Appraisal, this was very tempting.

This was not false news, as there had been instances where people had their Appraisals accidentally increased by the Ancestral God Pillar. At once, Totem Users from various countries had all gathered here.

After the battle where the Kovitan defense line was defeated, all of the monsters in the entire East Continent suffered great losses under the cleansing effect of the Ultimate Shelter. At once, all of the major forces moved out quickly to regain lost territories, while the monsters had lessened as well.

Some of the outskirts that bordered human residences had become much safer as well.

Thus, when the main environment became slightly safer, this piece of information began to spread, instantly gaining the attention of Totem Users across various lands.

"By the looks of it, the people from the Cthulhuism Society seem to be disturbing the waters, but this is beneficial as well, because it gives us a chance," said the boy quietly.

"Oh…" replied the girl, not really understanding what he meant.

***************************

Bang!!

A middle-aged man was violently smashed against a large rock, and like a struggling shrimp, he had curled up and was now rolling around, before he groaned dejectedly, struggled to get up, and ran away quickly. However, a man in red soon dragged him by his hair.

"Tell me… Where is the Seed of the Ancestral God?" asked the man in red gently.

"I… I don’t know…" said the middle-aged man in a quaking voice. "My Totems have all been destroyed by you, my lifelong efforts have all disappeared, so what else are you going to do?!"

"What am I going to do? Hehe…" The man in red giggled, and raised another hand, where a metal hacksaw had been installed in his palm. "Do you know the kind of feeling, when I drag this saw down every inch of your neck, and cut your throat open slowly?"

His voice sounded as if he was saying sweet, merciful words, without a hint of murderous intent, but a certain coldness lurked behind it.

"I… I don’t know anything… The Seed of the Ancestral God… Was snatched away by someone from Ender!! Besides that, the people from Sudan and West Hong Hall in Kovitan… They each had their own designated camps, all prime locations, and are most likely to have obtained the illumination of the Ancestral Light, accumulating the Seed of the Ancestral God!!" The middle-aged man told him everything he knew about the current situation.

"The closer the distance to the Ancestral God Pillar, the more Ancestral God Light one will receive, making its accumulated seeds stronger, this is all I know! Don’t kill me!!" The middle-aged man knew that the man in red before him was a deviant, because in the past few days, he had robbed and killed more than ten Totem Users. His actions were cruel, and his personality was cold, easily making his hair stand on end.

"Special treatment, huh? Really…" The man in red flung the prisoner in his hands away in one go, while a thoughtful expression appeared on his face.

Chapter 473: Arriving At Daniela 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Gee!!

In the sky, a black carriage was pulled by a group of black hawks. It was moving forward at high speed, and from time to time, the black hawks let out sharp cries. As they flapped their huge wings, large amounts of air current were created, bringing their body odor along.

Within a specific radius, every creature with a sharp sense of smell would retreat, to avoid conflict with this group of yellow-eyed black hawks.

In the blue sky, waves of clouds passed the carriage. Down below was a vast plain, and the yellow-green mountains were like centipedes on the green expanse. There were also deep black canyons and green lakes, with strange howls faintly came from the surface.

Garen sat in the carriage and looked out of the window. He felt a wave of desolation coming towards him.

The vast plains didn’t seem to have an end to them. As the carriage was pulled by the giant hawks, it was unclear how long it would take the reach their next destination.

A cold white color appeared on the faint sunlight. It did not carry any warmth; all it did was reflecting the paint on the surface of the carriage.

Garen placed his hands on the window, as if he were admiring the beautiful scenery below.

In the carriage, Wukang was giving a dirty look at his female guard. Both of them were like glue as they were cuddling each other; it was obvious their relationship wasn’t normal. They didn’t even care about Garen and started flirting softly.

"We have swept a few strongholds but the Cthulhuists still haven't come out. Looks like if they weren’t preparing for a more violent counterattack that they would give up temporarily to convene their forces for their internal situation." Garen turned and looked at Wukang. "What are your thoughts?"

"It depends on your purpose, My Lord." Wukang patted the female guard’s waist and raised his head to look at Garen.

"The purpose. Since the Cthulhuism Society needs the Glittering Water, if we don’t gain something from them, wouldn’t all our efforts to conquer the Glittering Pond be wasted?" Garen smiled. After the chaos in Daniela ended, Hellgate would be awakened. At that point, the Royal Alliance will be completely destroyed and the Obscuro Society would grow in strength. If he didn’t take advantage of this time to obtain an advantage and strengthen himself, he would be in real trouble.

He didn’t think he could withstand the unstoppable Hellgate.

For Beckstone to escape, many elites behind him gave up their lives to rescue him, time after time, from Hellgate’s pursuit.

However that decision was made because Beckstone was the Terraflor Society’s brightest hope. Garen himself wasn’t a genius, like Beckstone. People from the Royal Alliance also weren’t that noble to sacrifice themselves for others.

Cthulhu’s Origin, and the Seed of the Ancestral God were the two best things in Daniela. One was the root of the Chulhuism Society, while the other was the root of Daniela’s king.

The Ancestral God was also known as the Wing God. It was the iconic guardian of Daniela’s royal family, and in fact, the source of its power was from the Ancestral God Pillar.

The extent of influence of Daniela’s royal family was dependent on the extent of power of the Ancestral God Pillar that the king of Daniela could unleash.

"In Daniela, the two best things are the Seed of the Ancestral God and Cthulhu’s Origin. Although both of these are good, but our power path is already restricted. It won’t be much use to us even if we obtain it." Wukang had evidently received sufficient information from the Black Swamp Palace’s information network.

"I wouldn’t be so sure of that. No matter what, if we obtain the two things, it’s not a bad choice for us to study it, or leave it for our future generations." Garen uttered.

"You must have other plans?" Wukang laughed.

Garen didn’t answer but tilted his head to look out of the window once again.

Naturally, he would not reveal that he knew how to use Cthulhu’s Origin.

According to the original history, he gradually realized that there was another key reason the Obscuro Society’s marshalls could raise their abilities with the Cthulhu’s Origin. It was because of the adaptee.

It just so happened that Kid knew about the production of an adaptee. After questioning, Garen completely understood the secret usage of Cthulhu’s Origin.

If the Seed of the Ancestral God could raise the innate ability of totem users, Cthulhu's Origin was a treasure that could evolve the human soul.

However, since Cthulhu's Origin consists of the Cthulhu King’s indomitable will, an adaptee has to be found to separate the Cthulhu King’s will.

An adaptee naturally has the energy and spirit to fight the Cthulhu King’s will. It's the best way to separate the Cthulhu King’s will.

There was only one adaptee out of the whole of Daniella.

It was the one with the Winged-God arm, Hannet Thunderstorm.

This mere 14-year old boy was already an infamous fugitive throughout Daniela. The Cthulhuism Society was in heavy pursuit of him, hunting him down everywhere to try to utterly destroy the only counter to the Cthulhu King. However, there had been no complete solution until now.

It was obvious that the king of Daniela was backing him up.

"To Daniela, we are mere outsiders." Garen opened his mouth to speak.

"Yes. Daniel has two major forces, the Cthulhuism Society and the Royal Family. Behind them are many elites, the form fours aren’t even the key deciding factors. Daniela has already gathered the strongest forces in the whole of the East Continent." Wukang nodded in agreement. "Honestly speaking, I do not recommend we intervene. The situation is too chaotic. If we are not careful, even you, Lord Garen, would face danger."

"Then why are you willing to come along with me?" Garen asked him back.

"I want to see and experience the strength of the legendary Cthulhu King and king of Daniela." Wukang laughed. "I don't have many hobbies other than lust and fights. Three days without a fight would make me panic."

"Then you must have a lot of similarities with Blizzard."

"Fighting with the same person all the time gets old." Wukang shook his head. "After entering into fourth form, the body has greatly evolved. We have lifespans far longer than others. With such a long life, wouldn't it be boring if we don't have some fun?"

Garen smiled without saying a word.

Currently, Cthulhu King and Daniela’s king were the main players. For outsiders like them to obtain sufficient benefit, they needed an actual squad.

　　*********************

Two days later...

In the night sky, four rays of red light soared through the dark night. They looked like four red lines before they stayed suspended in the air.

The four red dots of light blocked a black carriage that was flying speedily in the sky.

Buzzz!!!

The four red dots suddenly combined to form a squared red curtain, completely blocking the carriage from progressing.

"Hands up!"

Four voices of men and women overlapped as they said the same phrase, as if they were a single voice.

"You will be punished by the Gods!"

The voice echoed countless times in the sky.

At the same time, similar squared red curtains appeared around the carriage. They were a hundred meters away. completely surrounding the carriage in the middle.

Crash...

The carriage door was swung open.

Garen and Wukang slowly leapt out. A black cloud and water vapor beneath their feet caught them respectively.

"It’s you?" Garen recognized the male leader at one glance. It was the Cthulhu that was killed by him at the Glittering Pond. "You’ve recovered completely in such a short time? You even found a few helpers?"

Even he himself was dumbfounded by that terrifying regenerative ability.

The male in red stared at Garen with hatred.

"I wasn’t fully prepared before. I never thought you would dare to come to Daniela. Hehe. I’m going to hang you upside down, skin you, preserve you and make jerky out of your meat! I’m sure the texture would be very tasty…"

Garen furrowed his brows. The other party had four Cthulhus, which were all peak fourth forms. He wasn’t afraid of getting rid of them once. But after killing them, would they be back with eight Cthulhus?

If all eighteen Cthulhus were present, not only him, even the department director would be in fear.

He did not come to Daniela to attract hatred. Being in the limelight is not a good thing at all.

He was already at Daniela’s borders. If any major thing happened again, his purpose would be disrupted.

"Are we taking action?" Wukang asked softly at the side.

"If not, should we just stand here and get beaten?" Garen gave him a glance and raised his hands to act.

Bang!!!

A frightening white pillar of light came from above.

With incredible accuracy, it hit the curtain where the four Cthulhus were. Three other similar pillars fell from the sky, hitting the remaining three curtains.

The white giant light pillar was few meters thick. It was like a sudden bolt of lightning in the dark night. It came down in a flash, leaving afterimages on the retina.

"When have you Cthulhus become the boss of Daniela’s borders?"

A clear male voice sounded in the sky.

A white-robed, middle-aged man quietly appeared before Garen’s carriage, blocking off the two parties.

As the pillars of light disappeared, the Cthulhus’ curtains had been utterly destroyed.

After retreating when the giant pillar of light struck, they now stood in a separated formation

The four Cthulhus looked in displeasure at the white-robed man.

"Ankama, the King of Holy Lake!" A big sized Cthulhu opened his mouth. Unlike the Cthulhu that Garen defeated, once he opened his mouth, the others remaining instantly kept quiet. He was evidently the one with the highest position in this temporary squad.

"Aren’t you in the valley of the Ancestral God Pillar? Why do you have the time to come here?" The Cthulhu seemed to have heavy resentment towards the white-robed man.

"I go wherever I want. No one set the rules barring me from coming here for a walk, is there?" The white-robed man, Ankama spoke in a relaxed manner. However, from his expression, he had a deep hatred for the Cthulhu party of four.

"Alright!! Count yourselves lucky. I’ll let you all go today!" The Cthulhu stared at Garen coldly. "Pray that you never meet me again! Remember, I’m the Hurricane God, Weir!"

"Sixth Brother!" The Cthulhu that was killed by Garen cried in dissatisfaction.

"Shut up! Let’s go!" Weir stared fiercely at his counterpart. He pulled back his right arm, and with a crash, pulled a red cloak to cover the four of them. The cloak rotated rapidly and became smaller and smaller, until it finally shrunk to the size of a small red cloth and disappeared, as if it were squeezed into space.

Garen and Wukang stood silently suspended in their original position. Regarding the Cthulhus, even Wukang could defeat two of them at once. Not to mention Garen, who could torture them with one hand.

They just didn’t want to draw attention to themselves. They never thought the opponent would think they were scared.

No matter how strong the Cthulhus were, they were only normal peak fourth forms.

Their level was far from Wukang’s, who was a unique fourth form with unique techniques.

As if he noticed their belittlement, the white-robed middle-aged man turned towards them.

"Do not look down on them. One Cthulhu is not frightening. When two of them are together, their powers would increase. When there are three or four of them, they would produce an evil spirit light, which multiplies the Cthulhus’ power by two or more. Moreover, the sixth ranked Hurricane God Weir was present. Even a normal fifth form would not be able to escape their wrath."

Both of them instantly turned solemn, especially Garen.

He quickly did some calculations in his mind. Four Cthulhus plus the Hurricane God. The power needed to get rid of them was actually…..

If initially he could defeat the enemy with only an arm. Now with this…..still only an arm was needed.

He paused for a moment.

He initially thought they were strong. But after calculating carefully, they were still within his grasp. Even if their power doubled up, he could still defeat them with a punch each.

He didn’t even need to use more than 20% of the Black Water True Technique.

Chapter 474: Arriving At Daniela 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You have to be careful in the future. That guy Weir obviously holds a grudge against you." The white-robed man whispered. "Let me introduce myself. I'm Ankama, the current King of Daniela's Holy Lake, one of the two kings. I was ordered to come and welcome both of you. The two Lords of your Three Departments are also at the Ancestral God Pillar."

Ankama surveyed the surroundings.

"Aren't you going to invite me to have a seat? You don't have to introduce yourselves. I've read information about both of you beforehand."

"Come up." Although Garen was displeased at the four Cthulhus, he steadied himself and returned to the carriage.

No matter what, the other party was here to help him. It would be even better for him to take advantage. When the two sides were engaged in battle and underestimated his power, he could secretly obtain Cthulhu's Origin. There was a high possibility he could obtain the adapter with the Winged-God arm.

The three of them returned to the carriage. The yellow-eyed black hawks were only mildly frightened under the protection of the tactic formation. They did not suffer any damage and continued flying forward under Garen's control.

As the three of them sat at the long table in the carriage, the girl guard served the three men some snacks and tea.

"This is our Kovitan's green tea snack. Some red fern roots were added. It tastes pretty good. You can have a try." Garen pointed.

Ankama took a snack but didn't eat. He only held it in his hand.

"Lord Garen, I heard that you've destroyed multiple Cthulhuism Society squads and temporary strongholds along your journey here? Is that true?"

"It is." Garen nodded.

"I was thinking why would the Cthulhuism Society send out such an elaborate squad. It was actually you that messed up their plans." Ankama nodded showing that he understood. He actually knew about it beforehand but wanted to verify.

"Most of the men sent by the Cthulhuism Society to conquer the Glittering Pond were annihilated by you. I want to first express my sincere gratitude." He sincerely bowed towards Garen and Wukang.

"I want to thank both of you for clearly standing on the side of the royal family."

"What do you even mean? I, Garen of the Black Swamp Palace am still one of the members of the Three Departments, serving the elders of the Royal Alliance. To protect the interests of the royal family is protecting our own interest." Garen answered with a sense of justice.

Ankama instantly felt ashamed. Daniela did not do anything during the assassination of the king of Kovitan. They were also bystanders when the monsters from the nest attacked the kingdom. After Garen's words, he instantly felt a sense of remorse.

The young King of Holy Lake was obviously not yet warped by governmental politics. He still had basic moral standards.

Royal Alliance? The Three Departments? Ever since so many spies were found out in Kovitan, everyone in the Royal Alliance had only cared about their own safety. The Three Departments were divided although they looked like one. Many secret dealings were going on inside. Every one of them was thinking of themselves. No one cared about the big picture.

"I express remorse on behalf of my brother's flawed decision making." The King of Holy Lake shook his head. The brother that he mentioned was naturally the King of Daniela. They did not back Kovitan up during that time. Now when they needed help, the elites from Kovitan still righteousness traveled thousands of miles to come here. A friendship like that...

"Daniela is currently lacking resources. Since both of you rushed over to support our royal family, we will not mistreat you. I wonder have both of you heard of the Seed of the Ancestral God?"

Garen and Wukang looked at each other. They knew that the show was about the begin.

"Of course. It's one of the two most precious resources in Daniela." Garen nodded and replied.

"That's good. The Seed of the Ancestral God is a rare resource that cannot be kept by any known method. It has to be consumed within an hour or it will completely lose all effects. Hence…"

Ankama paused.

"Hence, many totem users come to Daniela every year to obtain the Seed of the Ancestral God to raise the innate talent of themselves or their descendants."

"Does this upgrade work for everyone?" Wukang furrowed his brows and asked.

"Of course not. It can work for any totem below Spiritualization level. Also, it can only work once per lifetime for everyone. One seed represents a one-time effect." Ankama answered.

"Since it can't be kept, wouldn't it have no effect on us?" Wukang continued. "If it can be kept there still might be some value."

"Although you can put in this way, however for totem users above Spiritualization level, the Seed of Ancestral God can increase the maximum capacity of totem power," Ankama added. "Totem power determines the explosiveness of a totem user, the number of totems he can control, the strength of totem light and others. Even the usage of tactics is limited by totem power. No totem user wouldn't want their strongest totem as their core totem. Unfortunately, he has to provide sufficient power. If not, once it is summoned, the user would faint due to his energy being sucked dry. What would be the point then? Hence totem power is the foundation of everything."

After hearing those words, even Garen was a little interested.

His totem power was his largest shortfall. This was the reason why he did not develop other third form totems outside of the Nine-Headed Hydra. The reason was his totem power was absolutely insufficient.

He never thought the Seed of the Ancestral God had an effect like this.

Seeing that both of them had interested expressions on their face, Ankama instantly let out a smile.

"The time of the year for the Ancestral God Pillar's seed dispersal has arrived. Both of you can gather the Seeds of the Ancestral God at our designated locations. No matter whether both you are successful, we will provide two more seeds for both of you as a reward for your help. Using two seeds at the same time will double the effect. You must know that one person can only use the effects of the Seeds of the Ancestral God once in his lifetime.

"Deal." Wukang cheerfully agreed. Since Lord Garen had an unspeakable motive, and they were already here, why not obtain more benefits first.

Garen also nodded.

"Your nation is generous indeed."

"How so? Compared to your friendships, this is nothing." Ankama was obviously an honest man. He let out an expression of not taking advantage of his friends as he spoke.

　　******************

In a certain canyon in Daniela

In the sea of black-green forest, the black canyon was like a big crack in the ground. Its ugliness clearly drew the attention of all living things.

The crack in the ground stretched across thousands of miles. In the field of vision, it was extremely deep, as if it was separating the earth into two.

The trees on both sides were tall and healthy. The scene was like a green carpet with tall ancient trees sewn into it. They were like tall pillars that left huge shadows on the ground.

Many huge colorful butterflies were surrounding the ancient trees.

Their wingspan was about 10 meters wide. From afar, they can be seen as cute. But from a close distance, they looked like small, flying houses. Their huge, flesh-like wings continuously created violent winds.

Among the butterflies, some were white, some were pink, some were light yellow, but most of them were translucent, with crystal-like translucent wings.

On the clear sky, huge birds continuously swooped down and glided through the forest.

On the back of most of the birds were human figures. They came from all directions as they flew towards the biggest tree in the forest.

On an intersection between the sea of trees and the crack, a green river flowed down from the cliff of the crack. It formed a giant white waterfall. As large amounts of white water splashed around, a faint rainbow was formed under the sunlight.

Many huge, transparent soap bubbles floated around in between the giant trees. Each of these soap bubbles was two or three meters large, with human figures standing or sitting within them.

Some of them were men and some of them were women. As they were wrapped in the soap bubble, they seemed slow but in fact, they were traveling at an incredible speed through the forest. It was like a normal form of transportation.

On an empty plain beside the waterfall, a man and a woman in green vine armor stood there.

Both of them impatiently looked at the sky above, as if they were expecting something.

"Why are we the ones to welcome foreign ambassadors? Can't it be other people?!" the young man complained in a tone of displeasure. The vine armor on his body was a short-sleeved shirt and short pants, revealing his strong arms and thigh. He obviously didn't wear undergarments that he should have worn.

"This is our father, the king's orders. If you dare to disobey, I guarantee he will throw you into that giant, tragic hole for more than two weeks." The young girl answered impatiently.

"To hell with it. I've already waited for a full three hours. I don't give a damn about the tragic hole! No, I have to go and accompany my Collier!" The young man turned and wanted to leave.

Shuaaa!

A giant, sticky grey tongue gave him a full-body lick.

A three-meter tall giant grey snail crouched behind him. He protruded a strange tongue from his mouth and licked the man like a puppy. The man was dripping wet from his air. After licking the front it licked the back. After thoroughly licking his whole body, it crawled away in satisfaction.

The man was stunned before the snail. His neat demeanor was totally gone.

The snail slowly crawled away, leaving the speechless man in a mess.

The girl on the side clenched her mouth and kept laughing.

"Argh!! My image!! My hair!! The hairstyle that I've just combed this morning!!" The guy shouted. "I'm going to kill you!! Don't stop me! Don't stop me, Christine!" He leaped ferociously towards the snail.

"Thousand apologies my dear brother. I am 8.152 meters away from your position. If you can defeat the snails here, I won't stop you from doing so." The girl couldn't stop herself from laughing as she answered.

The young man's legs were running, but he was stuck in his position.

After complaining for about half a day, he looked at giant snails that were everywhere. Finally, he helplessly sat on a large white stone.

"Alright. That is why mutated creatures are scary! Someone heard that a snail is on par with a third form totem user? If someone told me this before, I would have definitely sent the crazy man to a mental hospital."

Suddenly a group of large black hawks appeared in the sky. The black hawks were pulling a large black carriage.

"They're here!" The two youths stood up in excitement. Especially the young man. Because of his body's nature, he was licked by many snails. Finally, the time for him to escape his agony has arrived.

Chapter 475: Phiroth 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bang!

The carriage landed heavily before the two people. The door was quickly yanked open. Ankama, the King of Holy Lake jumped out.

"Uncle! My uncle! You've finally come!" The young man jumped forward with tears in his eyes.

Ankama turned sideways with a pained expression to evade the young man's pounce.

"Can you not exaggerate?" He was slightly exasperated.

"I can't take it! I can't take it any longer! All my clothes are wet. Only vine armor can be worn. I don't even have undergarments. This life…." The young man crawled to his feet from the ground and cried mournfully.

"Enough! Stop making noise. Do you want the guest to think of you as a joke?" Ankama said sternly.

"This is?" A calm male's voice came from the carriage.

The young man raised his head and saw a blonde-haired young man about his age walking out from the carriage. He was handsome and fair. His pair of scarlet eyes was faintly glowing red, especially the three red dots on his eyebrows.

The man wore a full-body black robe. On his left breast was a simple silver dragon head pattern. He looked like a perfect prince from a fairytale.

The young man compared himself with the guest. Compared to his own wet, messy, helpless image, the other party looked ten thousand times better. A sense of shame instantly gushed out from his heart.

"This is Fenrir. My brother's fourth son. This is Fensal, the fifth daughter. Both of them are here especially to welcome both of you." Ankama quickly introduced.

Both of them stood up straight and officially bowed towards Garen and Wukang.

"Welcome to the Ancestral God Canyon."

Compared to his brother's immaturity, the younger sister Fensal projected a much better image. Her mannerism was on point. With her beauty and figure, she was dressed in a new green vine armor, revealing her fair long legs and some skin. She gave off a refreshing sense of sexiness.

"Sorry to trouble both of you." Garen politely smiled.

The six of them, under the lead of the brother and sister, headed towards the waterfall.

The carriage automatically followed behind, leaving two distinct tire tracks on the ground.

In the forest on both sides of the waterfall, two to three-meter tall giant snails could be seen everywhere. The snails were slowly crawling in the forest. Some of them were stuck on tree trunks, some were sleeping in bushes, while some were chewing barks and flowers.

Most of these snails were grey. They carried a round shell each. None of them were affected by Garen's party.

Fensal walked in the front and introduced the surrounding environment with a loud voice.

"According to statistics, there are forty-two different types of snails in the snail forest. The smallest ones are two to three meters tall while the largest ones are five to six meters. They occupy different ecological fields. The ones surrounding is now are the basic grey snails. These snails have strong sticky liquid. At the same time, they have incredibly poisonous stings hidden. Once they face danger, they will shoot poisonous stings. They are very powerful and can counter totem light. According to valuation, they are on par with a third form totem user."

"Oh?" Garen never thought that the peaceful giant snails around had such powerful abilities.

"Grey snails like these are all over the forest. Other than them, there are also Lightning Snails, Volcano Snails, Corroding Snails, Rampaging Snails. Especially the Rampaging. Look, there's one over there." Fensal pointed at the forest on her left.

Bang, bang.

Within the forest, there was a giant snail humanoid with a shell on its back. It was incredibly muscular. As it was patrolling, every step produced a low sound. Its body was fully grey, like a grey-skinned giant. The only thing was it had an additional giant shell.

The two antlers on its head were swaying to the right and then to the left.

These giant Rampaging Snail had a human face with a ferocious expression. It stood up straight and walked on two limbs as it patrolled around the vicinity. It was a standard giant creature about five-meter tall.

Fensal smiled as she introduced it.

"The Rampaging Snails are the strongest guardians here. Each one of them has Spiritualization and basic intelligence. They have huge resistance towards totem light. They are incredibly strong and fast, and also have rampaging abilities. However, we have an agreement with them to protect the balance of nature together. As long as we do not disturb them or destroy their surrounding environment, they will not initiate an attack."

Garen and Wukang let out expressions of praise. This manner of living together could only be seen in Daniela.

"I've heard of King Phiroth of Daniela advocating harmony with nature. Only by seeing it first-hand, I can experience the difference it brings."

"Father's beliefs are the goals that we pursue." Fenrir finally found an opportunity to speak. "With these beliefs as the foundation, our Daniela formed the only Three-Dimensional Combat Squad in the world!" He spoke with a hint of pride, and at the same time stared defiantly at Garen.

"Three-Dimensional Combat Squad?" Garen asked out of curiosity.

"This is just a one-time experiment. We have not succeeded yet. Please head here." Fensal instantly interrupted her brother's gloating. She gave him a fierce pinch, which almost caused him to shout.

Ankama stared helplessly at his own nephew. This man was obviously concerned about his redundancy. Although Garen was the same age as him, he was long playing on a different level. Both parties could not be compared at all.

The six of them descended along the cliff, then followed a small path to the back of the waterfall. Large amounts of water poured down on the left, stirring up a chilling breeze.

Very quickly, the party arrived at a semi-circular protruding stone platform. Whitewater from the waterfall was flowing on both sides of the stone platform. Only the front was empty.

A handful of white vine armored guards were on guard at the two sides. Two white-robed totem users were waiting on the stone platform. As they saw the arrival of the six of them, both of them bowed slightly.

"Head to the second Ancestral God tree," Fensal ordered the two totem users in a loud voice.

The two of them nodded and took out a magnifying-glass like a golden ring and blew with all their might.

Shhhhhh…..

After the blowing sounds, two transparent bubbles instantly appeared. From the size of a fist, it quickly expanded into the size of a soccer ball, then the size of a basin, then the size of a bathtub. Finally, it became a giant, three-meter tall bubble.

"Please come up." Fensal was the first one who headed for the bubble. She squeezed her body and instantly entered the air bubble.

The rest of them followed suit and walked towards the air bubble. The six of them were split into two groups. Fensal stood with Garen and Wukang, while Ankama and Fenrir stood with the female guard.

The air bubbles instantly floated up and headed towards the sky.

"The airspace here forbids flying creatures, tools or tactics without a pass to fly, especially the central Ancestral God Pillar area. Only natural air bubbles like these are allowed. The forbidden airspace has the support of the Ancestral God Pillar. Even a strong totem user will not be able to fly without a pass. Moreover, there are also flesh butterflies who act as guardians. Look, they are over there. The flesh butterflies have huge resistance towards totem light, and can cause huge damage towards fire types…"

Fensal cheerfully introduced every detail of the surrounding environment to Garen.

This green-haired girl slowly leaned her body closer and closer towards Garen.

Daniela's girls were straightforward towards love and hate, They didn't cover up much. Like meant like.

Fensal obviously took a liking towards Garen.

Nobody cared about Wukang on the side. He sat alone admiring the scenery.

Garen carefully listened. From time to time, he raised his hand to touch the inner wall of the bubble. It was soft, like the texture of a balloon.

"This is the Ancestral God Tree rubber bubble. It can expand and contract. Different Ancestral God rubbers are naturally attracted to their respective Ancestral God trees. With this principle, we use the rubber bubble for transportation." Fensal slid her hand through the arch of Garen's arm. She leaned her whole body on Garen's side.

"Oh yes, Lord Garen is not married yet?"

"Yes. Not yet. But I have a fiancee." Garen quickly clarified. Fensal's actions made him feel a little dangerous.

"Nevermind. Compare to your rumored fiancee, I think I'm the most suitable one for you." Fensal volunteered. "I like you. Take me home?"

Garen was made speechless by her straightforwardness.

"Do not be impulsive, Sixth Princess. Aren't we still unfamiliar with each other? Moreover, it is impossible for me to give up on my fiancee."

"Aren't I still young? You are also still young. Shouldn't young people have vigor? Who cares about being impulsive. Leaving behind beautiful, painful, regretful memories, aren't these treasures when we become old? Shouldn't young people be impulsive?" Fensal didn't mind at all. She pressed her firm chest on Garen's arm. "I can't wait to give you my body as a memory." She lowered her voice and spoke flirtatiously.

"Precisely because you are young, isn't it much more possible to meet a better one? Isn't it unwise to decide too early?" Garen adviced helplessly.

Finally, the bubble arrived at a giant brown tree and landed on one of its branches.

From to time, other bubbles landed on the branches around. The people that came out were also led by others. They were evidently foreign totem users like Garen's party.

Each branch of the giant tree was ten-meters wide. The top of the branch was flat, and there was a wooden fence on the side. Two totem users were on guard here, like the two totem users in the bubble.

As Garen and the rest exited the air bubble, they instantly smelled a rich honey smell. The sweetness was similar to brewed honey; incredibly tempting.

Tiny white lights flashed faintly in the air. The lights could be seen but couldn't be felt.

Garen tried to use his hand to catch but it was intangible. His fingers passed by the middle of the faint light.

"This is the Ancestral God Light. For our guests who love nature, it reduces their fatigue." Seeing that Garen didn't want to say much, Fensal changed the topic.

Giant vines surrounded the Ancestral Tree trunk. These green vines were like mountain paths. They circled around the giant tree, forming connected paths with the branches.

Under Fensal's guidance, Garen and the rest walked out of the branches and headed downwards to the vines.

The vines were seven to eight meters-wide. From time to time, white vine-armored guards who were leading guests would pass by. Some of them directly entered the holes on the trunk, some of them headed upwards on the vines to board the air bubbles, while some were walking downwards.

Garen carefully admired the beauty of the scenery. The clear air made his mood better. As he was genetically fused with the Nine-Headed Hydra, he was naturally drawn towards beautiful things. This naturally made his mood better.

Qiu qiu… Qiu qiu…

Suddenly, a noise came from the front. It was like the cry of a child.

Very quickly, on the vine path ahead, a group of small milk-white and light yellow mushrooms were jumping and leaping. They happily passed the feet of Garen's party. Some of the small mushrooms even circled around Garen's party before catching up with the rest of the group and continued rushing downwards.

Garen and the rest were awed. After walking for a while, they met another group of small mushrooms. They lined up and happily passed Garen's feet. They were jumping and leaping like kids.

Chapter 476: Phiroth 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Those are little elves. They are the sons and daughters of the Ancestral God Tree. Do not hurt them as it will enrage the Ancestral God Tree." Fensal reminded softly. "These children will be very grateful if you treat them well. They will even help you back. For example, if you need to search for something or someone, as long as it is within this area, they would be able to be of assistance."

Very quickly, they finally arrived at the top segment of the Ancestral God Tree. There was a big hole in the tree trunk.

A strong white-haired man was standing in front of the tree hole. He was topless with only a black cape over his back. He wore heavy black vine armor on his lower body with a giant silver dual-ax on his back. His hair and beard were tangled together and it was impossible to tell the difference.

"Welcome welcome! My dear friends from Kovitan!" The white-haired man walked towards Garen. He instantly opened his arms and walked towards Garen to give him an intense hug.

A heavy sweaty odor instantly came.

Garen naturally had a strong sense of smell. With that hug, he almost fainted.

Bang bang bang!!!

The man gave Garen loud pats with his strong arms.

"Nine-Headed Hydra Garen! Not bad not bad!" The strong man let go of Garen and let out a big smile. "My daughter likes you very much!"

This King of Daniela was a legendary peak fifth form elite, but he totally did not have the charisma that an elite should have. He was like a barbarian chieftain which did not care about mannerisms at all.

However, it made sense after thinking about it. Being the strongest King of Daniela, he obtained everything through his fists and kicks, seizing from the Cthulhuism Society. He didn't put any form of mannerism in his eyes. He lived however he wanted. Who would dare to instruct him?

"Oh, it's my honor…" Garen was already told that the king's daughter likes him very much after their first meeting. His intentions were exceedingly clear.

"Come to Daniela, I'll marry my three daughters to you! Your kids will definitely be able to inherit my great Daniela and destroy those disgusting Cthulhu worms!" The king of Daniela led them into the tree hole with a big smile on his face.

Unexpectedly, the decorations in the hole were considered luxurious. White-silver ornaments and jade-green vines could be seen everywhere. Their patterns looked abstract but in fact, there was a certain mysterious sequence to it.

The whole tree hole gave people the feeling of a mysterious shrine.

The king of Daniela was a straightforward man. He did not beat around the bush with his words.

"I know you are worried about your fiancee. It's alright. I won't make things difficult for you. Go back and settle your fiancee then come back and marry my daughter!" Phiroth, King of Daniela sat on his throne and spoke bluntly.

"This…..I've only met your daughter for the first time. Isn't this progression is too fast…" Garen did not want to bluntly reject.

"No worries. The daughters of Daniela do not say much. Get in the car first before developing feelings!!" Phiroth waved his hand and was ready to set things in stone.

Garen was completely speechless. At that instant, Wukang was whispering in his ear.

"Do not agree. The words that he just said to you, he has said the same to more than ten elites. He is more fertile than Grand Duke Benoch. He has forty-three daughters now and seventy-six sons. Every time he meets genius totem users, he will give away his daughters and sons. As for inheriting Daniela, he tells this to everyone…" Wukang decisively revealed the true nature of the old man.

Forty-three daughters...

Garen twitched his eyebrows. Although he didn't know how Wukang obtained the information in such a short span of time, regardless of whether it was true, he didn't plan to agree on this marriage.

"Thousand apologies, your honor. I already have a fiancee. Please forgive me for not accepting such an honor." Garen bluntly rejected.

"Oh?" Phiroth straightened his eyes. The atmosphere in the tree hole instantly tremored. It wasn't tremors in the heart, but the whole tree hole was actually trembling slightly.

The air seemed to solidify.

"Saying this, are you looking down on the daughter of Phiroth?" A wave of ferocity flashed in Phiroth's eyes. A tremendous pressure instantly pressed on Garen.

"Your majesty, we came from afar to aid the situation in Daniela. Everyone has their own free will. Are you trying to interfere with my choices?" Garen blinked his eyes. There was a tremor in his body. He instantly broke free from the shapeless pressure of the totem light to avoid direct conflict with the other party.

The pressure had faint resemblance with the aura of the martial arts world. It was as per Garen's prediction. A true fifth form elite would already have God-like martial arts.

Facing an elite like this, totem light was a protective field. It combines totem power and the totem's abilities to form the strongest foundational power. It was like the blood-flow in the martial art world. This was the foundational power of all martial arts. It was a foundational element like a magician's magic in fairy tales and the inner strength of wushu artists. Only because of the different totem abilities, it caused this foundational power to carry different attributes, strengths, and characteristics.

Reversing this power obtained by fusion and evolution, then pushing it into the body to transform it and eventually reaching a whole new evolved level. This was the principle of fifth form.

Facing a fifth form master once again, Garen gleaned some key points just from the short battle of auras. He was instantly delighted.

As he reached the end of this path, he never thought he would be walking his old path of martial arts. The only difference was low-level martial arts used blood flow as the foundation, while the martial arts here used a higher power which recycles in the body as the base for martial arts.

After he understood this, he regained his focus instantly and faced the King of Daniela, Phiroth. The other party was obviously showing off his strength for Garen to understand the difference between their abilities. There is always pride in geniuses.

As their auras came into direct conflict, the difference was Phiroth's aura completely covered the whole tree hole. The faces of the guards and servants around were pale. They were obviously in serious shock.

Even Wukang, Fensal and the rest did not look good, especially Fensal. She knew her father's temper. Although he had many kids, Phiroth especially loved twelve of them, including herself and her brother. His proposal being rejected in front of such a big crowd did not look good on all of Daniela.

"Hahaha!" Suddenly, Phiroth burst into laughter. His loud laughter shook the whole tree hole.

"Good! Good personality! I admire your character! I am at peace entrusting my daughter to you!" Phiroth directly ignored Garen's rejection.

"Your Majesty. It's not that your daughter isn't good enough. It's just that I'm already…"

"There's no need for more words!" Phiroth raised his hands. "I know what you mean, but Phiroth's daughter is definitely much better than your fiancee! However, the younger generation should handle their own matters. Regarding you and number six, both of you develop by yourselves. I'll leave it to you."

He raised the wine glass and gulped down some wine.

"Alright, I'm tired. All of you are excused. Coming from afar, have good rest today. Don't miss the gathering period of the Seed of the Ancestral God."

"Thanks for your understanding, Your Majesty." Garen heaved a sigh of relief. All these while there was freedom of love. He has never heard about forced marriage in front of a crowd. The King of Daniela was volatile. His thoughts were abnormal. It wasn't easy to deal with him.

The thing that made Garen more speechless was that a person like that was one of the strongest in the whole world. Even in the whole East Continent, Phiroth would be one of the top elites.

The habit of giving daughters away after meeting people wasn't a good one.

Feeling fortunate, Garen and Wukang finally left the tree hole. Two tree holes located at the bottom half of the tree were arranged for their stay.

Before long, there were totem users that came to visit.

As Kovitan's top genius who emerged in a few short years, Garen naturally had some fame. Leaders of middle and large-sized forces visited him one by one to be acquainted. They even brought along some strange treasures as gifts.

Garen took a few of the gifts including a potion that he concocted and went to visit the Lord and Deputy Lord of the Geometry Service.

The Geometry Service was different from other departments. The main power structure was from the Royal Star Court. The strongest Lord and Deputy Lord were equivalent to the directors and ministers of other departments.

However, he did not manage to meet both of them. Both of them were out. Garen had to leave the gifts and return.

Furthermore, basic manners were sufficient.

After a series of exchanges, Wukang who was incredibly good in espionage returned after going out alone. There were clearly several kiss marks on his neck. He walked into Garen's tree hole with a blissful expression.

"Daniela's girls are too wild!" His first sentence revealed his nature.

He showed off his kiss marks so Garen could see them better.

Wukang laughed and sat down. Then he drank the red fruit juice on the table.

"Say...What other good news have you obtained again."

"There is indeed a good news." Wukang placed the cup down. "The Cthulhu King has announced that he wants to make an exchange with the glittering water. Is this considered good news?"

"Of course." Garen's eyes brightened up. He was waiting for this.

"There is other news. I heard that two intelligence-type nest kings have appeared in the East Continent. They are incredibly strong." Wukang continued. "They control all the nests, gathering all monsters and dangerous mutants to form a complete organization. They are in three major countries and a whole group of small countries in the South. They restricted the monsters from attacking humans. Naturally, the environment became safer. At least all monsters with strong abilities are gone."

Garen naturally knew the origin of the two new nest kings. If the piece of information was accurate, he wasn't surprised.

"Anything else?"

"The situation. Many remnants of organizations naturally started to develop again while in a safe environment." Wukang shrugged. "However, I heard that Daniela's King wanted to recruit all these organizations to become one with him at the helm. His ambition is not small. He wants to disassemble the Elder Council and do things himself." Wukang stroked his chin as he spoke.

"After some careful thought, Phiroth indeed has a huge ambition. But the Cthulhuism Society aren't herbivores. There will definitely be conflicts during this upcoming glittering water incident." Garen whispered.

"Herbivores? What do you mean?" Wukang didn't understand. "Oh, are you saying they are as ferocious as carnivores? Yes indeed," he responded. "What should we do now?"

"The Seed of the Ancestral God and Cthulhu's Origin. We need to try our best to obtain these two things." Garen said with a solemn expression. "However, many other forces will have the same objective as us."

"Definitely. Elites from Ender, and also Sudan. All of them are led by fourth form elites. In fact, most of the strongest people in the East Continent other than the Elder Council, have gathered here. Hehe, the human population is already severely depleting. If there is another accident here, killing a whole bunch of people, the human race would be facing extinction.

Garen looked at Wukang. Although he didn't mean it, Garen knew that after Hellgate emerges, the actual situation would be like what Wukang has described. Many elites who fought against the Obscuro Society would perish. The forces of the entire East Continent would be depleted. In the future, even Spiritualization level would be considered elites., as fourth form totem users would be almost extinct.

After Beckstone and the rest defeat Hellgate with tremendous effort, the whole totem world in the East Continent would be broken. The totem civilization would regress backward by a few decades.

Chapter 477: Action 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The two of them discussed the rough arrangements in the room and how to react to possible scenarios. Only when all arrangements were complete did Wukang take his leave. It was likely he went to continue flirting with Daniela's girls. His female guard was also missing. Garen sat alone in the room and continued his practice of the Black Water True Technique. He only stood to leave the room when the sun was about to go down.

A green vine armored guard was standing by the door. As he saw Garen exiting, he asked respectfully.

"My Lord, do you have needs?"

"Where is the gathering area of the Seed of the Ancestral God? Bring me to have a look." Garen asked directly.

"The gathering area requires taking the bubble over. Please follow me." The guard was a young man. He seemed a little nervous when handling Garen's request. But he was considered decent. He was well-mannered, obviously from a good background.

The name of the Nine-Headed Hydra was thoroughly infamous throughout Kovitan, or even the outside world. He was the type who could kill without blinking. It wasn't an unusual thing to be severely beaten if one wasn't careful in dealing with him.

Fortunately, Garen simply nodded without uttering much.

Under the guard's guidance, both of them descended along the vine path and arrived at a larger circular plate. It was the departure point of the bubbles.

Similarly, there were two flight attendants on top waiting for orders. A guest-like man and woman in red robes were ready to board a newly-created bubble.

Both of them saw Garen and the guard who had just entered. In the instant they saw Garen, their expression changed. They obviously recognized Garen.

Garen himself was unclear, but they knew of him. Among the totem users that came to the Ancestral God Pillar, for those of them with strong organizational backgrounds, they had excellent information networks. All incredibly dangerous totem users were all marked with special portraits to heighten their awareness.

Garen was one of the top ten most dangerous men. He was on par with the top few Cthulhus of the Cthulhuism Society and the two elites of Daniela's royal family. Other than the totem users at the pinnacle, they were the ten most dangerous people. Conflict with them should be avoided at all costs.

This private list was circulated among all totem users from medium to smaller forces. Some grassroots totem users with methods of their own had also obtained and sold it to other totem users at a high price. Hence, in fact, all of the totem users who came for the gathering of the Seed of the Ancestral God were aware of this ranking.

The two totem users bowed to Garen from afar, showing their respects.

Garen didn't care about them. Under the flight attendant's arrangement, he boarded the bubble alone.

He sat in the bubble and quickly soared into the sky. He could clearly see the orange landscape below at one glance.

Each giant Ancestral God tree was like ginormous mushrooms. Their vast shade overshadowed the ground below.

From time to time, flesh butterflies and giant bubbles flew pass the Ancestral God trees. It added a fantasy feel to the environment.

The bubble that Garen was sitting in floated for a moment and quickly landed at the side of one of the largest Ancestral God trees. A few temporary gathering points were already built.

The gathering points stood in a circle within the green forest. Each of them had their own sign.

The gathering area was in the shape of an equilateral triangle. Every three gathering areas would form a triangle. From the inner region to the outer region, the grew larger and larger. Each gathering area lined up in three straight lines, stretching throughout the forest.

As Garen landed, the flight attendant was about to finish his shift. He was yawning when he saw Garen arriving. He instantly put on a straight face and a respectful attitude.

There were three take-off points in this gathering area. A handful of people were ready to take off on this particular take-off point. Seeing Garen landing, their expressions changed.

Garen felt something was off. As he landed on the ground, he blocked off the two people who were about to take off.

"Excuse me. Can I borrow some of your time?"

"Of course! Of course, you can!" The two couple-like totem users agreed hurriedly. If their faces hadn't turned pale, one would think they were very welcoming towards Garen's inquiry if it was just based on their tone of voice.

After a few minutes….

Garen looked at the two people fleeing. He finally understood what was going on.

The nation of Daniela worshiped battles. Be it the Cthulhuism Society or the Royal Family of Daniela, activities like a battle to the death in front of crowds were not rare sights. It was natural here for the weak to obey the strong.

Before Garen arrived, most of the masters who were ranked in the top ten had fierce personalities. They would severely injure or even kill people without saying a word.

Because of the tense situation between Daniela and the Cthulhuism Society, plus the gathering of Cthulhu's Origin and the Seed of the Ancestral God, more and more elites flocked over here. There were a few key people who were worthy of Garen's attention.

The first one.

One of Edney's famous, next-generation masters - Scylla Whitewater. He was believed to be on par with the Three Great Heroes, as a peak fourth form totem user. He fought on par with the Black Prince for more than ten minutes. According to rumors, he held various precious heirlooms, but nobody has seen them before. He was also the master of the Edney's Ancient Society.

Secondly.

The top three of the Cthulhuism Society - Thunder God, Light God, and Water God.

The three of them were the strongest existence other than the Cthulhu King in the Cthulhuism Society. They were fifth form masters with immortality. Even Garen himself had headaches when facing them.

Thirdly.

A mysterious figure from the Obscuro Society - a girl named Emilo. No one has ever seen her true figure. She always hid under a black mantle, with a black mask and white moon-shaped earrings. Once she'd appeared and heavily injured King Gallo, one of the two kings of Daniela. She destroyed all his various tactics, illusions and totem equipment. Had King Phiroth not arrived quickly, whether his brother, King Gallo could have kept his life was another question.

This sneak attack further intensified the tension between the royal family and the Obscuro's Cthulhuism Society.

Garen was similar to Scylla Whitewater. They were on par with the top three Cthulhus in the eyes of people. In addition to his fame which had spread here from Kovitan, he instantly became one of the targets that shouldn't be messed with by fellow totem users.

The gathering of the Ancestral God seeds was a grand occasion held together by the Cthulhuism Society and the royal family. At the same time, it was an opportunity to secretly show off strength and compete for positions.

The most important competition was for the three internal rings. The three internal rings were the best positions.

The three most central area of the triangle was the easiest place to gather the best Ancestral God seeds. Hence, this was the most intense competition over the years.

Garen directly headed to the three internal rings. He followed the paths between the triangular gathering area.

The triangular gathering area was layered. A bigger triangle would surround a smaller one, one after the other. The number of totem users here was uncountable. Some of them set up signs of the organizations, some set up regional signs, while some set up signs of the royal family. The sign of the Terraflor Society was also on a corner on the fourth layer.

Garen didn't care much. He passed the fourth layer and headed towards the third layer. As he passed by the gathering areas, there were owls, birds, mice on the sides. They were scouting totems. There were also totem users that came out to observe the newly arrived Garen.

On every triangular layer, there was a weak, simple balancing structure. Normally when they faced intruders, they would merge and defend, to avoid anyone interfering with the benefits that had been agreed on.

However, everyone had the information on Garen being one of the ten fiercest people. He was one of the cruelest totem users in Kovitan, even facing fifth form Marshall God Cloud heads on. He wasn't someone they could mess with.

Fearful gazes were fixated on Garen, observing him walking towards the internal rings.

Passing the fourth layer, he entered the third layer. The totem light waves in the gathering areas strengthened. It meant that spiritualization level tactic formations existed here.

On the empty spaces on the two sides, the branches above and in the bushes, the number of scouting totems increased.

Garen didn't head to any specific gathering area. He continued along the forest path between gathering areas and headed inwards.

Only stronger forces could obtain gathering areas in the third layer. Frozen Valley, Fire Dragon Island and Starry Eye Association. These three were strong organizations that could sustain themselves in this chaos. All of them had fourth form totem users, but none of them were located in Kovitan. They were large organizations with branches in Edney and Daniela.

Within the Starry Eye Association's gathering area

A group of blue-robed totem users gathered together around a giant crystal sphere, looking at Garen's figure which was reflected within.

"The final battles are taking place in the second layer. The Cthulhuism Society and the Royal Alliance each occupy a point. A fierce battle is taking place for the remaining point. A large majority of the ten masters are confronting each other for this position. Now another master on the same level has arrived. Looks like there will be a good show to watch." The association's leader was an old white-bearded. He was sucking a lollipop as he sat crossed-leg on the floor. He looked casual as he adjusted the clarity of the crystal ball in excitement.

"Normally, those two major forces would dominate the six positions in the first two layers. But now the foreign forces are too strong. Even the Cthulhuism Society and Phiroth had to tamper down their pride,and give up two positions." Another old woman who was knitting answered. "Last time, changes to these positions would take a long time to happen. But after the turmoil, many organizations have regressed and left many positions open. It is natural to have battles like this."

"Let's wait and see. It's not so easy to enter the second level." The old man looked like he was ready to watch a show.

His disciples on the side seemed used to it.

"Look! That guy is heading directly towards the Cthulhuism Society's territory!! What is he planning to do?" The old man suddenly cried out.

　　*****************

Garen stood before the Cthulhuism Society's gathering area on the second level. In front of his eyes was a small white bungalow surrounded by a white fence. There was a faint red glow above.

A few red-robed Cthulhu Society members were on patrol and noticed his arrival. A few of them stared closely at him as if he was an enemy. They looked ready for a battle.

The decision-maker quickly walked out from the bungalow. It was a tall, cold girl.

Her cold, expressionless gaze fell upon Garen.

"Nine-Headed Hydra Garen Trejons. What are you here for? This isn't Kovitan's stronghold." Two other girls behind the tall girl quickly gestured in the air. The tactic formations around the bungalow slowly lit up one by one. Dangerous creatures faintly appeared in the air at once. They patrolled in the air, ready for a defense anytime.

According to the Cthulhuism Society's intelligence, the man before him can only be defeated by four Cthulhus combined. He wasn't someone she could handle by herself. She only had to slightly delay with tactic formations before Thunder God and the rest arrived. Then they wouldn't have to be afraid of the opponent.

Chapter 478: Action 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I know that in previous years, the two other nations of the Royal Alliance have had their own gathering areas. Naturally, I am not here to raid your area." Garen laughed. "I heard that the Cthulhuism Society's master is planning to purchase glittering water. So happen I do have sufficient glittering water. The reason I came here is to make a deal with you. Your Cthulhu's Origin is something I have yearned for long."

"A deal?" The ice-cold girl shuddered. "I will convey your intentions to our master. You can go back to where you came from. Let me remind you of something. Kovitan's stronghold has already been invaded by an outsider."

"I'll settle it by myself." Garen nodded. Before the deal, he temporarily wouldn't take action against the Cthulhuism Society. It would be different after the deal was completed.

Before Hellgate's awakening, he had to do all he could to gather resources to upgrade himself. This was his final chance.

He stopped heading forwards and started walking around the level. He headed towards the direction of another stronghold.

One of the strongholds in this area was originally Kovitan's. Unfortunately, because of the huge changes to Kovitan some time ago, large amounts of manpower were recalled back. The stronghold was then occupied by some low-level forces from Kovitan until the incident with the red-robed man took place.

An unknown red-robed man attempted to seize control of a second level stronghold. He first challenged Daniela's stronghold. After being defeated by Gallo King who was on guard, he no longer dared to return. He next went to the Cthulhuism Society's territory. But his neck was almost snapped by the Earth God on guard. The Earth Guard was ranked in the top six in the Cthulhuism Society.

As his planned to become famous failed, the red-robed man helplessly headed towards Kovitan's stronghold. He released all his accumulated anger on Kovitan's totem users.

The man was unscrupulous. With his first tier escaping ability, he didn't care about the possibility of revenge by Kovitan's elites and instantly acted. The other forces who were observing at the sidelines were surprised.

The Kovitan compound was like paper paste, crumbling at one touch.

The red-robed man killed three of the men in charge in a row. He finally conquered the stronghold completely and chased everyone from Kovitan out of the stronghold.

Kovitan in its current divisive state no longer had the greatness when Avic was still alive. Their overall strength was even weaker than Edney. As they couldn't even manage their internal matters, troubles far away in Daniela shouldn't even be mentioned.

In the eyes of outsiders, Kovitan was like a sunset, no longer having the light and heat of a midday sun. The past greatness of this nation was no longer there. The strongest nation now was Daniela, while Edney was the second. Kovitan, with the Ultimate Protection, could barely be considered as the third. However, regarding their influence on the outside world, they were nothing once they stepped out of the Ultimate Protection.

As Garen arrived at the stronghold, the sun was only left with a small semi-circle on the horizon.

Kovitan's stronghold was a deserted white stone castle. The remnants of the great battle could be seen everywhere.

Some of the places were full of blood stains. A handful of totem users from Kovitan were fearfully looking from afar.

Whether it was the red-robed man or Garen, in their hearts they were both problems that could not be defeated. Garen destroyed his opponents in the country. He was incredibly cruel. Similarly, the red-robed man was strong. He did not blink when committing a murder. In the fight between two tigers, it all depends on who is stronger. Having said that, regardless of the winning side, there were no benefits for these imitation Royal Alliance totem users who previously occupied the stronghold.

Without hesitation, Garen took big steps into the castle compound.

It was quiet inside, without any human sounds.

Garen's clear footsteps echoed in the surroundings.

"You have finally come!" A cold voice came from within the castle.

The red-robed man stood on the peak of the castle. He folded his arms and looked at Garen proudly.

"I've studied totems for forty-two years. I couldn't find a suitable opponent on par with me after coming out from my training. I never thought you would come here by yourself."

Garen was speechless. This was obviously another one seeking fame by challenging elites. He was similar to the guy whose heart was ripped out by the Angel of the Night. He looked reckless, but in actual fact, he must have done his preparations.

"What's your name?" Seeing that his opponent was a fourth form, Garen asked.

"Justin Edward!"

Never heard of it.

Garen searched the original history and couldn't find this person. Most likely he was a small character that was killed by one of the elites.

"Alright. You can leave." Garen waved impatiently. He initially thought it was an important figure, a mysterious master. He never expected it to be a common person.

The red-robed man instantly widened his eyes.　

"You dare to ask me to leave?! Don't think too highly of your Dasula School!! Even your teacher dared not speak to me this way!"

"Dasula?" Garen instantly thought of teacher Emin, the actual old totem user that taught him the basics.

"I've heard that you are the strongest in the history of Dasula! Being the pride of the entire Dasula, I want to see your abilities today! Take this, Polyether Air Gun! Die if you cannot take it!!" As the red-robed man raised his hands, a blood red light appeared around him, forming a giant, invisible whirlpool of air.

Garen was lazy to speak nonsense with him. There was a sudden tremor below his feet and he became a black ray of light.

With a flash, he instantly appeared before the red-robed man and gave him a smack with his hand.

Bang!!!

The red blur fell to the ground, forming a pit with a diameter of more than ten meters. In the middle of the pit was the red-robed man. There was blood on the sides of his mouth. His body was glimmering in red totem light, but it looked shaky as if it would break down anytime. He was in total shock. His eyes were about to roll up, as if he didn't know how he was knocked down.

Chiiiii!!!

A black ray of light shot down instantly, accurately hitting his chest.

Bang!!

There was a huge tremor on the ground, forming a ten-meter long crack. In an instant, the red-robed man's body became a blood-like fog. Not even his bones were left.

The blood-like fog was quickly sucked in by the dragon blur on Garen's back. It became the Nine-Headed Hydra's nutrients.

"Dasula School? Looks like Teacher Emin has rebuilt his previous school. In actual fact, I am from Dasula." Garen stood at the side of the pit and reminisced about the past. His foundations were truly from Dasula. It was natural for the other disciples from the school to look at him as a top representative and pride.

If it wasn't for the challenger seeking for death who suddenly appeared today, he wouldn't have known that Teacher Emin had already rebuilt Dasula.

"I do know a little about Dasula School." Wukang suddenly appeared beside Garen. He brought along a heavy scent of perfume, which made people dizzy.

"The Dasula School officially announced leaving the Terraflor Society some time ago. They regained independence and just like previously, they were split into three branches. Your teacher Emin, the Luminarist is now the elder and master of the school. Having said that, these developments are heavily influenced by you."

"My influence?"

"Of course. Your fame and power are growing. In addition, the Obscuro Society faced some heavy losses after being defeated by Hawk King Goth. The Dasula School naturally shared some fame. Even if your teacher didn't plan to rely on you, the positive impact on him was unavoidable. Furthermore, the disciples think of you as the greatest pride in Dasula's history. It is true in fact. Although Dasula is considered strong regionally, it is just a medium-level school. Producing such a top elite like Lord Garen, naturally, they would publicize it."

Wukang grinned. "It has been said that the whole school regards you as a role model and cohesive force. The whole school has never been more united. The segregated branches of the past have also returned and the overall power has soared."

Garen did not consider this.

It was like someone who became famous or achieved something great. All their previous schools, primary schools, secondary schools and others would take pride in them. They would use that to publicize on the quality of their teaching. Their fame would grow and naturally their development would speed up. It was the same principle.

"Why haven't they come and look for me?" Garen couldn't understand.

"It should be your teacher's decision." Wukang wasn't sure as well.

Garen might have guessed something.

In order not to make life difficult for himself, Teacher Emin voluntarily left the Terraflor Society. Although relying on the Black Swamp Palace would be much help, but at the same time would bring great risks. Emin must have considered that and decided not to come and look for him.

Garen made up his mind to find a time to contact his teacher. Although the Dasula School was his teacher's school, it was also a force that supported him. He should take care of them once Hellgate awakened. Hiding in the Ultimate Protection, it was improbable that Hellgate could unlock it in a short time. Furthermore, there was that old man in the palace. In the original history, the reason Hellgate didn't break through the Ultimate Protection might be this.

"Speaking of this, I have some troubling news." Wukang continued. "After we presumptuously raided their strongholds, the Cthulhuism Society has sent people to take the Glittering Pond back."

"No worries. I've already sent a message to Voidharp, Blizzard and the rest. My Black Swamp Palace is not a weakling. If we can't even handle the Cthulhuism Society, a weak force suppressed by the royal family of Daniela, what qualifications do we have to interfere?"

Garen had long predicted.

He had already tied the elites of the Snowy Mountain together with him. This group of old people who had no fear of death was abnormally cruel. The conditions in the North were terrible, in addition to Kovitan's Ultimate Protection in the middle, it was abnormally difficult for the Obscuro Society to take revenge. Without anything to worry about, they naturally became tighter.

Furthermore, the most important was that the Seven Night Tower far away in the North was only familiar with the Royal Alliance as a traditionally strong force. As for the Obscuro Society, could they compare to the Royal Alliance? The difference was too big.

Their impression hasn't changed.

It was the same for people like Wukang. The Royal Alliance was an incredibly strong force. It wasn't something that the two fifth form Marshalls of the Obscuro could withstand. If they didn't hide properly, God Cloud and the other Marshall would have been annihilated.

Especially the Director of the National Service, which was someone that he himself would be afraid of. The main reason God Cloud was hiding for so many years was this man. God Cloud had been trained by him.

As the teacher of a black sheep, he searched everywhere for God Cloud. The reason God Cloud didn't dare to show his real body was because of this director.

Chapter 479: Clash 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Cthulhuism Society and the Obscuro Society were planning some tricks. They were obviously intending to move to the top.

As Garen and Wukang entered the stronghold, they were discussing the new pieces of information.

The stronghold was completely empty. The initial totem users had all been chased away by the red-robed man. Fortunately, Daniela quickly sent some servants and maids to clean up the place. As the host, battles in strongholds like this were very common. There was an unspoken rule where normal humans with no abilities would not be harmed. Otherwise, no one would be willing to serve here.

They found a relatively clean hall at the side. Garen and Wukang sat at the table and looked at the innermost Ancestral God Tree through the giant window.

The Ancestral God Tree was lush and abundant. Its dense leaves and branches were like green clouds against the sky. From time to time, bubbles and butterflies passed by in the air. On the side of the trunk, a huge black castle was built. The castle was facing Garen's direction. A black, translucent vertical pipe was on the castle's outer wall. It was like an elevator. There were moving stone platforms in the pipes which continuously sent people to and fro.

All of the people in the stone platforms had followers with them. They didn't look like normal people.

As Garen and Wukang were relaxing inside, they were eating Daniela's specialty fruits, green bananas and fist-sized peaches which were already peeled.

"This full-green Ancestral is the largest tree in the area. The rest of the giant trees are not even half its height. Obviously, this is the legendary Ancestral God Pillar. I heard that the Ancestral God Trees have uncomparable power. I wonder whether it's true." Wukang spoke with emotions as he was admiring the Ancestral God Tree.

"Who knows?" Garen casually answered.

"Are we just staying here? You are not planning to enter?"

Garen shook his head.

"This is the limit. If we go any closer, we will lose more than we gain. The most inner layer is occupied by the top people of the royal alliance and the Cthulhu King. It's not a place that we can enter."

"True." Wukang took a piece of fruit and put it in his mouth. "Then we're waiting here for the gathering to start? Do you know the approximate time?"

"I'm unclear. But it should be within these few days. Be patient." Garen smiled. "Have you realized that the air here is different from other places?"

Wukang was caught by surprise. He carefully sniffed and closed his eyes to feel the difference.

After not more than a few minutes, he opened his eyes. There was a hint of shock in his eyes.

"The air here has an abnormal vitality to it! It seems to have a positive impact on our totems. I feel that my core totem has become more energetic."

"Likewise." Garen blinked. "No wonder so many elites are fighting for strongholds on these levels. Looks like it's not as simple as the seeds. The position of the strongholds is also a key factor."

"Looks like it. The central region is really mysterious. If I didn't come here personally, I wouldn't have imagined that there would an environment that energizes totems in this world. This is a perfect environment to culture totems. No wonder the mutants around are at such high levels. It is not without a reason."

So don't be impatient. Let's wait for a while." Garen took up a slice of peach. "Let's take this opportunity to investigate the information we want."

Wukang nodded his head.

　　******************

The two of them waited in the stronghold for over ten days. The vitality in the air around the Ancestral God Tree grew richer and richer. Both of their core totems became more and more energetic. Their energy levels were shocking.

Especially Garen. His core totem was different from the normal totem user. His core totem was an empowered totem instead of a silver totem. In an environment with this form of vitality, the Nine-Headed Hydra, which evolved from a living being, was exceedingly energetic. In Garen's black space, it was inhaling large amounts of living energy, then exhaling waste.

With this metabolism rate, it allowed the exchanging of waste. It made Garen felt like he was improving every day.

His heart was also originally from the Nine-Headed Hydra's heart. Under this environment, it became even livelier and beat faster than ever.

Garen took this opportunity to continuously practice the Black Water True Technique day and night. After some time, even the fourth dragon head had signs of being able to be fused. This made him delighted. He initially thought he needed a few more weeks of time. He never thought that this vigorous air could quicken the progress of his fusion.

Garen decided to seclude himself to train in a secret room in the stronghold. While Wukang was responsible for the outside matters.

Meanwhile, the Sixth Princess would come to visit Garen every day. Her pair of dreamy big eyes made no secret of her intentions. By secluding himself to train, Garen avoided her embarrassing pursuit. He'd let Wukang handle it.

Wukang was incredibly experienced in handling women. Every day, he would try to gossip with number six. He continuously tried to change her impression of Garen but to no avail.

It grew closer and closer to the time when the Ancestral God tree would disperse its seeds.

Some of the people from Kovitan who weren't afraid of death slowly crawled closer to this stronghold. They wanted to get a piece of the pie. They were previously chased away by the red-robed man. After some of them heard the news that the master of Kovitan's stronghold had changed, they instantly had a glimmer of hope.

Garen and the rest were too lazy to care about them. Everyone could only gather one Seed of the Ancestral God. The only difference was the level of vigor would differ according to the distance to the tree. The position of this stronghold was the most concentrated gathering area on the second level. The seeds gathered here were the best among the second level. The other positions were not comparable to it.

However, those that could enter the second level were naturally not normal totem users. They wouldn't presumptuously chase people away like the red-robed man. Since he couldn't absorb all the vigorous air by himself, and that they were from Kovitan, he didn't mind those people.

The time was approaching day by day.

Finally, there was something new happening at the Ancestral God Trees.

　　******************

Night

Garen had just awakened from his martial arts training.

There was a suspicious look in his eyes, which emitted a red glow in the dark.

"The vigor in the air seems to have grown stronger? Compared to the slow increase previously, it seemed to have multiplied this time."

He stood up, pushed open the door of the secret room and headed out.

Most of the defects on the white stone stronghold had been fully repaired. The outside scenery could be clearly seen through the semi-circled, full-length window in the hall.

Green lights filled the sky. They were descending slowly like snow, completely brightening up the night sky in the forest. Everywhere looked green. The fluorescent green light shone through the window, dyeing a huge portion of the stronghold's hall green.

Garen widened his eyes and looked at the descending green lights. There was a shocked expression in his eyes.

He hastened his steps and pulled open the door of the hall, planning to go and have a look.

Suddenly a ginormous grey toad was blocking at the front of the door. The three-meter tall toad completely blocked the doorway. As its white tummy was rumbling along, its two protruding eyes stared at Garen.

Its body was full of grey blisters of different sizes. Its rough skin was like tree bark. It looked tough but it also had the moisture of a swamp. A faint fishy odor came from its body.

Garen furrowed his brows. He was more sensitive towards smells.

"Attention sixth stronghold, the gathering is about to begin. Please get ready." As the toad opened his big mouth, it was speaking the language of Daniela.

"Alright." Garen nodded.

"By the way, the raw air outside is too strong. Do not go out carelessly, in order to avoid danger." Once the toad finished, he hopped away towards the wild.

Garen stood at the door to send it off. Wukang silently appeared behind him.

"It starts tonight?" He was still rubbing his eyes in a set of white pajamas. He looked like he just had a good sleep.

"Let's prepare." Garen nodded.

The two of them finished changing, drank some juice then took the breakfast toast provided by Daniela. As they ate, they came to the balcony on the second level of the stronghold.

The balcony was a full-white, semi-circle terrace without railings.

Both of them finished their bread and each stood on one of the marked areas on the ground. The marked areas were three oval-shaped tactic formations, obviously for gathering seeds.

The green light dots all over the sky slowly descended. Garen stretched out his hand to catch it but they were like illusions. The light dots directly passed through his palm and exited below.

The rich, vigorous air seemed to have a life force. It rapidly entered Garen's nostrils. The Nine-Headed Hydra in Garen's body was greedily absorbing the vigorous air. From its initial state of malaise, it grew more and more energetic.

He looked from afar at the Ancestral God Tree. The raw air had already reached a horrific density. The inner layer most likely would have been more terrifying.

Garen looked into the distance with his unnatural eyesight. He actually noticed Phiroth.

The strong King of Daniela was sitting opposite a black bear on a large branch on the Ancestral God Tree. There was a small stool between them with a chessboard on top of it. Both of them were concentrating on the chess game.

From time to time, the black bear would scratch its head in deep thought. Then it stood up, folded its hands and stared at the chessboard.

Besides the two of them were a handful of rabbit humanoids serving food and drinks. Each of these rabbit humanoids had a rabbit head with two ears standing tall. They had bodies of a beautiful human girl. They had huge busts, long legs, and white skin, while wearing breezy, low-cut dresses.

Chiiiii!!

Suddenly, a green light beam shot out from the right side of the forest. It soared into the sky, breaking through the layers of cloud.

The slender green light was pure, without any impurities. It soared directly into the sky.

Chiii chiii!!

After a number of light sounds, several green beams shot into the sky.

Garen regained his focus and nodded towards Wukang.

At the same time, the two of them quickly started to gesture in the air. Their ten fingers constantly drew large amounts of dense symbols, leaving shadows behind.

As their creation of tactic formations sped up, two of them were gradually surrounded by a layer of fluorescent green light.

Chiii!!

Suddenly, a ray of piercing green light shot out in between them and headed towards the sky.

The green light beam completely engulfed the two of them. Small black dots were gradually appearing in the airspace in front of their chests.

The dots slowly grew bigger and bigger. Their shape became more and more like an oval.

Then, as the black balls faintly released white water vapor, they became flatter and flatter.

Puffff!

A hole cracked open at the bottom of the ball, emitting white gas. Together with the white gas, a green toothpaste-like thing came out from the hole and suspended in the air before Garen.

The green paste was squeezed out in lines. They gathered in circles with a pointy end, while emitting mild heat. They formed artistic, mysterious objects.

Garen twitched his eyebrows as he looked at the legendary, poop-like object before him.

"Don't tell me this is the legendary Seed of the Ancestral God?"

Wukang's expression was also inquisitive. He glowed in green then in white. He looked at the green, poop-like object and didn't know whether he should take it.

The green light around the both of them dissipated and everything became calm again.

The green dots in the air also grew faint and finally disappeared. The green fluorescent waste was all over the ground, lighting up the whole forest in green.

"Congratulations to all for obtaining the legendary Seed of the Ancestral God! Hehe. Isn't this year's shape really artistic?" A clear voice came from the direction of the Ancestral God Tree. It was the voice of Phiroth.

No one spoke a word and the whole area was in silence. All of the elites didn't know how to reply. "Your Majesty's taste….is really unique…" An old man's voice came from one of the levels.

Two women followed suit with a dry laugh.

Garen looked at the Ancestral God Tree from afar. On the giant branch, Phiroth stood triumphantly with both of his hands on his hips. Behind him were the black bear and a handsome young man. Both of them looked ashamed. This time, Phiroth humiliated the eight generations of Daniela.

After tugging on the skin of his face, Garen still took the poop-like seed of the Ancestral God up and kept it. He didn't touch it with his hands but formed a tray with water vapor. He wrapped the green poop and placed it the isolation box, which was prepared beforehand.

"New experience. This is really a new experience.." Wukang shook his head at the side with a painful expression. "What do you think? Should we absorb it, or not?"

Garen tug on the skin of his face. "The outer appearance is just a facade. Do not be restricted by the eyes of the world…

Chapter 480: Clash 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Island Master Wukang was laughing hysterically.

Although he was speechless in reaction to Phiroth's prank of changing the shape of the Seed of the Ancestral God, what had to be absorbed has to be absorbed.

While the shape was like so, the content wasn't…

Two of them sat on their knees as they face the crystal made transparent isolation box. They both reached out their palms and placed them firmly on it. Then, they closed their eyes and absorb the life force inside it through Secret Techniques.

The pure and strong life force left the isolation box like a small river and flowed into Garen and Lightless' body.

This life force was much stronger than the air previously but it was very neutral, unlike the invasive air.

As both of them were absorbing it, they could clearly see that the green poop inside the isolation box had started to shrink.

Time passed slowly.

The night sky unknowingly turned brighter as the green light started dimming. Twilight had started to break in the sky.

After some time, Garen suddenly opened his eyes.

Roar!

The red dragon's shadow flashed past his face.

"Four dragon heads have merged…" He casually felt the changes of the Black Water True Technique inside his body. Four out of nine dragon heads had been absorbed by him.

The absorption of the dragon heads was not able to give him more strength as it was just a conversion of energy from the totem into Secret Technique.

The totem had weakened but in returned, the Secret Technique had evolved.

There was no change in the overall strength. However, as the strength was converted into the Secret Technique, he could apply this strength onto his actual body and evolve to a level he couldn't have achieved previously.

The Black Water True Technique's strength had undoubtedly become stronger again as there were only five heads out of nine left from the nine-headed hydra totem. The remaining heads were in high spirits and not on the verge of dying under the effect of the life force.

It was estimated that the convergence of the fifth head wouldn't take long after this.

This was the benefit of the Seed of the Ancestral God.

Garen suddenly recalled the original ability of the Seed of the Ancestral God was to enhance the totem strength.

He closed his eyes as he felt the changes in his body and he could feel that his internal organs had become more active than before. Furthermore, he was able to control the Nine-Headed Hydra with his mind better and he felt that he still had more strength left in reserve.

He opened his eyes and glanced at the attribute pane.

‘Strength 14. Agility 10. Vitality 10. Intelligence 10. Potential 35124%. Possess the qualification of a Luminarist.

Seed of the Ancestral God Enhancement: Increased totem control limit by 1.'

"An additional totem to control? Not bad." Garen nodded in satisfaction. Compared to the increased merging speed of the dragon head, it seemed pointless to increase the totem's strength.

He'd originally planned to obtain some small benefit but he didn't expect to reduce the merging duration. It was indeed an accidental reward.

The sky had turned bright.

Garen and Wukang walked out of the stronghold after they finished absorbing the Seed of the Ancestral God. Although both of them obtained something beneficial, they had a strange look on their face.

As they walked outside of the stronghold's forest, they saw a few guards patrolling in the area and didn't see much totem users outside as they're probably still absorbing the Seeds of the Ancestral God.

Before the seed appeared, the atmosphere here was very strict. Everyone was cautious against each other as conflict might occur at any given moment. However, the atmosphere had loosened a lot the moment the seed was condensed since one would have to wait until next year before the next one appeared.

Daniela had sent out a group of typically trained soldiers led by low-level totem users. Conflicts had been dramatically reduced and the typical argument could be settled by these patrols.

Garen and Wukang were walking outside and they didn't think that the release of the seed of the Ancestral God would greatly affect the plants in the forest. Some of these plants had completely changed and some had been sucked dry by some parasites. It's as if the whole forest had undergone a big change.

As the Ancestral God Tree was huge, both of them were almost lost as it was a no-fly zone.

As Wukang was about to wave his hand to the patrols and request for them to guide the way, Garen on the side stopped him.

"There's no need to rush. Let me handle it."

Garen glanced at the surrounding patrols and he grinned.

"You! Come over!" He pointed at a short patrol.

This person was in an all-white armor and helmet. He was lowering his head as he followed his team from behind and seemed completely unwanted in any way.

Garen's eye slightly turned red as he glanced at this patrol once more.

The leader of the patrol team heard their call and ran towards them.

"Sir, what order do you have?" The team leader was a middle age man and he looked very humble.

"We have lost our way as the geography of this place changed last night so we need a person to guide us around. There's no doubt about it, let him guide us!" Garen pointed at the shorty standing at the very back of the team.

"Alright alright… Garfield, you'll now follow these two lords and guide them in their path. Report back to me when you're done, understand!?" The leader talked to the shorty sternly.

"Understood!" The shorty's voice was quite coarse.

"What happened to your voice?" The team leader was stunned and asked him softly.

"It's nothing. I had a flu last night…" The shorty Garfield answered immediately.

The team leader patted his shoulder and whispered.

"Go ahead. Do your best. Perhaps these lords would reward you greatly."

The shorty Garfield nodded seriously.

Garfield stayed back with Garen and Wukang after he gave him his orders. The patrol team then continued their patrolling.

Garen looked at the shorty Garfield when the team was further away from them.

"Alright. We planned to look at the Ancestral God Tree in a close distance. You have no problem with leading the way right?"

Garfield was always lowering his head and immediately answered as his body kept shivering." No problem! Of course, there is no problem in that."

Wukang who was at one side noticed something was wrong but he didn't say much as he saw Garen's expression. He was wondering what Garen had in his mind.

The three of them walked into the dense forest and increased their pace.

The totem users in the stronghold started to appear due to the change in the landscape. Most of the totem users were cautious towards Garen and the others when they saw them and would act in such a manner that they didn't know them and avoid them completely.

Only small amounts of totem users who were confident in their strength would walk past them.

As the distance to the Ancestral God Tree grew shorter, the area of the stronghold became larger and the population of the totem users gradually increased as well.

They could see a totem user in the strongholds every few ten meters. These totem users were in all kinds of clothes and they're obviously outside guests from different backgrounds.

Soon, the trio arrived at the second layer of the triangle and they headed straight to the first layer of the triangle.

A team of men in red shirts were guarding the passage up front and the leader's eyes were glowing as he stared at the totem users who passed by.

The core of the first layer wasn't as on alert as before after the condensation of the seed, and anyone could freely enter and exit the place. Many people had the same intention as Garen as they purposefully tried to get closer to the Ancestral God Tree. The Ancestral God Tree Pillar's totem user was also walking inside the gap within the stronghold.

They had created a wall at the core layer and there were only three entrances and exit.

However, they weren't sure when this group of red-shirted people had appeared at the entrance of the passageway.

They weren't on guard but they were guarded by the side as they stared at the passers-by, as if they were looking for something.

Garen and the other two walked towards the entrance as they followed the totem users in white robes in front of them.

As they got closer to the men in red shirts, Garen could feel that the patrol Garfield who was leading the way started to tense up.

He was anxious.

Fortunately, the trio walked into the passageway without any issue. The leader of the red-shirted men stared at the trio and paid extra attention towards Garfield.

After they passed the tall walls, up in front was the zone where it was shaded by the Ancestral God Tree. The giant tree was like a giant green umbrella planted onto the ground as the branches draped over a clear small lake. A group of small mushrooms was making noises as it jumped and collided with each other. The air was filled with green light dots, the same green lights they'd seen last night.

Giant crystal butterflies were fluttering about as they flew around the branches. There were transparent ones, yellow ones, white ones and black ones. There were many of them stopping at the bush which was four to five meters tall.

"Hold right there!!" A voice broke from behind the trio all of the sudden. The voice was deep like thunder as it deafened a nearby totem user in white robes.

A lightning sound was heard and deep blue lightning landed in front of them. The red-shirted man appeared in front of them.

The man was tall, tanned and his gaze was of lightning as it gave off a tingling sensation like a sun. His red robes were like a tight suit on him as they outlined his strong and muscular body.

What was most interesting was that there was a blue-black glowing light on his right side of the neck, as if a firefly was resting there. It was the size of a bean and it could be clearly seen.

The man glanced at Garen and Wukang before he focused his attention on the patrol Garfield.

"This man seems very suspicious. I suspect him to be the spy who had escaped away from the Cthulhuism Society. Men!"

"Yes!"

"Take the spy away for interrogation!" The man raised his hand as two men in red shirt went up against the patrol Garfield.

"Oh? How dare you to take away my guide right in front of me! The Cthulhuism Society sure is imposing!" Garen glared as he suddenly appeared in front of Garfield.

"Nine-headed Snake Garen, I have yet to approach you for the old matters. Looks like you don't plan on leaving Daniela alive…" The black-skinned man's expression changed as he stared at Garen.

"Since you know who I am, perhaps you people from the Cthulhuism Society haven't learned your lesson yet…" Garen's expression changed as well as he knew the man in front of him was not a simple character.

"Thunder God Havana, the person you want is me! Don't drag the others into the situation!" Unexpectedly, the patrol took away his helmet, revealing his white hair. He was a short youngster with the character Chuan imprinted on his forehead.

He faced the Thunder God head-on without any sign of fear.

Surprisingly, Island Master Wukang grinned as he walked to the front.

"All of you step back. Today, I want the Cthulhuism Society to learn the reason for which I'm famous!!"

Chapter 481: Clash 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A huge screen of black smoke billowed from Wukang’s body before he finished his sentence. He planned to reveal his Wukang Prison here.

Wukang, who had been following Garen around to purge people from the Cthulhuism Society, was very unhappy with the crazies who had been spewing nonsense everywhere. In addition to the obstruction by the four members of the Cthulhuism Society during his journey, he’d held resentment from the moment the King of Holy Lake defeated him on the spot.

Wukang and the Thunder God glared at each other as one grinned while the other looked on in contempt. Both of them instantaneously turned into a screen of black smoke and lightning respectively.

In a mere instant, the black smoke and lightning clashed against each other at least ten times.

Huge amounts of black smoke and lightning arcs spread about in the surrounding, forcing the members of the Cthulhuism Society and Garen to take a few steps back to distance themselves.

Garen stared at the battle between those two.

The Thunder God didn’t use any special ability and was only relying on the high velocity movement which formed into lightning. He kept moving about as he attacked instantly and every attack he lashed out had high momentum and electrical effect.

On the other hand, Wukang was releasing a huge amount of black smoke and he could instantly move anywhere within the black smoke. His whereabouts was unknown as the smoke was an extension of his body. Furthermore, the smoke appeared to be poisonous as well, which was the reason Thunder God didn’t dare to get close to it; he kept vaporizing the black smoke that was approaching him.

Both of them were considered the speed type and within seconds, the black smoke was rebounded back towards Garen and Wukang staggered out of the black smoke with a pale face.

"I couldn’t fully utilise the Wukang Prison due to the air restriction zone…!" Wukang grumbled angrily.

"Do you think you have the chance to get closer to me without the air restriction zone?" Thunder God Havana smiled coldly.

It looked like Wukang had the disadvantage. After all, their difference in strength was apparent.

"I didn’t expect the Cthulhuism Society has someone like you with them…" Although Wukang was at the peak of form four, he showed off his extreme battle strength and was able to go against the form five Thunder God. However, he was able to experience the strength of a form five for the first time during this probing.

Furthermore, he wasn’t considered strong compared to the Cthulhu King even though they were at the same level. Their main strength was the Immortal Body and Alliance Tactic and these two skills were not revealed at all just now.

Thunder God looked at Garen as his eyes were slightly filled with fear.

"Looks like you guys plan to go against my Cthulhuism Society?"

Garen started smiling.

"I heard that there’re three kings in the Cthulhuism Society who are the strongest within the society and the Thunder God is one of them. I wonder how your strength fares as compared to the other two kings?"

The Thunder God narrowed his eyes without changing his expression.

"The Light God is obviously much stronger than me. As for the strongest God, the Water God. His strength isn’t something that should be compared to mine. Lord Water God once stated that he doesn’t have the confidence to win against you. At first I thought he was just being humble, but it looks like you’re the real deal…"

"What are you trying to imply?" Garen said coldly.

"Regardless, this guy is the reincarnation of the previous Thunder God of the Cthuhulism Society. You don’t plan to meddle in our personal issues, do you?" Havana moved his gaze to the short patrol Garfield.

"The previous generation’s Thunder God?!"

The totem users nearby who overheard the claim had their eyes onto the patrol Garfield in shock.

Garen, too frowned slightly. Although there were very few rules that totem users followed, there were still a few rules that they obeyed. One of the major taboos was to never meddle in other people’s internal affairs as meddling with other people’s affairs meant that they were declaring war in the totem world.

Although he had killed a few members from the Cthulhuism Society, this didn’t hurt them at all as the Cthulhu could revive them as many times as they wanted. Dying once simply meant that they were defeated once.

If they were to declare war, the battle would be endless.

Furthermore, if other parties were to found out that he meddled with another party’s internal affairs, it would leave a bad taste for the other parties.

"This is the battle for the Thunder God’s position. It’s not open to some outsider’s meddling." Havana said coldly.

Garfield, who was quiet about the ordeal the entire time, finally opened his mouth.

"That year, you ambushed me from the back, severely injuring me and caused me to lose most of my power. I had no choice but to reincarnate and the whole Thunder God Society has been absorbed by the Cthulhuism Society. Have I not been nice to you as the Lightning Attacker? Why!?" His eyes were glowing in blue as he spoke as the Thunder God of the previous generation.

Havana smirked.

"Why do you ask? Do you think a mere Thunder God Society could go against the powerful Cthulhu King? I know you have a death wish but it didn’t mean the others had it as well! And you still dare ask why? What a joke."

Garfield shook his head.

"The Thunder God’s will is to rage and purify. The characteristic of such power is chaos and disobedience. For these past few years, do you really think you have gained the trust of the Cthulhu King? In the folklore, the Thunder God is known as the forbidden god. Right at this moment, do you feel that parts of your body have been slowly electrified? Do you feel it? The immense pain from your chest whenever the spring thunder rings."

His face turned grey.

"Do you really think that I would be easily ambushed by you guys back then? Do you really think I have lost my mentality? You disappoint me. You didn’t even realize after so many years. I thought that you have realized it by now."

The arrogant look on Havana’s face slowly dissipated as Garfield continued. His cheek started twitching as an unnatural expression appeared on his face.

Garen and Wukang had already retreated to one side. Wukang, who had been holding on all this while, was injured quite badly. He was in a serious disadvantage against the Thunder God as he couldn’t output his actual strength.

It would be natural to let the two generations of Thunder God to settle their affairs between themselves.

Garen occasionally set his sight onto Garfield as he was skeptical of him.

He was the will adaptee of the Cthulhu who could easily dispel the origin of the Cthulhu King, Hannet Thunderstorm. He matched every details the intel he had searched. It’s just that he didn’t expect him to be the Thunder God of the previous generation.

No matter if it’s Garen or the Obscuro Society who wished to absorb the Cthulhu’s Origin, one must go through him. Without his help in purifying the Cthulhu King’s will, the Cthulhu’s Origin could not be absorbed and could only be considered a form of high grade preparation material.

If he didn’t predict wrongly…

Without any additional movement, Garen glanced at the crowd of totem users that had started to gather around.

Most of the totem users were observing from one side and some of them had grouped up to discuss about the two Thunder Gods. Some of them even took out crystal balls and cameras, to take an overall picture of the situation.

These totem users were not anxious at all due to the protection of the Ancestral God Tree and the alertness of the Royal Household of Daniela.

Among these totem users, Garen saw a slender, black human figure.

It was a woman in a black veil with a pair of white crescent moon earrings on her ears.

"So you’ve arrived, Emilo." this name flashed across Garen’s mind. She was an elite sent by the Obscuro Society who’d severely injured one of Daniela’s King with just an attack.

Since Emilo had appeared here and the Obscuro Society was on friendly terms with the Cthulhuism Society, she would definitely side the Cthulhuism Society if there were any conflict.

As he was lost in his thoughts, the two generations of Thunder God’s conversation had reached its end. Havana had lost his temper by the words of the previous generation’s Thunder God Hannet Thunderstorm. Even a commoner could see the fear on his face.

"The Cthulhu King has ordered to kill the previous generation Thunder God Hannet Thunderstorm on the spot!" Suddenly a sharp male voice could be heard from afar.

Havana was startled and with a slight delay, dark purple lightning ball formed around his hands.

"Don’t you want to know how to release yourself from this curse?" Hannet smiled without any anxiety.

The totem light force field on his body was only form 2 but he wasn’t scared at all. He stood still as he stared at the Thunder God. It was as if the opponent’s lightning balls were just a magic toy and were not something that could kill him instantly.

Havana struggled as he raised his hand while the lightning balls were moving violently in his hand but they wouldn’t move away from his hand.

"Thunder God! You dare to go against the Cthulhu King’s order!" The voice of the man could be clearly heard from the sky. However, there was no one in the sky. It was as if the person had used some sort of technique to communicate from afar.

Havana started to struggle even more as he slowly raised his hand and aimed at Hannet with the lightning ball. Thousands of beads of sweat formed on his forehead.

"There’s only one person who knows how to break the curse." Hannet was very calm as he smiled, as if he didn’t know that the lightning balls were aimed at him. "Havana, you can kill me if you really want to become a mindlessly obedient Thunder God."

"Don’t force me…!!" Havana’s dilemma had become more and more apparent. His voice even started to become coarse.

"The Cthulhu King never trusted you." Hannet said coldly. "He’s forcing you to kill me and it also means that you’re committing suicide."

"Just because of that legend?!"

"Perhaps." Hennet smiled. He was a young man, yet his smile was old.

"Die!!"

Suddenly, a pure white light was shot from the sky and was heading towards the calm Hennet.

The speed of this light was incredible fast. As the sky flashed, the light had already reached in front of Hennet. The light was surrounded by pure white feathers that were falling gently. It was as if the light was a gift from the Heavens.

"The Heaven’s Light! It’s the Light God!" A knowledgeable old totem user recognized the light.

"How dare you!!" A sharp tone of a woman came from the left side of the forest. Before she shouted, A black hole appeared in front of Hannet and a white slender hand came out from the hole and gently block the white light in front of him.

The hand gripped the egg-thicked light pillar and gently pinched it.

Boom!

The light pillar was completely shattered.

At the same time, the white hand from the black hole disappeared as well.

The crowd then reacted since a conflict finally occurred.

Some totem users the situation was rather complicated and started to retreat. Soon there were only a few people left who dared to stand still.

"What is the meaning of this, Marshall Aixi?"

A pure white humanoid figure appeared from the wall from the right. It was a handsome man with white hair, eyebrows and eyes. He had no pupil and his eyes were pure white. One would immediately know he was no ordinary elite just from his appearance.

On the left, black fire condensated and formed a human figure in a black cloak. One would immediately know that she was a female judging from her body figure. She was in a black veil and had a white crescent moon earrings on her. She was the self proclaimed Emilo sent by the Obscuro Society.

"You can’t kill him." Emilo’s voice was calm.

"No one can stop me, a member of the Cthulhuism Society, from killing who I want to kill." The Light God said calmly.

"I repeat, you can’t kill him." Emilo repeated once more.

The air around these two started to bend and both of them started to confront each other secretly.

"Aixi, a deal is a deal. However, didn’t you cross the line by butting into this matter?" The Light God showed his right hand and a white flame appeared above his palm.

Emilo didn’t say another word. Both of them were equally matched as they confronted each other and no one could do anything to the other party.

The situation had become a statemate.

"Aixi, are you really planning to meddle in the internal affairs of my Society?" Suddenly, a sonorous voice boomed from the sky.

Chapter 482: Clash 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This time it was a gentle woman’s voice, completely devoid of evil.

At the same time, Hannet Thunderstorm’s face turned purple as he stood in his original position. Blood started to pour out from the orifices on his eyes and nose.

Ah!

The dirt underneath Hannet moved about, and formed into a Mudman as tall as a person. The Yellow Mudman reached out its hand in front of Hannet’s body.

Boom!!

The Mudman suddenly exploded and formed into a pool of mud. What was peculiar was that the strange symptoms on Hennet’s body disappeared along with the Mudman’s explosion.

His face was filled with cold sweat as he took a few steps back, wiping off the blood on his nose and mouth.

"Mother Nature’s Substitution? Scylla Whitewater? Are you interfering with my religion too?" A hint of dissatisfaction appeared in her tone.

Soon, another Mudman appeared beside Hannet.

"Lord Water God, won’t it destroy your gentle, beautiful image if you were to kill people without any prior notice?" A young man’s voice came out from the Mudman.

"Do you think an Earth’s puppet could get in my way?" The Water God’s tone turned cold. "Although the Ultimate Heirloom is very powerful, it’s not something that would frighten me."

"It’s not entirely impossible to interfere with Lord Water God. However, if it were a substitution, that’s another story." Scylla smiled.

Within the short time of ten minutes, four elites had appeared and were battling each other in pairs. All of them appeared because of the previous generation’s Thunder God, Hannet Thunderstorm.

It was obvious that Scylla represented the Royal Household of Daniela, and the people from the Obscuro Society were protecting Hannet for some reason.

"Looks like we won’t be able to do anything today." Hennet smiled. "I didn’t know that I’m more valuable than I seemed to be. This is something."

The current Thunder God placed the Lightning Balls down. Both of them knew that the current situation was not decided by them, but by two overwhelming powers. One wrong move and it would become a full confrontation between the Royal Household and the Cthulhuism Society. Currently, both parties were not ready to go all out just yet.

The original body of the Water God must have been restrained by the King of the Stars of the Geometry Service; one of the three Major Departments. The Cthulhu King and the King of Daniele were restrained by one another. It was unknown what the influences of the two form five totem users of the Obscuro Society were, but they, too, stayed their hand.

"Looks like this is the current situation." Garen had become a bystander. "Both parties are not ready to go all out. Looks like Hannet’s life is…" Suddenly, his expression changed as he stared at the bottom of his leg before he could finish his sentence.

Boom!!

Suddenly, Garen was shot out to the middle of the sky above Hannet.

One fist!!

Kaboom!!!

The shockwave in the sky was clearly visible.

The resulting gale fluttered everyone’s robes, and a tree of leaves were blown off from their branches. Dirt and pebbles followed suit, blasted every which way as if there were an explosion. The pebbles that happened to impact trees far away punched a few holes through. Lastly was the surrounding totem users, who were forced to take a few steps back away from the shockwave.

Sizzle…!

Two black burnt marks appeared on both of Garen’s legs.

Roar!!

The dragon’s shadow flashed across his face as he stomped both of his legs into the ground to stabilize himself.

Red veins started popping out from his face as sweat started to vaporize on his muscular body. That was the steam created by him using his full strength.

He raised his head up and saw a huge bloody face appearing in the sky. The face was at least ten kilometers wide, skinned, muscles and tendons exposed for all to see.

The left eye was pitch black and there was a man in red robe and silver mask standing to the side of the eye.

That man looked down from afar as if he were a god looking down at mere mortals, as if he were a superior being.

"Cthulhu King…" Garen spelled out his name slowly.

The man didn’t stop for long at the side of the bloody face. Suddenly, he flew far away at great speed and disappeared at the horizon of the sky.

After a while, an explosion could be heard beyond the horizon of the sky. The ground started to tremble as a man’s laughter echoed throughout the sky.

"Since you have come to my Ancestral God’s Pillar, why don’t you stay for a bit! Let me give you a heart-warming welcome!!" It was Phiroth’s voice and it was obvious that he had engaged battle with the Cthulhu King.

Sigh…

Garen exhaled as wafts of white vapor came out from his mouth. It was easy to see how far Garen’s Black Water True Technique had come.

The Cthulhu King stood at the peak of the form five and his strength was not something that could be easily dealt with. There was a vast difference in strength between the peak of form five and below. With Garen’s current strength, he would have no problem in dealing with the middle class of form five. But a simple attack from the Cthulhu King…

"No! It’s not just a casual attack! He was spitting at him!!" Garen recalled the horrifying scene the Original Eye saw in that instant.

That silver masked man gave off such a terrifying strength by just spitting down at them.

Perhaps he planned to appear in that instant to interrupt the situation and leave afterwards, but in that instant, the king of Daniela Phiroth caught up and engaged in a battle with him.

The peak of form five was definitely different from the others.

A typical form five totem user could elementalize themselves, giving them the ability to travel fast within a very short amount of time. The speed could be benchmarked by the element they’re good at. However, this ability required a large amount of totem light and the travel distance couldn’t be very far apart. One would be considered very good if they were able to travel for a few thousand meters.

They’re much stronger compared to the spiritualized and form four elites but they shouldn’t be able to react this quickly.

Spiritualization was just a temporary form of self-elementization, where one could transmit Tactical Formations. On the other hand, form four totem users could move in short distances through elementization, but it required a lot of totem light. Form five totem users could use this short distance travel on a normal basis. It’s not something a typical elite could do.

These elites who stood at the peak of form five’s elementization speed was close to instantaneous teleportation, where they could instantly move about from far away. One could see most of the element traces left behind from a typical form five users.

Garen sighed as his body started to tremble.

"That was close. I almost got injured." His face was cold as ever. It’s best not to interfere during the early stages of merging with the Hydra. It was fortunate that he had the Heirloom Flash Screen, which had blocked off most of the force. The remaining force had been fended off by his Black Water True Technique, so he had managed to walk away unscathed.

Wukang came to him from the side.

"How does it feel?" In that instant, he, the Thunder God, Light God and Water God didn’t even realize Cthulhu King’s hidden attack. If not for Garen’s Original Eye, he wouldn’t even be able to notice it as well.

This technique was not a unique ability but a pure technique in utilizing his pure strength. With this attack, Garen realized he had greatly underestimated the Secret Techniques of this world.

He had been relying on his king of the century’s absolute minute control of strength to oppress his opponents of the same caliber. If the most gifted totem users could merge with his inner strength to produce 100% of his strength, then the effect of minute controlling could basically allow him to release 150% of his strength.

This strength had been one of the two major reliance for Garen. Now, the attack from the Cthulhu King reminded him that this world had someone who was better than him in terms of controlling their strength.

This mouthful of Qi gathered and condensed all totem light to produce such a terrifying power.

Garen was enlightened as he pushed Wukan away who was trying to help him.

"I’m alright. The Cthulhu King sure is something. He’s able to produce such a strong force with a basic exhalation."

He looked around his surroundings and he realized that in that instant, the Cthulhuism Society’s elites had retreated. Even Emilo from the Obscuro Society’s shadow could be seen in the forest as she had obviously left.

Only Scylla Whitewater and the previous Thunder God Hannet Thunderstorm were left in the scene.

"The Black Swamp Palace Master sure is strong. You can even go against the Cthulhu King’s ambush!" Scylla’s Mudman praised him as he walked closer.

"If it weren’t for you coming out and saving us, our face would have been thrown down into the river." Scylla said hopelessly.

"You’re being humble, leader." Garen immediately showed his respect. Scylla was Ender Kingdom’s strongest leader of the Ancient Society, excluding the Royal Household. He had tremendous authority and was also a cunning elite. Similar to Garen, his strength was similar to of a form five based on his strength and heirloom.

"I’m not being humble." Scylla shook his head. "Oh right, the seed from last night had been successfully transferred and could still last for another two hours. Daniela has reached its limit. Should we go and obtain our share?"

"Sure." Garen nodded. Daniela had promised that the additional Ancestral God’s Seed would be given to him and Wukang. It looked like it’s time to fulfill that promise.

"The Seed of Ancestral God can only be used once. I plan to give my seed to Xiwa." Wukan simply said.

Garen nodded. He originally hadn’t been interested in having an additional totem. However, with the activation from last night where he had completely absorbed, he had completely forgotten about using these two seeds at once.

This wouldn’t greatly affect him as the effect of Ancestral God’s Seed wasn’t something he wanted. What he really wanted is the seed’s intense life essence. This life essence was able to respond to the merging of Nine Headed Hydra and greatly reduce the merging duration.

With the next Ancestral God’s seed, he could reduce the absorption time for the fifth dragon head. Unfortunately, Daniela’s storage duration had reached its limit. If he were to have unlimited amounts of Ancestral God’s Seeds, the merging period could be greatly reduced.

This was the main advantage as the core of the Silver Totem. He wouldn’t have this benefit if the core totem was made from silver.

"Since the Cthulhu King is unable to kill Hannet himself this time, the Black Swamp Palace Master’s reputation will definitely spread." The Mudman Scylla was very affectionate. "Once you have absorbed the seed, are you interested in meeting a few friends of mine? We have some plans in mind, perhaps you will be interested in it."

"No problem." Garen was very interested in these kinds of small circles as these elites usually had their own intel circulating within them. This was what he was currently lacking.

Chapter 483: Deal 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After setting a time with Scylla, Garen turned around and looked at Hennet, who was standing to one side.

This seemingly young yet old white haired youngster was looking at them, something evidently on his mind.

"How do you guys plan to deal with me?" Hannet voiced out after noticing that Garen and Mudman were staring at him.

"I don’t know why the Obscuro Society is protecting you, but what I do know is that the Royal Household is so that the opponent cannot advance smoothly. I don’t think it’s very likely that you will be engaging in battles recklessly with the Cthulhuism Society."

Garen immediately cleared out the whole situation.

"What’s your objective?" Hannet raised his eyebrow.

"I need you to help me out." Garen’s abnormality gradually disappeared, returning back to his usual handsome self. His green veins had completely disappeared.

"Sure." Hannet nodded.

He hesitated for a moment before he moved his mouth, giving him a set of information.

Garen noted this down and rushed into the forest, disappearing as he turned around.

That information was the public channel data used for communication via radio. It seemed to be one of the communication methods used by Hannet and his people.

"Can we take our leave first?" Wukang’s face was pale from the battle with the Thunder God. Either he had exhausted too much, or else just didn’t want to be there anymore.

"You should head back first." Garen nodded.

Wukang’s female guard soon arrived. She delicately took out a few small bottles from her pockets, and mixed different colors of powders together for Wukang to consume.

"I’ve lost all my dignity this time." Wukang sighed as he swallowed the mixed medicine powder. "I can still deal with him if he were at a typical level. However, I didn’t expect him to be a form five, and even have this unique strength which coincidentally is a counter against me! But… if it weren’t for the restrictions in the area, I wouldn’t be afraid to fight him to the death."

Wukang’s personality was rather unstable. He wouldn’t loosen up even if he was with someone familiar. Garen looked at him holding onto his female guard speechlessly. He would secretly touched the female guard’s body here and there, pretending that his injury was severe enough to warrant it.

The female guard would always fall for this trick. She was even worried for him as she carried him, fearing that he was seriously injured. She didn’t even realize there was an additional hand near her nether areas…

The situation here had finally settled, and Garen followed Scylla to the Ancestral God Tree.

There were guards waiting for them at the bottom of the tree. As they saw Garen and Scylla arrive, their demeanor betrays the fact that they’ve been expecting them, and they immediately brought them to the Vine Road, the road which went straight to the Ancestral God Tree up to the largest branch.

Scylla’s Mudman dissolved at the foothold of the tree, and reappeared near the canopy, waiting for them.

As they walked along the heavily guarded Vine Road, they finally reached the giant branch after about ten minutes.

The King of Daniela, Phiroth was already back at the branch. He sat on his knees, smiling. There was a dark green vine winding at the table beside him, with a light green crystal placed on top of it. Two green, floating, feces-looking objects were floating within the crystals.

There was a young man in white shirt with golden sleeves beside Phiroth, who was also sitting on his knees on the branch. He had an awkward smile on his face, clearly because there was a beautiful woman in vine armor sitting beside him.

"What’s wrong? You’re not giving me any face at all, are you?"

Garen, who was standing from afar, could hear Phiroth’s deep tone towards the young man in the white shirt. Although he had a smile on his face, his tone was cold.

"Are you stating that I, Phiroth’s daughter, am not to your liking?"

This voice was as strong as thunder. Garen instantly understood. Phiroth was up to his tricks again… Planning to send her daughter away the moment he met someone…

As he resisted his urge to roll his eyes, Garen picked up his pace and immediately arrived at an empty space on a tree branch.

The atmosphere was stifling. The young man in the white shirt was ecstatic as he saw Garen’s arrival.

"Palace Master Garen you have arrived. Just like what we’ve discussed, let’s go meet some friends of mine. Your Majesty Phiroth… the problem we spoke of just now isn’t urgent. We’ll talk about it some other time, as I have made an appointment with Palace Master Garen…"

"Are you… Scylla?" Garen recognized the youngster’s totem light.

Phiroth’s eyelid started twitching.

"Good timing. I wanted to discuss something with Palace Master Garen regarding the Thunder God of the previous generation."

"Please say what you need, Your Majesty." Garen nodded as the guards sent up a plate of fruits. They took their places on the floor, kneeling. The plates were filled with the local specialties, the green bananas and fist-sized cherries.

Phiroth nodded.

"The Cthulhuism Society definitely has an upper hand against the previous generation’s Thunder God. They have been restrained by my Royal Household all this while, but now they don’t even care how they look when it comes to this. Looks like that Hannet guy is very crucial, at least to them."

"Your Majesty, what are you trying to say?" Garen asked softly.

"Hannet better not be in my sight from now on." Phiroth said, directly and without hesitation. He immediately turned his head and looked at the young man in the white shirt, and started to converse with Scylla.

Garen had doubts regarding this decision and pondered.

The previous generation Thunder God, Hannet Thunderstorm, impersonated as a guard to get close to the Ancestral God Tree -- Ancestral God’s Pillar. It was obvious that he had motives towards the Ancestral God’s Pillar.

While Garen didn’t know what Hannet’s intention was, it obviously had made Phiroth unsatisfied. This statement was obviously a warning towards Hannet.

"This is the Ancestral God’s Seed for the both of you." Phiroth turned his head around again and talked to Garen. "We’ve taken it out just last night and it’s very fresh. I have already sent my men to pass the seed to Wukang, rest assured."

Garen was speechless.

Garen took the pile of green defecation with him and bid goodbye to Phiroth together with Scylla before they left the branch.

Both of them walked down the road slowly. It took them about ten minutes or so to travel from the top to the tree to the ground, which was a good window for them to interact with each other.

Although Scylla looked very outgoing on the outside, he was actually a very mysterious person. It was impossible to know what was going on inside his head. As Garen’s personality was similar to his, both of them could understand each other better and were able to converse freely.

"Do you know why His Majesty Phiroth has such an attitude towards Hannet? While he’s the Thunder God of the last generation, he’s only a mere form two totem user. The strength deficit between His Majesty Phiroth and Hannet is far too great. But.. why did he have to say such a phrase at the end?" Garen decided to pour out his curiosity as he talked to him.

Since both of them had such similarities and were getting along with each other, Scylla chose not to hide anything from him, and told him the reason after some consideration.

"Perhaps Palace Master hasn’t heard of it yet. When the Cthulhu King and His Majesty were fighting against each other, they also talked as well. It was about that guy Hannet."

"Oh?"

Scylla started to frown.

"During that time, Cthulhu King pointed out that hannet’s motive is the Ancestral God’s Pillar, as he is qualified to absorb its strength. He has the legendary Winged God Arms. Although the strength of the Ancestral God’s Pillar has always been under the control of Daniela Royal Household, His Majesty wasn’t sure if it would affect the current Ancestral God Pillar if the Hannet were to inherit it."

"Is that so?" Garen sort of understood the situation.

He had managed to find an explanation to this issue. Garen then asked about the giant stone statue’s incident related to the Ender Kingdom. The angel giant stone statue appeared among the nests of creatures during the attack of Kovitan. Kovitan wasn’t the only one investigating this issue; even the Ender Kingdom was having a hard time about it in the dark.

As he raised this incident, Scylla’s face was filled with rage. He wasn’t sure who had stolen the key to controlling the angel statue. This weapon of warfare was usually stationary, and would only be used once every few centuries. However, this had given others an opportunity to steal it. The people who were responsible for the loss of the key hadn’t report the actual incident to the upper management in fear of getting punished. Instead, they reported that the key had been broken and used some technique in forging a new key.

When they realized something was wrong, the angel statue was already on the move, causing havoc.

Ender Kingdom had dealt with everyone responsible for the incident.

As both of them were talking along the way down, A group of female guards were on their way up, flanking and holding a girl.

The girl had an hourglass body and was in a purple cloak. Her black hair was waist-long and her skin was white as snow. A purple veil hid her face and a pair of, deep, unfocused purple eyes.

This girl was being held by the female guards, as if they were scared that she might slip and fall.

"It’s princess Dilan." Scylla walked to the side as he pulled Garen, who hadn’t reacted.

The female guards who were walking towards them bowed to both of them, before they continued carrying the purple clothed girl up.

The woman acted as if Garen and Scylla weren’t there, instead leaning towards one of the guards, exchanging hushed whispers.

Garen frowned. He waited until the group was far away before he asked softly.

"Princess Dilan? The princess doesn’t seem to know proper manners, no?"

"Don’t misunderstand." Scylla shook his head. "Rumor has it that Princess Dilan is the favorite princess of His Majesty Phiroth. Her beauty is unparalleled and she has an amazing body. Her voice is as touching as hundreds of birds. However, she has a major flaw."

"Flaw?"

"Yes. and it is an uncurable one as well." Scylla nodded in confidence. "She was born retarded and blind."

"Are you sure?" Garen recalled the purple shirted woman. She indeed seemed like she was blind, but retarded...

"This is the truth. Princess Dilan has the intellect of a typical three-year-old. She also has serious memory loss. This is an open secret everyone in the Royal Household of Daniela knows." Scylla shrugged. "She’s just like a piece of white paper. She knows nothing and can’t even recognize her own daughter and treats her as a stranger. She can immediately forget the things that happened a few minutes ago. What’s most surprising is that the only person she can remember is His Majesty Phiroth."

Garen then understood that there’s no point in being offended by her manners when she’s naturally born with this sickness.

When both of them left the Ancestral God Pillar, they sat on the flying bubble to the second Ancestral God Tree. There were already people waiting for him to the other side. Two women in white attire clapped their hands and greeted them with a peaceful expression.

"Lord Scylla has returned. Lord Sith and the others are waiting for you."

"Lead the way." Scylla said coldly.

Chapter 484: Deal 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Two women nodded and walked to the front, bringing the duo away from the flying point. They walked down for a few hundred meters along the tree branches, and finally stopped at an oval shaped hole in the tree.

Both women stopped outside the door as Scylla pulled Garen into the tree hole.

It wasn’t very spacious inside, and the inner wall of the tree hole was painted in gold. The surrounding walls were placed with green vine stone pillars, and there were realistic sculptures of animals on top of these pillars. There were giant eagles, lions, two headed snakes and four eyed sugar gliders.

Black chairs were placed in between these pillars, of which some already had occupants. Two people who had arrived before they had.

These two stood as they saw Scylla and Garen enter.

"This is?" There were one male and one female. The man had a small mustache on top of his lips, and his silver attire made him looked like a noble. He was also wearing a white bottom, long leather boots and was even wearing a white curly wig.

The woman was in a green, full body short dress and had a green longbow behind her back. She had one green eyepatch on her that made her look like a one-eyed dragon. Her slightly black hair was placed in front of her chest, and she was staring at Garen who just entered the hole.

"The Black Swamp Palace Master, Nine Headed Hydra Garen of Kovitan. I’m sure you two have heard of him, right?" Scylla smiled as he introduced Garen.

Both of their pupils shrunk at the same time, and it was obvious that they have heard of his name.

The man immediately revealed a gentle smile.

"So it’s Palace Master Garen in the flesh. I am the Tower of the Read Leaf’s tower master of the Ender Kingdom, Duoren."

"The Nine Headed Hydra Garen is very famous. Your name has even spread far to my Willow Valley of the Ender Kingdom." The woman spoke softly. "No wonder Scylla would invite you to participate in our activity."

"This is the valley master of the willow valley, Limalanda." Scylla introduced.

Garen greeted both of them and found out that both of their essences were clouded. It was obvious that they were using some Heirloom to hide their strength. However, whoever was able to interact with Scylla with the same level must be someone strong. They were both form four elites.

After some niceties were served, Scylla waved his hand, and the cave was suddenly covered with a layer of yellow light.

They settled down on their seats.

Garen placed one of his hands onto the ancestral God’s Seed Crystal as he slowly absorbed it while listening to them talking.

The Red Leaf Tower Master Duoren was the first one to speak up.

"With Scylla as the leader this time and Palace Master Garen to watch over us, the trade between Cthulhuism Society shouldn’t be any issue."

"We should be cautious. The Cthulhuism Society has always been very cunning. The previous incident is our lesson." Limalanda objected softly.

"We don’t have to worry about this part. As long as it’s not Cthulhu King himself who comes for the trade, I am confident that I can retreat without any issue, even if it’s the Water God." Scylla said confidently. "Palace Master Garen, I believe you have heard about the trades with the Cthulhuism Society for the Cthulhu’s Origin, right?"

"Yes." Garen nodded. "Are you planning to do a secret trade with the Cthulhuism Society?" In his mind, he was pondering on how to get in touch with the other side. He didn’t expect someone to hand him the solution.

"That’s right." Scylla didn’t intend to hide from Garen. "Everyone here possesses Glittering Water. Especially you, lord Garen, I believe you have obtained quite a few Glittering Water since you seize quite a few Glittering Pool, right?"

"That’s true." Garen didn’t deny it.

Scylla smiled. "Though it’s true that we are members of the Royal Alliance and it’s a major taboo to occupy resources to themselves before an impending war, I refuse to believe that the Cthulhuism Society is able to turn the tides by obtaining Glittering Water. On the other hand, we are able to further strengthen the potential of our core totems by obtaining the Cthulhu’s Origin. This will be our foundation in advancing into form five."

He paused for a while. "Frankly, His Majesty Phiroth understood this. However he’s just acting as if he knows nothing about it." He occasionally placed his gaze on the valley master of the Willow Valley, Limalanda.

"However we’re unsure of the amount of Glittering Water we have is enough to trade for one Cthulhu’s Origin." The Red Lead Tower Master Duoren said as he frowned.

"Don’t worry about that. I have specifically brought along the trading schedule from the other party, and it clearly marks the prices of the products." Without any hesitation, Scylla pulled out a small piece of paper from his shirt. He then gently opened it, and out came the Danielian alphabet, densely packed together.

He jittered his hand and threw the papers out as it floated between the four people.

Scylla turned the white ring on his finger.

Suddenly, a layer of semi-transparent glass surrounded the paper, and all four of them had one each. On it, the relevant information was clearly stated.

Garen looked carefully at the information.

‘Trading price: One upper-level Cthulhu’s Origin is equivalent to a hundred units of Glittering Water. (Enough for one person’s usage)’

‘One middle-level Cthulhu’s Origin is equivalent to fifty Glittering Water.’

‘One lower-level Cthulhu’s Origin is equivalent to ten Glittering Water.’

‘One lower quality Cthulhu’s Origin is equivalent to two Glittering Water.’

The price was clearly written, but Garen didn’t understand the difference between the grades of the Cthulhu’s Origin.

He had about twenty two Glittering Water that he obtained along the road. These were the amount the he always had on him, as these things condensed very slowly and were not something that could be easily accumulated. In addition to the amount he had in his vault, which was about thirty, he couldn’t even trade for one middle-level Cthulhu’s Origin if he were to use the pay scale here.

"These Cthulhu’s Origins are separated into different grades?" Limalanda frowned as she asked. "What does it mean to have different grades of Cthulhu’s Origin? I wonder if you have asked clearly about it, Scylla."

Scylla smiled as he nodded.

"This naturally has to be cleared up."

He pointed at the upper-level Cthulhu’s Origin.

"This is the highest quality Origin, which is extracted directly by Cthulhu King and is of the strongest origin. Hence it’s the upper-level."

His finger then moved to the middle-level Cthulhu’s Origin.

"This is the origin extracted out by the Water God, so it’s middle-level."

The lower-level is extracted by the Light and Thunder Gods, and the lower quality ones are extracted by the normal Cthulhu." Scylla explained it very clearly.

He then continued. "I have already traded a lower quality origin to try out, and it indeed has an obvious effect in enhancing totem potential. The effect is very good as well. If we were to use a hundred of them, I’m confident that our core totems will be twice as powerful! We can even go past the fifth form and reach greater heights!"

Sizzle…

Including Garen, the three of them inhaled a mouthful of cold air.

Scylla right now was able to fight against the Water God’s substitute. If he were twice as strong, how strong would that be? He would be considered a powerful opponent even among the fifth forms.

"If the lower quality has such an enormous effect, then the better ones…" Garen’s eyes were fired up.

"We still have to trouble you to set a time and place for the trade." Limalanda said softly.

"This isn’t a problem at all." Scylla responded happily. "Coincidentally, I have planned for a trade the night after tomorrow. We can move together then."

"Thank you, leader." Duoren’s face was brimming with excitement. Limalanda’s expression had softened a lot as well.

Garen, who was sitting at one corner, kept the same expression on his face as he suddenly inquired.

"I wonder if the leader has some remaining Cthulhu’s Origin for us to look at."

Scylla smiled.

"I see Palace Master understands me well. I indeed left some so that I could compare it with the higher grade ones in the future."

He placed his left hand into his waist and opened up his palm.

A green crystal ball the size of a fist appeared. The interior of the crystal ball was filled with green smoke. It looked cold, as it quietly floated on his palm.

The smoke inside the small ball kept rotating, and one could faintly see strange images formed inside it. The green seeds inside sprouted, grew bigger, with flowers blooming and forming new seeds, then finally wilted. The new seeds were then sprouted again.

These images kept cycling again and again. The smoke within the crystal was moving about, as if it contained an innumerable amount of souls within.

"This Origin comes from the Wood God, and I have used up most of it. What’s left is only one percent left of the amount I have traded so it can only form some smoke." Scylla smiled as he passed the crystal ball to Garen. "Have a look."

Garen reached out his hand and took it and he suddenly felt a jolt.

Although the totem light’s force field inside the crystal wasn’t big, it gave off the feeling that there was something alive inside the ball. As he held it in his hand, he felt like he was holding an egg that was about to hatch. He could feel the sensation of a heartbeat coming from within.

At that time, the Ancestral God’s Seed had already been absorbed by him and he could recover soon from the next merge. He expected that the merging duration with the next dragon head would be greatly reduced within the week.

As he put away his right hand, Garen carefully observed the Cthulhu’s Origin.

The green smoke inside the crystal ball kept moving about and the images of the seed sprouting until it wilted kept repeating inside. As he observed closer, he realized that these images were formed by countless smoke particles, without any order.

As Garen held onto it, he could faintly smell the fresh fragrance of the leaves and flowers.

.

According to the original timeline, this item only appeared once, and it was from a normal commander-level member of the Obscuro Society who reached the peak of the form five by absorbing it. He was then on the same level as God Cloud. There was no related news regarding this afterwards.

Now that Scylla and the others planned to trade for the Cthulhu’s Origin, and since there were so many grades for them to trade with, why weren’t there any more people revealing the secrets of the Cthulhu’s Origin in the history?

This question flashed through Garen’s mind.

Since so many people had absorbed it, did that mean the effect was most obvious among the members of the Obscuro Society?

Garen suddenly recalled the issues with the Cthulhu King’s Will in the Cthulhu’s Origin. Was it because of this?

He pondered for a while before he passing the crystal ball to Limalanda before he turned his head to look at Scylla.

"Scylla, did you absorb it directly after you obtain the origin or…?"

"Don’t worry. I was worried that the Cthulhuism Society would pull my leg as well so I only absorbed it after making sure the thing is safe through detailed analysis." Scylla said. "I didn’t expect the effect was exceptionally good."

Garen didn’t change his expression but he was very sure of something.

There was something wrong with these Cthulhu’s Origin. Without an adaptee to filter out the Cthulhu King’s will and to absorb the origin just like that…

Garen squinted his eyes as he could smell something sinister from this simple trade...

Chapter 485: Deal 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After discussing with the others in the cave, Garen bid them farewell and left alone, sitting on the flying bubble as he flew towards the giant tree where he stayed.

As for the fact that Cthulhu's Origin contained Cthulhu's Will, he didn't immediately say it out loud. If he said it just like that, Scylla and the others might not believe him, after all they barely knew each other, if he said something too deep while their knowledge of each other was still so shallow, it might make them wary of him instead.

Cthulhu's Origin was the main reason he came to Daniela this time. It was an aberrated treasure that could let a regular Form Five reach the peak level, the Cthulhuism Society wouldn't bring something like that out so easily.

Sitting in the bubble, Garen looked down at the green canopy of trees below him, a flash of understanding in his eyes.

"No wonder the Cthulhuism Society wanted to kill the previous Thunder God, Hannet, no matter the cost, because only he has the right to filter Cthulhu's Will, as long as he was gone, then the Cthulhu's Origin that was sent out would become so many ticking time bombs, becoming a trump card for their battles."

After returning to his residence, Wukang's tree hole up there was utterly quiet, some black smoke roiling faintly in the cracks of the doors and windows on the tree hole, the long and large breathing inside repeating endlessly, Wukang was evidently focused on healing his injuries.

Garen went past Wukang's tree hole, and was about to return to his own tree hole.

Boom!!

Suddenly there was a huge dull noise, as though something had exploded. The Ancestral God Tree also jolted slightly, shaking somewhat, many branches and leaves floating down on him like raindrops.

Garen frowned, turning around and looking towards the direction of the explosion.

Roar!!!!

In the distant white sky, a huge red bird spread its wings and raised its head, making a terrifying loud howl, like that of a bird but also of a lion or a tiger.

The huge bird was covered in a red glow, its feathers a fiery bright red, it had six tails, and each tail was a poisonous red snake, the end of the tails being the snake heads that kept reaching out their slithery tongues as though they wanted to eat you whole.

The whole giant bird almost took up half of the sky in the distance, its body a full hundred meters in size.

Garen was also shocked by the bird's size for a moment, but after looking at it closely, he discovered something odd about it.

The bird's body looked solid, but it actually had a vague insubstantial feeling.

"It's the Geometry Service's Royal Star Court's Starry Sky Summoning!"

Garen suddenly remembered the information he had read before.

'From an unnamed starry sky galaxy, a temporary helper who can reply your call is summoned, by paying a certain price in return, obtain a response from an unnaturally terrifying existence from an unknown time and space.'

That was the description of the Starry Sky Summoning, it was also the Royal Star Court Master's secret ultimate technique, to think it would suddenly be used now.

"Who on earth could it be? To be able to force the Court Master to use such a terrifying secret spell!" Garen's heart gave a jolt as he watched the projection of the bird pounce down, its mouth wide open as it instantly sprayed out countless little red flame birds, covering land and sky as they cascaded down.

These little red birds were not solid either, they were all silhouettes made of red flames, when they were sprayed out, they actually all opened their mouths as well, and once more spat out currents of flames tinged with gold.

The gold flames gathered together, forming a small river that flowed relentlessly and quietly downwards.

Garen watched the huge bird's movement carefully. He had seen some information in a dissection book before, it was an anonymous scholar's research content.

He had been extremely interested in this surprisingly scary Starry Sky Summoning, and had spent a lot of time and energy researching it in particular. In the end, he came to a conclusion.

The Starry Sky Summoning did not actually call over a powerful existence from a starry galaxy, that did not follow the rules of energy conservation at all, to transcend here from a faraway galaxy would use some astronomical energy just on the journey itself, what was more the power needed to fight for the summoner.

In actuality, the core principle of the Starry Sky Summoning should be a sort of derivation, a technique to construct life.

The creatures that it can summon were all actual living creatures from the beginning phase, after they figure out all of the creature's biological structures and way of existence, the creatures can be summoned. The cost was a huge amount of Totem Light.

And then there was the middle level phase, which was to summon some special creatures that were slightly out of the ordinary, with special powers, and the cost would be Totem Light and some specific special items.

The last final phase was to summon fully-derivated terrifying creatures that had appeared at some point in time and space, the cost being a tremendous amount of Totem Light and a very specific rare item.

Actually, according to the scholar's research, the very beginning of the Starry Sky Summoning had been used to test if the structures of these derivated creatures had existed before. This technique had only been a sort of practical experimental technique, but after merging it with instant structural studies, it had become this terrifying offensive technique.

The huge bird that showed up now was the Star Court Master's signature Snake-tailed Bird, this was the strongest legendary creature derivated by the Star Court, although nobody knew when this terrifying creature existed, but its power was definitely at the peak of Form Five. Compared to peak-level fighters like the Cthulhu King and Phiroth, it wasn't as easily controllable, but when it came to pure power it was just as good. Of course, this didn't take the other methods these peak-level fighters could use into account.

This move was already the Star Court Master's strongest attack, and the power demonstrated by the Cthulhu King and Phiroth were just their normal states. The difference between them was obvious.

The Snake-tailed Bird was resisting against a dot of black light beneath it, the golden fire spraying recklessly as though it was free, this was clearly already its strongest attack, but it didn't have much of an effect on the black light dot beneath it.

Whoa-aah!!

A crisp sound, like the clash between metals. The black light suddenly shot out countless black chains, like a deity scattering flowers, spraying out in all directions.

The countless black metal chains were like living creatures, surrounding the Snake-tailed Bird from all directions.

The moment he saw the chains, Garen instantly recognized the user of this technique.

God Cloud!

He narrowed his eyes, a glint of danger rising in his eyes.

"It's definitely the true body, the true body that has the Distorted Bead!" Garen licked his lips, since the fight on the snowy peak back then, when he was grievously injured by God Cloud and had to escape, he couldn't keep it out of his mind.

But not only was God Cloud Obscuro's strongest military leader, he was also at the peak of Form Five, although he was defeated by Phiros in the past, he could still bulldoze past other Form Five fighters.

"He's not at the World Crevice, he's not controlling the situation or healing his wounds, why did he run all the way here?" Suspicion rose in Garen's heart.

This was Phiros' domain, with the help and increment from the Ancestral God Tree, he was already probably the strongest in history as long as he was here. Add that to an unnamed Original Heirloom.

Garen wouldn't have forgotten, that Daniela actually still had an Original Heirloom hidden away. Although it couldn't be as powerful as Kovitan's Caeserton. After all, Original Heirlooms had their categories too, Caeserton just happened to be perfectly suited for war. Regardless, this one couldn't be that bad, it should also have a special effect.

"The two of you, could you please take it for my, Phiros' sake, and call a temporary ceasefire?" Just as the black chains were madly shooting everywhere, and just about to completely surround the Snake-tailed Bird, Phiros' voice reached them.

God Cloud snorted, the black light shooting into the sky abruptly and vanishing, evidently disappearing into the distance.

"These are the Ancestral God Grounds, fighting is not allowed in this area." Phiros seemed to be explaining something to the Court Master, and then his voice fell silent.

The Snake-tailed Bird also rapidly shrunk, rather worse for the wear, and slowly became transparent, before disappearing into the air.

The many totem users who were being forced down below remained silent for more than ten whole minutes before they began discussing the battle that had just erupted again.

Their fight had only lasted a short while, but within the Ancestral God Grounds, there had already been a large piece of empty land that was completely burned away, covered with giant collapsed trees, and there was a raging golden fire burning away as well.

Soon enough, though, a green mist quickly spread across the area, rapidly extinguishing the golden flames, and the collapsed trees also began to grow new roots and shoots. They grew at a speed visible to the naked eye. Not long later, this area was once more covered with green, as though the damage from just now was just the aftereffects of a long-ago battle.

Garen stood on the tree hole, his sharp eyesight allowing him to watch all the changes clearly. Up until all the traces had been utterly recovered, only then did he finally return to his tree hole, closing the wooden door.

Everything inside the tree hole was completely quiet, the soundproofing was very good, and it seemed like a completely isolated little space.

Inside the hemispherical tree hole, there were many white vine decorations of different sizes hung about, and the tables and chairs were all grown directly out of the ground, so they could not be moved. A bush of small black flowers grew on the corner of the wall, emitting a natural and fresh minty fragrance, acting like a natural air freshener.

Turning on the black radio on the table, he simply tuned it to Daniela's public channel.

'...the later conflicts had created a hidden threat, since the Battle of Sunview back then, in order to take revenge for his wife's betrayal, Tesowork convinced Moro of the Black Light Tower, and activated the legendary World War…'

As soon as he turned on the radio, the female host's voice came from the machine, the program showing was one that explained historical wars.

In this era, with the rapid development of radios, after a bit of tweaking, some single-sided broadcasting techniques were successfully introduced, it was something similar to what they had on Earth, news and other programs appearing to meet demands. Daniela's people were usually battle-thirsty, so this sort of programs explaining the wars in history was especially popular.

He changed the channel, and after some static, a new voice came from the radio.

'...According to the West Continent, the Lyonesse incident should have been caused by a West Continent terrorist group, Forest Black Court. Although the group did not publicly claim the incident, the many clues showed that the Forest Black Court would be Lyonesse's biggest suspect."

This was intercontinental news.

Garen was slightly surprised, he didn't think that news from the West Continent would reach here so quickly too. Evidently, after totem users were utterly exposed and stopped hiding, walking into the limelight instead and using their totem skills, the Luminarists and forgers would surely have used all their methods to cross the continental distance, achieving rapid continental communication.

After the radio played some music, there was another man's clear voice.

'This is the intercontinental news.'

'After the event in Kovitan, the mastermind, the Obscuro Society has finally come to light. The leader of the Obscuro military division, God Cloud, announced yesterday that they would assume responsibility for this incident. The National Service's diplomacy division has also released a bounty warning, aimed for all of Obscuro's members…'

'In Daniela's 231st Forest City, there was a large-scale plague spreading today, a terrifying virus known as Grimlan Number Three is rapidly spreading, those infected would have swollen eyes, many tiny blisters forming on the surfaces of their eyeballs, making it unbearably itchy and painful for the patient. The infected would lose their vision within three days, and die after five. The relevant departments are sending researchers to discover a vaccine at the first possible moment.'

231st Forest City?

Garen's heart sank. That was a city close to Heart of Life.

Daniela's structure was different from other countries, their cities were like so many different-sized tribes, scattered and built across the limitless sea of trees, each city was hidden by many plants and trees, harmonious and natural, with beautiful surroundings. Before the chaos began, the whole of Daniela was a famous tourist spot. Most of the people wouldn't leave their hometowns, the people of Daniela, especially the normal people, were all very attached to their homes. As a result, the transportation between cities wasn't very developed either.

The benefit of that was that if a plague started in one place, it could be easily quarantined away.

Garen vaguely suspected that in the original history, Phiros hadn't actually set down the kill order because the concubine was assassinated, but mostly because of this sort of plague.

The original history had actually already been changed in some way.

After the regicide incident in Kovitan, Daniela would quickly discover that their concubine had been assassinated, and Phiros gave the order to carry out a massacre in the refugee camp of Heart of Life, but to think there was now a minuscule change in the process.

Obscuro was probably being hunted hard by the three departments, and the plan couldn't be successfully completed, so Daniela's side was basically peaceful and free.

If the concubine wasn't assassinated, Heart of Life might not be massacred again, and the revolution might not occur, so Obscuro might not have a chance to take advantage of it.

Daniela's history of collapse in three months, may have already changed before they knew it.

Chapter 486: Deal 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The radio was still broadcasting the news, this method was already slowly replacing newspapers.

‘From the Enderian side, the country’s Construction Department has announced that the world’s largest underground palace, has finally been completed. This construction process was a historical miracle, after ten years and six months, this huge underground palace will soon become the biggest architectural pride of Enderians in history."

"Eternal Night Palace?" Garen smiled coldly, the Enderian King was a madman who chased power, and the Eternal Night Palace was actually an incomprehensibly huge Totem Tactic formation, it was meant to merge his own body with Ender’s largest sleeping statue, in his pursuit for the unprecedented, strongest power.

He was just a madman who wanted to be god, it was just that he wasn’t showing it yet.

As he listened to the news, Garen cleaned up a bit, ate some fruits, and then put on his clothes and sat cross-legged on the bed, beginning his daily secret technique practice. His practice every day was part of the basic steps to merge the Nine-Headed Dragon.

In the next ten or more days, Garen didn’t waste his time wandering about, he just stayed in his room and told everyone else that he was absorbing the Seed of the Ancestral God, when in actuality he was waiting for the Cthulhu's Origin transaction time.

Obscuro was growing more and more low-key, after that battle against the Royal Star Court, it was as though the whole Obscuro Society vanished without a trace, it made no move at all, in the intercontinental news, international news, and even within the other countries’ domestic news, there wasn’t any news at all.

The yearly Seed of the Ancestral God activity had ended, and the many totem users from various different countries also began to leave.

The Ancestral God Grounds became quieter and quieter. This was originally Daniela’s holy ground anyway, Phiros was always standing guard over this place, he lived right on the largest Ancestral God Tree. Now that there weren’t any Ancestral God Seeds left here, the totem users from other countries have no reason to continue staying here either.

These past few days, the Star Court’s two Court Masters had also left in a hurry, but no one knew if it was because they were slightly injured in the battle against God Cloud or some other reason.

The three departments also never got along well with each other, by the time Garen found out that they had left, they had already gone two days ago.

Daniela’s sixth royal daughter would occasionally visit Garen and co as well, she was evidently very interested in Garen.

Finally, when the people from the Cthulhuism Society were about to leave, Garen finally got the news he was waiting for.

Scylla sent someone to inform him that they were ready for the deal

The time was set at three in the morning, the location Ender’s ambassadorial hall.

*******************

Two in the morning, in the middle of the darkness, Garen abruptly opened his eyes, pulled off his covers and sat up in bed.

Looking at the small clock on the cupboard by his bed, the neon green needle was pointing at half past two.

It was all dark in the tree hole, and there was only a slight ray of green light coming in through the curtains on the circular window.

Garen got out of bed, and put on a black folded dress.

The structure of the dress was very simple, a circular hole was cut out of a piece of rectangular cloth, so a person’s head could go through. And then a silver belt was tied around the waist, two pieces of cloth in front and behind the person’s body. The waist was tied tightly, two hidden zips on either side pulled up, and a simple yet beautiful dress was done, suitable for both men and women.

The only flaw was that such a dress didn’t have sleeves.

Garen had actually only gotten these clothes after the last time he took a hit from the Cthulhu King, and his own clothes were destroyed, the servants here had offered these up for a change.

He took his waist pouch of ingredients with him, although Garen wasn’t strictly a totem user who relied on tactics to fight, the many ingredients and materials in his waist pouch could be indispensable at times too. In order to deal with many different surroundings and situations. Inside, there were healing potions, recovery potions, anti-poisons and other similar things, but of course the most important was still the Glittering Water he was planning to trade off.

Putting another wide black hood over his folded dress, Garen began trying to utterly conceal his own aura and Totem Light. When even he couldn’t feel any energy from his own body, he finally opened the door and walked out of the tree hole.

Outside the tree hole, the two sleeping maids moved slightly, as though about to wake.

Garen took some powder from his waist pouch, and scattered it.

Their heads tilted, and they were once more asleep, leaning against the door.

This was Traceless Sleeping Powder, in small doses it was a sleep medicine, in large doses it was an instant tranquilizer, it acted really quickly too, and was hard to detect. It was part of the preparation Scylla had sent over.

Garen glanced up at Wukang’ tree hole, he could hear the even breathing of four people from inside, it went without saying that the guy went and hooked up a few more Daniela girls again last night.

Garen stayed quiet, pulled his hood close, and took a black mask out of his pocket, stuffing all his golden hair into the hood, and not leaving a single trace. Only then did he follow the tree hole both of them stayed in, walking out.

There were more than ten tree holes in a row, all squeezed close to each other, but there wasn’t the sound of breathing coming from the other holes, they were evidently not in use.

Garen exited the tree hole area easily, and reached the vine road.

There were three people in black hoods standing at the flight area as well. One of them wore black gloves with golden dots and patterns, this was the sign Scylla had told him about in advance. Seeing Garen come out, Scylla took one step forward to greet him.

"You’re the last one." His voice was deep and hoarse, completely different from usual, he had evidently used some methods to change it.

"And here I thought I was considered early." Garen took it one step further, and had directly changed his voice to a slightly hoarse woman’s voice. He was an expert in secret techniques and the structure of the human body, after all he had messed around with the King of Nightmares for some time, so a slight change of his voice like this was nothing to him.

Scylla and the others were slightly dazed as well, as though they hadn’t thought he would be so adept at changing his voice.

If it wasn’t that the black hood he was wearing was the same design as the one Scylla had given Garen, Scylla would have suspected if he was the same person at all.

"Since we’re all here, let’s go." He quickly recovered, and looked at the black-hooded person on his right.

That person nodded, took out a round black ball, and tossed it into the air.

Noiselessly, a huge black bubble formed in mid-air, it was a full six meters in diameter.

The black bubble floated down slowly, and landed in front of the four of them.

Scylla was the first to step inside, followed by Garen, and then the other two.

The black bubble instantly took flight, floating slowly towards the black night sky. Its surface reflected bits of the starlight, as though it had vaguely merged together with the starry sky, and the two were inseparable.

The bubble left the Ancestral God Tree, and slowly flew towards the direction of the Ancestral God Grounds. After about more than ten minutes, soon enough, they could see several figures also dressed in black hoods among the trees below.

The black bubble landed solidly, on the right side of this group of people.

The bubble scattered, and Scylla’s group of four walked out.

"I thought you wouldn’t come this time?" Amidst these black figures, an old man’s voice came. He was facing Scylla, and evidently talking to him.

"How would that be possible, last time was just an experiment, this here is the real deal." Scylla shook his head, "I just got some stock, at first I wanted to collect more before I made the exchange, but there’s no time anymore."

"Me too." The black figure nodded, and said no more, evidently they were just like Syclla, one person leading a group, coming here together to exchange something with the Cthulhuism Society.

The two groups together made up to more than ten people, Garen took a look around, and not too far away from where they were, amidst the trees and foliage, there was a black wooden stake stuck into the ground, there seemed to be some tiny black tactic glyphs glittering on the stake.

Soon enough, two more black bubbles landed from the sky, and more than ten more people in black hoods walked out of the bubbles.

"We can begin now." Scylla said.

"Of course." A clear woman’s voice replied from one of the black hoods that had just arrived, and someone in a black hood stepped out, walking to the very front.

"According to our old rules, let us first complete the promise of exchange from last time." The woman’s voice said calmly. The black hood blocked away all recon methods, so that no one could tell if the person was a man or woman, or how strong they were.

As the person spoke, all of the black hoods glowed slightly, as though there was silver light flowing on the surface. Silver numbers rapidly appeared on the chests of the hoods.

From number 1, to number twenty-eight.

Garen looked at his own number, number eleven.

The black stakes surrounding them suddenly and abruptly fell silent, emitting a layer of grey powder mist, slowly enveloping this whole area, forming an upside-down hemisphere.

The sky also began to take on a layer of grey. It had evidently been completely blocked away by the black stakes.

"Let the deal now begin. I’ll start first." The woman’s voice came from the black hood again, her number was one. "This time it’s my turn to be number one, the item I have is one Blood Jade Pillar, about five hundred years old. I want to exchange it for a Spring of Attas, one or more units. The quality cannot be lower than White Light."

She flipped her right hand, and a small intricate red jade stick of wood appeared on her black-gloved palm, it looked just like a normal stick of jade, and was not extraordinary in the slightest.

"I brought the Spring of Attas, but if you want to get a unit of White Light quality or above, your Blood Jade Pillar is still rather lacking…" A person in the number sixteen black hood from the group on the left of Garen and company stepped forward and spoke directly.

Similarly, he held a transparent crystal cup in his hand, it was filled with a viscous white liquid that was emitting white steam.

"Then I’ll add on five Evolution Stones."

"Done."

One deal was quickly completed, and after both sides checked the items, they readily exchanged.

Garen watched them coldly from aside. This was evidently a small-scale transaction, they weren’t just exchanging the Cthulhu's Origins. The so-called Evolution Stone was just an Evolution Crystal, it was evidently a form of hard currency.

And then the second person stepped out, completing the promised transaction from last time.

There were mainly two ways for them to make the deal. One was this item-for-item exchange. Even if it was something they didn’t have right now, they could make a promise to meet again one year later here.

And the other, was to exchange a condition. Using a treasure, to exchange a favor of one fight from a strong fighter.

Just now there was one person who gave a strange dagger that could grow upon absorbing blood in exchange for a powerful fighter’s promise to fight for him once.

Because of this, Garen had also noticed that of everyone here, five of them had different robes from the rest.

Himself, Scylla, and two people from the group on the left, and then there was number one who had first stepped out from the group opposite.

Their five hoods were all slightly blacker than the others, the color purer.

This was evidently a sign of their power.

They stood out one by one, some exchanging treasures and supplies, some exchanging promises to fight. These exchanges were not very believable, after the person who promised to fight obtained their item, it depended on them whether they really were going to fight or not.

But most strong fighters wouldn’t break their promises in order to protect their long-term trustworthiness, otherwise next time nobody would seek them out for such transactions.

As for the side that provided the treasure, all they could do was pray that they were lucky. After all, to hire a fighter of that caliber, in the normal world, that was practically unimaginable.

At such a level, they were incomparable to any War Guild or Assassins’ Guild.

Soon enough, the deals reached the end, and from the group opposite them, the first person who had spoken, Number One, finally stepped out again.

"Alright, now it’s time for the main event. I’ve brought the Cthulhu's Origins that I promised last time. Anybody who needs to trade for them, you can step out now."

Chapter 487: Danger 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As soon as she spoke, the other four with dark black hoods, including Garen, all stepped out. Four others in regular black hoods, including the Willow Valley Master and company, also joined in. That made eight in total.

Number One nodded.

"Okay, the rest can leave now."

Quietly, the others all released their own black bubbles and flew away from this area, going past the dim grey bowl-shaped barrier, and quickly disappearing into the night sky.

After the others had left, Number One turned around and led the rest out of the grey barrier, walking towards the depths of the forest.

The nine of them walked through the forest for several minutes, soon enough, a small white mansion appeared ahead of them.

There were tall walls all around the mansion, a stone pillar next to the white metal gate, the words ‘Enderian Ambassadorial Hall’ carved onto it.

Number One led the group to the front door, and the door opened automatically with a creak, there wasn’t anybody at all inside. The whole estate seemed unnaturally quiet.

The group walked into the estate, and the door automatically closed behind them. Going to the second floor, in a wide room like a study, Number One finally came to a stop.

There was already a circle of chairs arranged in the room, more than ten of them, and everyone took their seats.

Scylla and Garen sat next to each other, and the others surrounded the other two strong fighters in dark black hoods, taking their seats next to them. Number One sat in the very center.

"Now can we start?" The old geezer leading the other group asked impatiently, he knew Scylla, and he was one of the five strongest people. He sat next to a normal black hooded person. The geezer’s number was seven.

"That’s right, we don’t have as much free time as you." The other warrior on his left nodded, he had number two.

Number One laughed lightly.

"We can start whenever.

He pointed at the ground with one hand.

The floor between the people whirred, and a translucent crystal pillar rose from the ground. The middle of the crystal pillar was completely transparent, it had a hollow in the center, and a wad of twitching yellow mud was floating inside.

The mud was only the size of a fist, yellow in color, and there was a pair of large black eyes on it, blinking occasionally.

"Earth God’s Origin, one standard unit, if you need it you can trade." Number One said calmly.

"I want it!" Number Two said immediately. He raised his hand, and a light blue bottle left his hand, and at the same time he grabbed at the air from the distance, and the Gaia’s Origin shot straight out of the crystal pillar, disappearing into his sleeve with a whoosh.

Number One didn’t seem offended either, nodding and catching the small clue bottle, after she opened the cap and looked inside, she kept it away quietly.

"The next one." After the crystal pillar sank down, it rose up again soon, and this time there was a cloud of faint black mist inside, forming a tiny whirlwind, the small black tornado whirring away, until the faint sound of wind howling could be heard through the whole room.

"Wind God’s Origin." Number One said mildly.

"This was the one I booked last time." Scylla said. He also threw out a small black bottle with one hand, and walked up himself, carefully transferring the small tornado into a black hourglass item. No one knew how it was done, but he just had to touch the crystal pillar lightly and everything was done in an instant.

After Scylla kept the item away, he sat down once more, looking rather satisfied.

"I don’t need the others, it’s up to you guys now." He said softly to Garen and the others.

Garen nodded, while the other two just smiled.

After that there were still some more lower quality and lower level Cthulhu's Origins, they were all taken away by the four normal black hooded people, the Willow Valley Master and the other three were slightly weaker, so after they got their items, they immediately bid farewell and left without hesitation.

Soon enough, there were only the five strongest people left in the room.

Garen watched them all coldly, the Glittering Water he had was not enough to exchange for middle- or upper-level Cthulhu's Origins, but he could still get lower-level ones. One lower-level Origin required ten units of Glittering Water, he had thirty units of Glittering Water on him now, in other words, he could exchange them for three lower-level Origins.

As for which three, he would need to consider them carefully, because they needed to match his attributes.

The Origins were taken out one by one, evidently there was one split out from each Cthulhu, the nineteen Cthulhus, including the Cthulhu King, there was one for each, but of course nobody could exchange for any of the middle-level ones, because how long had it been since the Glittering Pond appeared? Nobody at all could have collected fifty units of Glittering Water.

"There are still a few left, they are all lower-level Origins, it depends on you all whether you need them or not." Number One said mildly.

"The price for your middle-level Origins is so high, I bet you don’t really plan on trading them off to outsiders, do you?" Number Two said coldly.

"How could that be, if we didn’t want to trade, why would we need to bring them out?" Number One laughed and replied.

"Alright, tell me, what are the ones left. Hehe, if it weren’t for the fact that these things can only be split and taken by the Cthulhuism Society headquarters, I would have killed a few Cthulhus myself to get them. Why would I need to waste my time here!" Geezer Number Seven said impatiently.

Number One didn’t get angry, she just flicked her finger, and the crystal pillar in the ground rose again, this time it was filled with several differently colored Cthulhu's Origins.

Red, white, black, purple, the four different Origins formed a small square in the hollow, dominating one corner each. Red flames, white ice, black blood, and purple sand. The four types of Origins each presented a different magical sight.

"These are the Fire God’s, Frost God’s, War God’s, and Time God’s Origins, of these the War God’s and Time God’s Origins are lower-level, the other two are lower quality, why don’t you see which ones you need." Number One said calmly.

"Cronus?" Garen was slightly surprised, he didn’t think that there was someone among the Cthulhus who dared to use such a powerful title, after all an attribute such as time was not something totem power could interfere with.

"It’s just a Cthulhu who can turn back time a little, the title sounds very strong, but in truth they’re not much." Scylla’s voice came from above, "I met him before, he’s ranked number three among the lower-level Cthulhus, he passes but barely, that crafty guy."

The only high-level one was the Cthulhu King himself, the middle-level ones were the Water God, Light God and Thunder God. The lower-level ones included the Wind God, War God, Time God and the like, as for the last ten Cthulhus, they were considered lower quality.

"I want the Fire God’s.""I want the War God’s."

The voices spoke again.

"I want the War God’s and the Time God’s." Garen’s voice seemed to have clashed with another. He paused slightly, and glanced towards the direction of the voice, the one fighting for it with him was Number Two.

Number Two hesitated, and looked over as well.

"If you want it, sir, then I’ll let go." He actually gave up straight. "I already got two Origins just now, this time I’ll leave it to Number Eleven."

Garen was ready to fight for it, but he didn’t expect the other person to just give up, so he nodded at him as an expression of gratitude.

Both were lower-level Origins, that made twenty units of Glittering Water in total, Garen wrapped the bottles of Glittering Water together, and then threw the package at Number One. At the same time he went up to keep the two Origins into the crystal ball container he had prepared beforehand one by one.

He had only meant to use these two Origins for research purposes. Before he found out how to use them, he definitely wouldn’t absorb them carelessly. And the healing effects of the Glittering Water were very formidable as well, he also needed to keep a portion of that, and couldn’t just exchange it all.

The two Origins he kept into the crystal ball were black and purple respectively, forming two differently-sized areas of light inside the ball, the two powers seemed to be resisting against each other, with the black one being stronger as it took up most of the space.

Keeping the Origins’ crystal ball away carefully, Garen returned to his seat.

He waited until all the others also completed their transactions, and agreed on which Origins they needed for the next time, before the deal was finally over.

Together with Scylla, Garen used a special item to release the black bubble, sitting inside as they immediately went on a ride through the trees, finally arriving back at the Ancestral God Tree departure point Garen had been at.

The night was slowly becoming brighter.

The black bubble slowly landed on the departure point, and Scylla took a black ring out of his pocket.

"This is a simple gadget we can use to communicate from now on, it’s the basic version, so it can only contact up to ten people, if there’s anything good from now on you can also contact us. Of course, if we get any good info, and couldn’t monopolize it alone, we’ll ask you for help as well, we could all use the benefits to improve together."

"Improve together." Garen smiled too, accepting the ring and putting it on immediately. Even if he still needed to go back and check it out, naturally he couldn’t do something so inconsiderate right in front of the other party’s face.

Another source, be it in information or fighting power, could be of great use in a pinch.

The other party was evidently also favoring the Black Swamp Palace and the Snowy Mountain powers behind him. Scylla also obviously represented Ender’s power. Naturally, that would involve more than just him alone.

"The others who own this sort of ring are Ender’s two Form Fives…" Scylla reminded softly, and it instantly allowed Garen to understand, so the importance of this ring in his heart increased another level. At the same time Scylla had pointed out that the Red Leaf Tower Master and the Willow Valley Master who had been with them probably didn’t have the right to get this ring.

"Much thanks."

The two of them separated at the departure point, after watching the black bubble rise into the night air and until it totally vanished, Garen finally walked towards his own tree hole.

It was all quiet inside the tree hole, Garen patted the little green fruit next to the door.

With a smack, the whole ceiling of the tree hole lit up with a layer of dim green light, as though a lamp was illuminating the entire tree hole.

Garen looked around for a while and didn’t discover anything out of the ordinary, so only then did he take off his black hood and reveal the clothes inside.

He walked to the exact center of the tree hole room, raised his left hand, and pressed lightly in the air.

Whoosh!

A cloud of black poisonous mist spread out in all directions with him in the center, and rapidly reached every corner of the room.

The poisonous mist scattered for a few minutes, until the few insects in the corners of the tree hole utterly melted into pools of pus, and then it retreated back into Garen’s body.

He looked around the room, satisfied, and the blood-red secret technique aura flowed out from beneath his feet again. Soon it had completely covered the whole tree hole room. After ensuring that the aura had completely covered the room, Garen picked up the radio on the table, turned it on lightly, and began to tune it to the channel frequencies according to the numbers in his memory.

Chapter 488: Danger 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This radio was actually the same gift he had gotten from those little guys in Kovitan, he had always been using it until now.

In no time, the radio was tuned to the channel that the former Thunder God, Hannet, had mentioned.

It was all empty inside, with only the crackling of signal interference.

"Hannet? You there?" he said at the radio.

There was no reply at all.

The time ticked past, and just as Garen thought he had input the wrong code, or that Hannet had lied to him, finally a tiny voice came through the crackling of the radio.

"Is it… Big Brother's friend?" A timid girl's voice came from the radio.

"I guess so, are you his little sister?" Garen asked.

"Yeah… Big Brother went out… He told me, if someone comes looking for him, then tell them, it might be a while before you can meet him…" The girl spoke hesitatingly.

Garen frowned, he had no idea when Black Sky and Obscuro would surface, time was now his biggest problem.

"Then can you tell me, where did your brother go?" He tried his best to make his voice sound friendly and easygoing.

"I don't know either." The little girl replied in a small voice. "Recently there have been more and more people from the Cthulhuism Society, that Aud hurt Brother and Uncle last time, and now he's back."

Garen thought about it, but he had never heard of a Cthulhu named Aud in the Cthulhuism Society.

"Is Aud very powerful?" He asked quietly.

"Mn, very powerful, Uncle nearly died thanks to him last time." The girl's voice was slightly worried as she replied.

"Who's Uncle?" Garen had no idea there were two such unknown people next to Hannet.

The little girl seemed to drop her defenses around his status as her brother's friend, so under Garen's prodding, she soon spilled the beans about the whole situation.

Compared to his glory before the reincarnation, Hannet had now almost hit rock-bottom.

That so-called Aud was the hunting dog that the Cthulhuism Society had sent to hunt down the three of them, he was the Thunder God's number one general. His power was at the Spiritualized level, and every time he would force the three of them to a dead-end, or the edge of despair.

Thanks to the pressure by the Cthulhuism Society, the three of them had seen their family killed and destroyed, the Hannet of this life had no choice but to take his only blood-related younger sister and their family's uncle on the run for their lives. And they kept getting hurt along the way.

If this was a martial arts hero story, perhaps these challenges were so many training sessions for him, and his mind might grow stronger and fuller from it, geniuses with astounding talent could train for future battles by battling now, growing stronger and stronger, finally creating some sort of base for them to work on.

Unfortunately, this was the world of totem users.

Totems required vast amounts of supplies for maintenance preservation, and that was not including the commodities needed for evolution. Every totem user was an expert in spending. Even back then, Goth could only start his road to evolution because the Blackfield Bird was practically useless, and so consumed very little, plus he had his father's help and his mother's planning.

With the way he was using it, Hannet was already considered very lucky that his core totem hadn't degraded, as for evolving it, without the materials and supplies, he probably wouldn't be able to evolve it for the rest of his life.

After chatting with the little girl for a while, finding out about Hannet's current location and situation, Garen could hear that the girl was slightly tired and out of breath, so he took the initiative to stop the conversation.

Turning off the radio, he temporarily lost his motive to find Hannet and ask him for help in filtering, instead he took out the crystal ball again.

Filled with the Cthulhus' Origins, the crystal ball looked extraordinarily beautiful, the black blood and purple sand floating and moving slowly, if he looked closely at the black blood, he could see hints of dark red blood threads. And there were some golden grains of sand vaguely hidden among the purple sand.

"Guess I'll still study it for a bit first." Garen decided, twisting open the cover on the crystal ball, slightly less than half of the crystal ball was revealed, showing the Cthulhus' Origins flowing inside.

First, he chose the slightly stronger War God's Origins. After raising his awareness of the surrounding auras, to stand guard for possible threats, he carefully channeled the Black Water True Technique, and let it run at the highest state of activity.

Only then did he lightly reach out his pointer finger, lightly touching the mound of black blood with his finger. The tip of his finger was instantly covered with a tiny bit of black blood.

Closing back the cover, Garen looked at the bit of black blood on his finger carefully, one of the red blood lines on it kept swimming like a leech, as though it was alive. He couldn't feel any movement of Totem Light on it, as though it was just a bit of normal blood.

Ah!!!

Suddenly, a piercing scream shot through Garen's brain.

The red blood thread darted out abruptly, like a piercing thorn, aiming straight for Garen's right eye.

The scream made him ever so slightly slow to react, it was just an instant, then Garen immediately flicked away the black blood, rapidly retreating backwards.

Boom!!!

His surroundings gave a huge jolt, and in the distant unknown darkness, a pair of black blood eyes opened slowly. Transcending an uncountable distance, just as the blood thread was about to pierce through Garen's eyeball, their gazes met,

"Black Water!!!" Garen roared, the Black Water True Technique throughout his entire body activating at once. His right hand became a bolt of black lightning, wrapped up in countless black water, and with a whoosh, almost as though it teleported, he pinched the blood thread precisely.

The tip of the blood thread collapsed and broke off, the thorn continuing to attack Garen's eye.

Clang!!

Garen flicked it with his fingernail, and at the same time he chased after it, utterly flicking away the broken tip.

Bam-bam-bam!!

Garen took a few continuous steps back, leaving deep and clear steps in the floorboards, until finally his legs were deeply sunk into the floor, and he finally stayed steady on the spot, unmoving.

He had the blood thread caught between his fingers, his chest rising and falling drastically, a tiny sweat already broken out on his forehead.

Just in that instance, before the Flash Screen even had time to activate, the moment that blood thread ambushed him, he had completely relied on his instincts to stop, if it weren't for the fact that the King of the Century level meant he had terrifyingly precise control of his body, his body probably wouldn't have been able to react at all.

Even if it were a Form Five fighter, they might not be able to react to such an attack.

"Those eyes… that aura… the Cthulhu King!" Garen's fingers gave a jolt, and the blood thread instant scattered into red dots of light, vanishing.

Other than that peak-level fighter, what other method could have gone around his Totem Light, and almost made him, Garen, unable to react. Just in that instance, Garen vaguely felt his heart grow unsteady, the changes in that moment were far too fast, and too terrifying.

The level of threat Garen felt from that blood thread was no lower than a direct frontal attack from the Cthulhu King.

Sitting down cross-legged, he quickly began adjusting his body's condition. But just then, the Nine-Headed Dragon that had already been fused took that opportunity to struggle.

Before they were completely fused, totems still had their instinctive need to struggle.

Pfft!!

Garen couldn't help but spray out a mouthful of blood. His complexion turned pale for a moment. Although he had long since prepared himself mentally, he had guessed that there would be something wrong with the Cthulhu's Origins. But he hadn't thought it would be this direct and explosively violent.

"That was close… To think that just a normal Cthulhu's Origins would also be hiding the Cthulhu King's tricks." His face was as pale as paper, most of his blood qi used to press down the restless dragon heads.

"Cthulhu King…" A flash of hatred shot past Garen's eyes.

Whoosh!!

Garen's figure disappeared in an instant, and the two clouds of Cthulhus' Origins vanished as well.

A huge hole had soundlessly opened up in the tree hole room's window. A black figure shot into the sky like a bat.

****************

Enderian Ambassadorial Hall

Garen's figure instantly appeared in front of the door.

Boom!!!

With one fist, the large door instantly fell apart, exploding inwards into countless shards of shrapnel.

"Who are you!!!" A few guards and a totem user on duty looked over nervously.

Garen strode forward, stepping indoors. Ignoring the commotion around him, he raised his head and looked at the second floor of the Ambassadorial Hall. By the window there, a young woman's surprised face was also looking down at him.

Garen spread open his arms, and copious black water vapors began to spray from his body. The countless black clouds formed several dragon necks, twining around Garen's right arm.

Brrr!!

The ground rang with a series of explosions, and Garen morphed into a bolt of black lightning, crashing his fist towards the direction of the woman on the second floor.

Roar…!!!

Countless roars from the Nine-Headed Dragon overlapped, they roared and howled at the same time, the five black dragons twisted around his arm like a black pillar of aura as it crashed towards the second floor of the whole Ambassadorial Hall.

In the night sky, among the black-green sea of trees, a black cloud exploded and began to spread.

Amidst the many black clouds, the five black dragons flew around in circles, destroying everything in sight. The deafening dragon roars kept reverberating in the air.

The Ambassadorial Hall was turning into countless shards of debris amidst the black clouds, and a pillar of blood light shot into the sky.

"Garen! You've gone mad!" The piercing woman's voice could be heard throughout half of the Ancestral God Grounds.

There was another huge dragon roar, and the five black dragons merged, forming the largest dragon mouth that gnashed at the air fiercely.

It had actually bit and swallowed up the red light.

"You nearly destroyed my roots! The Cthulhuism Society, you're dead!!" Garen's voice was mixed with the dragon roars, ringing out explosively.

From the very beginning, his intention behind obtaining the Cthulhu's Origins had already been clear to the Cthulhuism Society, and they had purposely tweaked the War God's Origins, or maybe even all the Origins. Since the Cthulhuism Society had forsaken even the last veil of concealment, and had openly declared war on him, he no longer had any reason to hold back.

If you want me to die, I'll kill you first!

The black clouds scattered, and Garen grabbed Number One's head with one hand, his fingers like dragon fangs as they pierced deep into Number One's skull, drawing five deep holes into her pretty face. The grey matter leaked out together with her blood.

If he hadn't been prepared beforehand, raising his awareness while checking the Origins, this ambush may have succeeded, and then it would be nearly impossible for him to enter the Form Five fusion phase.

He was this close to being forced out of his fusion phase, this close to wasting all his previous efforts. All of the fused dragon heads nearly broke free from his blood qi control. He never wanted to experience that sort of feeling ever again.

Beneath the Ancestral God Grounds, on the many Ancestral God Trees, the many tree holes began to light up, in no time at all, the green and yellow lights were all illuminated.

Soon enough, several powerful auras shot into the sky, Garen glanced at them coldly, picked up the body and rapidly disappeared into the night sky.

Chapter 489: Depart 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After forcefully breaking past the Ancestral God Tree’s no-flight power, Garen quickly searched the woman’s body, and found a Cthulhu’s Origin that hadn’t been exchanged, glancing at it he realized it was the Light God’s Origins that had been introduced before.

Keeping it into his waist-pouch, Garen’s face flashed with a red dragon shadow, and the body in his hands was instantly swallowed by the Nine-Headed Dragon, leaving not a trace behind.

His fury from being ambushed previously had also mostly drained.

He released a fierce breath, and his heart suddenly tightened, after being ambushed just now, his temper had exploded, and the wrath just overtook him. Under the influence of the Nine-Headed Dragon’s explosive killing intent and bloodlust, he had actually gone straight to the Cthulhuism Society and killed someone.

"Now that I’ve gotten the Cthulhu’s Origins, I can’t stay long!" Garen was just about to turn the communicative ring on his finger to contact Wukang, when suddenly a black cloud appeared in front of him, and he sensed a familiar Totem Light ahead of him.

"Wukang?"

"It’s me!" A man’s voice came from within the black clouds. "What happened?"

"I can’t explain now, let us leave here now, I killed someone from the Cthulhuism Society, and stole some things, so they surely won’t let it go." Garen said hurriedly, "We’ll just use radio transmission to inform His Majesty Phiros later, now we leave!"

Wukang didn’t waste time chatting either, the black clouds carrying the carriage they arrived on, and the female guard was already riding on it, the three of them didn’t say much, the black clouds cooperating with Garen’s Black Water True Technique, they rapidly flew towards the outskirts of the Ancestral God Grounds.

"Let’s split up, you go straight back at full speed, I’ll go settle some other things, I’ll be back in a jiffy." Garen told him quietly, he was floating in the middle of the black clouds, and there was nobody around him, but he knew that if he talked like this, Wukang would definitely be able to hear him.

"That’s good too, I’ll take the others back first, if you need me, you can contact me whenever using the communicative ring." Wukang knew as well that, faced with the high-level fighting power of the Cthulhuism Society, right now he would be no more than a burden.

******************

Three days later

Outside the Daniela Ancestral God Grounds, among several differently-sized villages.

In a newly-built small wooden house, the dim light came in through the window, the faint light of dawn dying a small part of the little house white-grey.

Cough cough cough…

Inside the little house, a short young man with white hair was coughing into his hand despite himself, his face pale.

"Are you okay?" A middle-aged man’s voice came from the bed in the little house.

"I’m fine. I won’t die." The young man put down his hand, and hit that little bit of blood in his palm behind him. "In the end Aud landed a fist on my back, so I was slightly hurt. It’s nothing serious."

"I’ve already given her the medicine that you found from inside. Her condition should be getting better now. Too bad we’re stuck here instead." The middle-aged man said helplessly.

"It’s okay, there will be a way." The white-haired man was Hannet, who had just left the Ancestral God Grounds. He had been chased down by the Cthulhuism Society the whole way, and nearly died a few times before he finally managed to hide into this village. For now, he had earned some breathing space.

"Stone and the others are coming soon, with their help, it will probably be a lot easier." The middle-aged man said softly, watching Hannet’s pale face, how could he not know Hannet’s current condition, Hannet was on his last legs, and had been pushed to the limit. After repeatedly getting hurt, all the materials and supplies he had at hand for totem maintenance had been completely used up, and compared to before, his power had once more fallen to the freezing point. He had only been at Form Two power before, but now he had fallen to Form One.

If it weren’t for the Winged God Arms’ support, Hannet would probably have fallen a long time ago to the Cthulhuism Society’s efforts.

Seeing Hannet’s eyes flash with a hint of hatred, perhaps the other thing supporting him was also his deep-set hatred towards the Cthulhuism Society.

His parents’ tragic deaths, his family members getting dismembered and eaten, the grudge between the Cthulhuism Society and Hannet was already at a point of no return.

"They are them, I am me." Hannet replied emotionlessly, "Don’t put your hopes in anyone else, that is a foolish way to think."

"But in any case Stone has reached Form Four too, so he’s far more powerful than we are. Isn’t that right?"

Hannet fell quiet, and said no more.

******************

Arooo~~~!!

A huge white wolf, more than ten feet tall, howled at the sky, spraying out many golden threads that spread apart, shooting in all directions like raindrops.

These golden threads were almost alive, rapidly darting through the luscious green forests, searching out any possible target.

Ding!!

There was a crisp sound, and several silk threads were cut apart.

A flash of gold darted past in mid-air, running away from the white wolf at high speeds.

"Run!! Run run run!!" Beckstone looked like a mess, a hole torn through his robe at the butt, revealing his fair white buttocks, while his whole body was covered with sticky golden liquid, and even some of his exposed skin was covered with the pale gold liquid.

Underneath him was a huge golden flower, a large flower like a sunflower.

There were roots and dark green vines growing from underneath the flower, like so many tiny short legs, running so fast it nearly turned into a wheel.

The Eleventh Princess Tina was sitting on the huge flower, the little girl hugging Stone’s thigh tightly, the mucus and tears covering her face, without a trace of her elegance as a royal daughter, while her entire body kept floating from the extreme speed with which they were moving.

"This is the residual pressure left behind from the strongest totem three thousand years ago, the Heavenly Wolf King! That place just now had the strongest mark of residual power discovered in archaeological history, we should be fine as long as we get two thousand kilometers away!!" Tina roared loudly, not daring to wipe away her mucus, so she could only press her face hard against Stone’s robes. The two of them were an utter mess."

"A damned totem can still be so strong after three thousand years, are you f*cking kidding me!" At this point, even Beckstone couldn’t help but curse.

After all, after being chased for three days and nights, without even time for a toilet break, once it got to that, even a retard would probably be invoking some four-letter words.

"You’re saying that now! I told you that thing can’t be touched, but you just had to touch it! If it weren’t for you, we’d be at Daniela ages ago!" Tina started screaming.

Shh…

Some white water flew out from under Tina. It followed the wind and floated to the back.

The corner of Stone’s mouth twitched a few times. The two of them had been living like that for the past few days, having gotten used to wetting their pants or whatnot. As for their pants getting wet, they would dry in the wind soon anyway…

"I wanna die!!" Tina’s face was filled with shame and fury. Although it wasn’t her first time wetting herself, each time still made her unbearably embarrassed and angry.

"Just relax." Beckstone said woodenly.

Suddenly, a huge black shadow covered the tops of their heads.

"Dodge!""To the right!!"

The two of them screamed at the same time.

Barroom!!

There was an instant explosion like a high-powered bomb, and a large patch of trees were blown down, a deep black trench appearing in the ground.

The huge white wolf raised its right paw, golden threads pouring out non-stop from its mouth, these golden threads were like mist, spreading apart, locking down the areas the two of them could dodge into among the trees.

On the way here, at first they did not need to worry about their safety at all considering how strong Beckstone was, but he had assumed that safety was a non-issue, so his largest curiosity as a researcher was utterly activated by the strange and mysterious things he kept seeing on the road.

Relying on his Form Four power, he had started exploring everywhere, and at first Tina’s warnings still had some effect, but towards the end, it simply became that whatever she warned him against, he would go straight to touch it.

After he tried that a few times and nothing happened, he began to grow fearless. Until he messed with this extremely powerful white wolf.

This white wolf could instantly switch between dematerialization and materialization, and was extremely powerful, it could avoid any attack. Its speed was shocking, as was its destructive power. It chased the two of them non-stop for three days and three nights, extremely persistently.

Soon enough, they could vaguely see the sign marking Daniela’s country border.

The two of them slipped behind the boundary marker, and instantly a huge power rushed straight at them.

The huge white wolf behind them roared long and loud, unhappily, and finally retreated slowly.

Bam!

The two of them fell sitting to the ground, an utter mess, and lay on their backs, unwilling to move even half a finger. They just kept breathing the fresh air in large pants.

Beckstone’s hair had been blown into a broom by the air, standing high on end, while two dents had been blown into Tina’s checks, the two pieces of chubby flesh hanging slightly low by her chin, looking a bit like a pug and seeming like it might not return to the way it was.

"How blissful…" Tina moaned, "I just want to lie like this forever."

"Let’s find human civilization first. We’re finally at Daniela…" Beckstone stood with some difficulty, feeling how empty the seat of his pants was, there was a faint breeze blowing past his legs.

He looked around himself for a while, all of his luggage and belongings had been lost in the chase, even his waist pouch was gone, all he had left were the few rings on his fingers.

Heaving a heavy breath, he lifted Tina in one go. The golden flower was also panting out of exhaustion next to them, the golden sunflower-like flower head tilted to a side, its body rising and falling, as though it was panting heavily as well.

"You okay, Sunflower?" Stone patted Sunflower.

Sunflower nodded hurriedly, its many roots tapping the ground to indicate that it still had energy.

"Then we’re counting on you." Beckstone said helplessly. Pulling Tina back onto Sunflower, they hurried towards the direction of Daniela’s Ancestral God Grounds.

****************

Garen was sitting alone, cross-legged, in a forest, there seemed to be a faint black mist permeating through the air, and the trees and grass seemed to be wilting slightly.

The place he was meditating was already several tens of kilometers away from the Ancestral God Grounds.

This was an extremely isolated part of the forest, and he was mostly surrounded by bamboo.

Amidst this green sea of bamboo, there was a small round area of faintly black light, like a small spot of black ink of green cloth, unnaturally clear. That was where Garen was recovering.

It had been three days after he left the Ancestral God Grounds by himself, the fifth dragon head’s fusion was already successfully complete, with the help of the two Seeds of the Ancestral God, he had successfully completed the fusion, and at the same time he had begun fusing the sixth dragon head.

Leaving the Ancestral God Grounds was not a decision he had made simply. Although this way he would face the Cthulhuism Society’s hunting directly, he would also be able to hide his own tracks, going from out in the open into hiding. That way, should Black Sky’s Hellgate reemerge, and decide to make a move on the Ancestral God Grounds, it would not affect him for now. With a bigger and more definite target in the Cthulhuism Society and Daniela’s king, no matter what they would not go for an outsider power like him first.

Chapter 490: Depart 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He could clearly remember. The first place that Hellgate went after his awakening was the Ancestral God Grounds.

By obtaining Cthulhu’s Origin, he had already achieved his purpose; here was no point in remaining here. Next, he had to find the previous Thunder God, Hannet, to filter Cthulhu’s will. If not, he couldn’t use the Cthulhu’s Origin on hand.

Having the advantage as the King of the Century, once Garen entered fifth form, his battle ability would instantly hit its peak; on par with Phiroth and the Cthulhu King. He had already trained his martial arts to a complete level, totally different from the rest of the fifth forms who had to start their martial arts training from scratch. This was his advantage.

However, the key factor was the lack of potential of the Nine-Headed Hydra. By level, he could only achieve lower fifth form, which is the beginning of fifth form. It was impossible for him to continue progressing. Due to the limits of the Nine-Headed Hydra’s genes, nothing could be changed.

Even though his strong battling ability could imitate a peak fifth form, it was only due to his martial arts, which far exceeded others.

After Hellgate’s awakening, the president of the Elder Council, an experienced, peak fifth form also perished by his hand. Moreover, Hellgate achieved victory without suffering any injuries. According to the original history, no one could withstand the Obscuro’s progress, not until long after the big battle, when the The Great Heroes slowly rose up. Only after using the strength of an ancient tactic to gather everyone’s strength, they managed to severely injure Hellgate. Only with that in addition to Beckstone’s sneak attack did they then managed to defeat the strongest totem user in history. However, this battle caused huge losses to all the elite forces in the totem world. A great deal of heirlooms were lost, and the totem civilization dropped to its lowest point. Instead, it was the technological civilization. They gradually grew stronger through their confrontation with monsters.

"Whatever the case, let me enter fifth form first. Only then I would be qualified to have a space in the East Continent’s chessboard. If not, once Hellgate awakens…" Garen was clear.

Bang!!

Suddenly, the sound of an explosion came from a distance.

Currently, the population in the East Continent had been vastly reduced. Monsters had also slowly gathered together after being recruited and controlled by the Nest Kings. As a result, the situation was much more peaceful than before. Still, only strong totem users dared to walk around in the wild.The outliers were the chaotic beasts that do not follow orders.

Garen slowly retrieved his protective poisonous fog, and started to change position again.

Very quickly, he found another drain. He sat tightly on the mountain walls and started to operate the Black Water True Technique.

Out of his expectations, another sound came from the distance. Messy footsteps could be heard. It was obvious someone was quickly approaching him.

Garen furrowed his brows. Once could be a coincidence, but not twice. The other party seemed to be headed straight for him.

Even if he used the Black Water True Technique with all his might in addition to the Troll Grip and his various battle technique, he could barely be on par with a medium-level fifth form. If he met a true medium-level fifth form, he definitely had to flee. In his two indirect fights with the Cthulhu King, he clearly understood that although he would be on par with a medium-level fifth form if he fought with all his might, this was a key period to fuse with the dragon heads. He could not be emotionally or physically affected.

The last time he was almost hit by the Cthulhu King from a distance, it wasted all his previous efforts. Hence, in actual fact, he was weaker than a medium-level fifth form.

"I’ve already given the secrets of Cthulhu’s Origin to Phiroth, Scylla and the rest. They should be currently busy giving the Cthulhuism Society trouble. How would they have remaining strength to pursue me?" Garen was curious.

Without further hesitation, he changed his location again.

This time he went slightly further.

Very quickly, not more than ten minutes, the sound came closer again. This time, Garen was sure that the other party had a way to track himself. He stayed still on the ground, waiting for the other party to approach. He wanted to investigate who was the person.

The dense steps quickly approached.

In the sea of bamboo in the distance, more than ten masked men and women in tight red clothing were carrying a beautifully decorated seat.

On the red seat was a black-haired man in a red dress.

Garen was mildly surprised. After another careful look, it was indeed a man in a red dress.

His mouth was covered in pink lipstick and his eyes were drawn with eye shadow while holding a white feather fan in his hand. From time to time, his eyes would flicker.

It would be better if this person was a metrosexual beauty, but based on the light beard marks on his chin and the squarish shape of his face, he was clearly a majestic man. He had a strong body yet still let out a charming winking gesture.

Garen felt sick in his stomach. Suddenly, he thought of one of the eighteen Cthulhus of the Cthulhuism Society. His description exactly matched the appearance of this person.

"Flower God… It should be him." Garen looked from afar. The other party seemed to notice him. He flapped his fan and winked at him.

Garen’s expression did not change. He suppressed his discomfort and quietly waited for the arrival of the other party.

Other than this group, there were no other elites worthy of attention, except the Flower God. Even the Flower God was one of the tail-ranked Cthulhus. He was only a fourth form. For him to come here alone, there must be a reason.

After a while, Flower God’s party quickly arrived before the crossed legged Garen.

As they slowly put down the seat, the Flower God twisted his thick waist, got up from his seat and stood on the green grassy plains. He looked interestingly at Garen, who didn’t bother about him at all.

"People always speak about the brutal ferocity of Nine-Headed Hydra Garen. As long as it was an enemy, he wouldn’t spare their lives. Not even beauties of the land would be spared. Now, it just seems like they do not know how to appreciate him."

Garen’s eye twitched. His intuition told him that if he allowed this person to continue, the situation would be heading in a weird direction.

"The Flower God comes here to look for me. What’s the matter?" He directly asked.

"What’s the matter?" The Flower God covered his mouth with his white fan and laughed ‘adorably’. "As one of the Chulhus, spending so much time to look for you, what do you think is the matter?"

"Do you think you have the ability to defeat me?" Garen let out a disdained smile.

"You did not attack me at once. Are you mesmerized by my beauty?" Flower God vainly took out a small mirror and looked at his appearance.

"Even with my handsome looks, I wouldn’t dare to speak like that!" Garen couldn’t hold himself in any longer. As he uttered those words, he felt something was wrong.

Under normal circumstances, he would never speak this way.

After making the connection to the previous incident with his previous murderous intent, Garen could roughly guess why.

The Nine-Headed Hydra’s nature was finally starting to affect his subconscious. He hadn’t forgotten that a Lord-level living being would naturally be as vain as one. All this while, since these effects were not obvious, he hadn’t taken it to heart. He never thought that the effects would be so subtle.

As he said those words, Garen knew something was wrong. His eyes widened.

Sure enough, the Flower God opened his ‘small mouth’, and looked at Garen in shock. It was as if he had found a true friend.

"I thought that other than I, nobody in the world could reach such a level of admiration and infatuation towards himself. I never thought that I would meet someone like you!" He seemed a little excited. His cheeks were flushed as he looked at Garen with affection.

"No wonder why you were so familiar. Looking at it now, only beautiful people like us are the perfect couple!"

The pores all over Garen’s body stood up. He tried his best to suppress the disgust in him.

"I don’t think we are a good match. If you don’t leave now, don't blame me if things get ugly." For an opponent like this, he had no interest to take action. He felt disgusted to even go any closer to him.

As he finished speaking, he kicked with his legs and his whole body floated backwards. He was surrounded by the corrosive poisonous fog as he flew away.

Garen stood still on the ground with an excited look.

"You cannot run. There is no one in this world for me but you…."

Before he finished speaking and his words were still echoing in the woods, the dress on Flower God’s body flew up and became a red rotating cloud.

Sheeeshhh!!

The red cloud descended and instantly appeared before Garen, becoming a red umbrella.

As the red umbrella rotated, a rain of white flower petals fell from the sky.

The umbrella exposed a charming, enchanting fair face. It was actually an indescribably perfect girl’s face!!

The same red dress, same demeanor, same gaze and also the same totem light!!

Shockingly, it was the Flower God!

"God Flower, capture the king!!" As the Flower God pointed, her slender jade-white fingers headed towards Garen.

It was as if the surroundings were spinning. The bamboo forest gradually disappeared and became countless green light arcs. The surroundings became a blur and nothing could be seen clearly.

"Even a lowly fourth form dares to act!" Garen’s expression was cold. He single-handedly leapt forward to meet Flower God head on.

Dang!!

Their fingers met and let out a metal clashing sound. Their totem light collided, splashing out large amounts of broken light dots. The red and black dots were like elvish rain, circulating around the two people. This forced all of the Flower God’s servants to retreat.

Garen lightly blocked his opponents sharp fingers. Then he reached down with his right hand, intending to tear the Flower God’s head apart.

Suddenly, he felt pity towards the Flower God’s perfect beauty. His heart involuntarily paused for a moment. A trace of pity an affection arose from his heart.

Due to this hesitation, Flower God took the opportunity to leap back. As the red umbrella swiveled, her graceful figure was portrayed and fragrance filled the surrounding air. Combined with the lively green bamboo forest around, it gave off an illusion of perfection.

"Sure enough. Lord Garen talks tough, but has a soft heart." Flower God let out an adorable laugh.

"You’re thinking too much!" Garen’s expression grew cold. He suppressed the strange feeling in his heart and raised his left palm. Countless black water vapor dots gathered in his palm, quickly forming a black water sphere.

As the water ball rotated in his palm, a moving black dragon shadow could faintly be seen within.

With a crash, the ball instantly split to form a water vapor whirlpool. Garen inserted his right hand into the whirlpool.

Sheeshhh!!

A black whirlpool appeared in the air behind Flower God. A white large hand came out from the middle. Its fingers as sharp as knives and its fingernails were as red as a dragon head. It fiercely bit at the back of Flower God’s head.

Ahhh!!

Flower God let out a cry and fell to the ground. Coincidentally, the shoulder region of her red dress was torn open, revealing a jade-like shoulder.

Garen’s heart skipped a beat. He instantly felt dry in his heart. Even closing his eyes had no effect.

Chapter 491: Communication 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What kind of ability is this?" Garen retreated more than ten steps. After he could finally stand still, his forehead was covered with a layer of sweat.

He could feel like there was a small hand disturbing his abnormally stable state of mind.

"Take a guess?" Flower God laughed adorably as she saw Garen tremor.

"Good good good! Good plan from the Cthulhu King!" Garen instantly turned. With a few somersaults, he quickly disappeared into the forest underneath the protection of the black poisonous gas.

Flower God stood still on the ground. Her eyes were wandering as if she were reminiscing something.

Swoosh!!

A black blur instantly soared pass the sky above the bamboo forest. As the black wind blew by, large amounts of bamboo leaves fell to the ground. Even the bamboo poles were shaken.

As the black wind landed on the ground, a human figure instantly appeared.

Garen’s expression remained still but there was a flash of hatred in his eyes.

"No wonder Flower God dared to track me alone. The feeling just now was a mental ability!"

He carefully thought for a moment. It was indeed a mental ability.

Normally, this ability wouldn't have much effect, but it was a special period now. His state of mind cannot be shaken. Once it was shaken by the ability, it wouldn't mean much to a normal person, but all his efforts for the fusion would be wasted.

The Cthulhu King must have seen this. Hence, he sent Flower God to pursue him alone. The other Cthulhus must also have been caught up with other matters. If not, it wouldn't be just one Cthulhu in pursuit of him.

After Garen realized this, he instantly fled. Although the Flower God’s mental ability wasn’t destructive, now was a period where it could be lethal. Furthermore, the Cthulhu King had given him some unknown secret tricks. In this situation, it was foolish to be aggressive.

As for his reputation, Garen naturally will not be affected by all these. His actions only needed to be tactically sound.

He took out a water bottle from his pouch bag and drank from it.

"If it were me before my death in the previous world, maybe I would battle him head on to protect my pride. But now…." Garen felt nostalgic. As he thought of the previous world, he remembered his sister Ying Er, Andrela, King of Nightmares and his old friends. He also remembered Sylphalan, who eventually fell into lava.

"Lord Garen…." A charming girl’s moan came from afar. She was complaining, as if a beauty was asking her lover to change his heart.

"Lord….Do not run away from Little Flower alright?"

Pu!

Clear water almost blurted out from his mouth.

Garen was already affected by the mental ability. His reflexes were already slightly slower. But the final two words, Little Flower, left him completely speechless. His whole body trembled.

Maybe the people of this world did not relate it to something bad, but he who came from earth had deep negative impression towards the name "Little Flower".

In that instant, the effect of the mental ability greatly reduced.

Garen’s eyes became clear and turned back to look at the bamboo forest. He saw Flower God heading over here through the bamboo forest.

Without hesitation, he activated the black cloud and fled into the distance.

As the two of them were running around, Garen seemed to be secretly bringing the Flower God in a loop.

He had subtly realized that his state of fusion was stabilizing under the Flower God’s abilities. It seemed harder and harder to be shaken.

Realizing the benefits, he would rather bring Flower God on a wild goose chase in the bamboo forest. At times, Garen even had to slow down to wait for him.

Flower God seemed to sense that his ability wasn't working well. He kept quiet and chased Garen with all his might. However, once Garen stopped, he wouldn't voluntarily go closer as well, but merely tailed him from afar. From time to time, Garen could see his sad eyes through the gaps of the bamboo forest.

It took a full, five days.

On the sixth day, Garen was still bringing Flower God in circles.

Suddenly, a red string shot out from the back of the bamboo forest.

As the sharp red string flew towards Garen, it abruptly slowed down, becoming a thin line. It lightly surrounded Garen and landed on the ground before him.

Garen didn't know where it came from. Flower God’s aura was still two kilometers away.

He frowned as he picked it up. The red string was a little thick. Surprisingly, there was a white piece of paper within.

He tore open the string to retrieve the paper. On the water was a clear line of words.’

"Angokhan Village, Twelfth wooden hut - Hannet."

Garen surveyed the surroundings. There wasn’t even a shadow, nor was there a sign of any totem.

"He is indeed the last Thunder God, God of Taboos. Even this stealth technique is already extraordinary." He knew that the messenger was either Hannet himself or his kin.

With such a stealth technique, no wonder the Cthulhu King could not capture him after such a long period of time.

"Lord Garen." Flower God’s girly voice came from behind again.

This time, Garen set crossed-legged on the ground and waited quietly for the other party to arrive.

Very quickly with a red flash, Flower God gently dropped from the sky. He still held the red umbrella in his hand. The tight red dress clearly revealed her sexy figure. His skin was white as snow, while he was as pretty as a flower.

If Garen’s didn’t have a deep first impression of that squared-face, burly man, most likely he would have thought that the other party was a true beauty. 　　

Unfortunately, after these few days, he already figured out the background of Flower God.

This guy’s true self was that burly man in women’s clothes. However, the beautiful girl was his totem. He relied on his strange talent to combine himself and the totem into one.

Complete fusion before reaching fifth form did give him strong power, but also his strange state. Normally, he would look like the burly man. Once he used his totem’s ability, he would transform into the beauty.

Flower God constantly changed between two extremes, extreme inferiority and extreme narcissism. Finally, he had come to this strange, this crazy persona.

"You've finally stopped running?" Flower God looked grim with resentment. "My company for so many days couldn’t cheer you up?"

Garen twitched his lips. Flower God really liked to create a flirty environment. Unfortunately, once he thought of the squared-face guy in female dressing, his mood would instantly turn sour. This became his biggest counter towards the mental ability.

"What did the Cthulhu King want you to say to me?" Garen steadied his emotions and slowly opened his mouth.

Flower God was surprised, as if he did not expect Garen’s movement.

"Well, nothing, actually. So you can die now."

Before his words could finish, Bang!! A fair-skinned palm appeared before Flower God.

The palm’s five blood-red fingers formed a claw, like a dragon opening its mouth.

Roar!

Dragon roars loomed. With this, Garen activated the Black Water True Technique with all his might, using the full power of the five fused dragon heads. He aimed his full power at the Flower God’s eyes.

Not even a normal fifth form would dare take him head on, what more a peak fourth form.

For the past few days, Garen relied on Flower God’s ability to reduce his chances of being affected during the fusion period. Now, he could finally use his full-strength.

The Flower God let out a cry. With a bang, he disintegrated into countless flower metals, trying to escape from the claw.

The flower petals quickly regathered in the bamboo forest in the distance. As they were about to form a human, a black light flashed by.

Garen’s figure stood beside the flower petals with a calm gaze. He slowly retrieved his hand.

He thrusted his right arm into the middle of the flower petals. The Black Water True Technique was as fierce as the sea. With the new power from the fusion, he used a tremor-style technique. Within a split second, large amounts of flower petals were separated.

The large amounts of flower petals again flew to another spot, trying to form a human figure. With a flash of black light, the petals who had just gathered were separated by Garen again.

Being in an elemental state without being able to regain his physical form, Flower God started to panic. His strange ability allowed him teleport to any place with flower petals. However, forming a human figure needed time. In his elemental state, he couldn’t teleport far away, but only within a small radius. Regretfully, Garen’s speed in a small radius was equal to teleportation.

Everytime Flower God tried to form a human figure, the petals would be separated by Garen. After each separation, the gathering power would weaken a little. In his elemental state, every second required large amounts of totem light. Flower God got more and more anxious.

Bang!

With a punch, Garen separated a bunch of pink flower petals. The broken flower petals flew everywhere. This time, different from the ten previous times, Flower God did not stand up.

He completely became flower petals and slowly disappeared on the spot.

"Unfortunately Cthulhus are immortal. If the origins remain intact, there is no way to completely destroy the opponent." Garen shook his head in pity.

By using the Flower God’s mental ability to train himself, he had wasted quite a lot of time. As his body stabilized, the fusion with the dragon heads also became faster than previously expected. The training obviously had a stimulating effect on the fusion process.

After the five heads, most of Garen’s power had already moved to the Black Water True Technique. His body gradually developed an integration between totem light and blood flow. Together with Flash Screen supporting it fully, a normal fifth form totally had no chance to pierce his defense and injure him. However, Flower God’s mental ability went around this and directly affected his mind. This caused Garen initiate his retreat.

"Lord Garen is so charming even when killing someone…Truly, you're the man that caught my eye." Flower God’s soft voice came from the air. "I’ll come look for you again."

Garen had goosebumps. He headed for the village he remembered in his memory.

Before he came to Daniela, he memorized the map around the Ancestral God Grounds. He wasted practically no effort finding this village.

　　****************

Angokhan Village

A small village on the outer borders of the Ancestral God Grounds

There weren’t many villagers in the village. The chief was a Cthulhuism Society caretaker who, every Sunday, would have people to teach the kids. While Hannet’s cover was the combat instructor to these kids.

He was a retired Daniela soldier who knew a few decent combat techniques.

The whole village was a simple village built with white wood. There was a sharp fence surrounding it. On the outer regions, there were some villagers who reared cows and goats. These mutated goats had fat bodies, and from time to time they would bow their heads to eat the mutated grass.

"Net, going to teach the kids again?"

"Net, you don’t look good recently. Do you want to go to Linla’s to have it checked?"

"Uncle Net. Do you still have more of these handmade sacks?"

As Hannet came back from the temple, the villagers around greeted him warmly.

He was dressed in a brown, sackcloth shirt. On his face was a warm smile. He wore a black leather hat on his head, completely covering his hair.

He returned to his small hut.

In the hut, the middle-aged man was squatting in front of a wooden basin, using a knife to cut some wood. As he heard him entering, the middle-aged man turned back to look at him.

"Beckstone and the rest have found Elin. They are rushing her over here. Since they look raw, they should be able to find an opportunity to go near the Ancestral God Pillar."

"It is not so simplistic." Hannet sat on the ground opposite the man. "Both the King of Daniela and the Cthulhuism Society will not allow me to absorb the power of the Ancestral God Pillar. If it wasn’t for the accident last time, I don’t think I could have successfully left the Ancestral God Grounds."

"To handle Thunder God and the Cthulhuism Society, maybe we can ask for outside help." There was a flash in the middle-aged man’s eyes. "I just went to look for that elite from Kovitan."

Hannets pupils shrunk.

"You’re crazy! That guy is a murderer, fierce and cruel. What if he turns his back on us…."

"To take on the Cthulhuism Society and get back the power that Havana stole, we can’t do it on our own." The middle-aged man calmly whispered. "At the Ancestral God Grounds, he helped you once. He must have had certain intentions."

Chapter 492: Communication 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Another one who seeks the Winged God’s Arm?" There was a flash of sorrow in Hannet’s face. He involuntarily clenched his fist.

"Nine-Headed Hydra Garen, Lord of Black Swamp Palace, One of Kovitan’s Four Gargantuans. He is incredibly ferocious. To seek power, his family used humans as living experiments. Everyone in Kovitan knows of this matter. To solidify his position of power, Garen once killed thousands of people in one day. Blood flowed like a river and no one in the kingdom wanted to mess with that lunatic." The middle-aged man explained. "Messing with a fierce man like that would create headaches for the Cthulhuism Society. This will immensely relieve the pressure on us."　

"This Garen is a dangerous man. With his strength, it will put us in danger as well by cooperating with him." Hannet thought of the incident on the Ancestral God Grounds. In his mind, he instantly placed Garen on a level of extreme danger.

"Nevermind. Nine-Headed Hydra is just a peak fourth form. Once Beckstone and the rest arrive, we will also have a fourth form elite to completely control Garen. By cooperating with each other, both sides can obtain what they want." The middle-aged man seemed to have arranged everything. "This time, I discovered a big secret of the Cthulhu Society."

"Oh?"

"Recently most of their elites have gathered over. On the surface, it looks like a standstill with the royal family of Daniela. In actual fact, they have discovered a new set of ancient ruins. The ancient ruins here have a certain relation to Cthulhu’s Origin.

Seeing Hannet closing his eyes, the middle-aged man said, "What I meant was, since the Cthulhuism Society is focusing on the ruins, we can tell this piece of news to the royal alliance. Once both sides are engaged in battle, we can take the opportunity to sneak into the Ancestral God Grounds to inherit the power of the Ancestral God."

"Phiroth is always on guard beside the Ancestral God Pillar. The success rate of this plan isn’t high, is it?"

"Naturally...Who’s there!!" The middle-aged man suddenly realized something off. Both of them leapt to their feet. One of them was glowing in blue lightning arcs while the other one’s body was full of red tactic symbols, as if he had a full body of rashes.

Both of them suddenly realized that in the closed hut, there was suddenly another human figure.

This person was sitting crossed-legged beside the two men, carefully listening to their conversation.

Hannet’s hairs all over his body stood up. The person before him was incredibly dangerous. Even more than the current Thunder God, Havana who robbed his power. He had never experienced such fear, not even in the Ancestral God Grounds.

Both of them were most proud of their stealth techniques. They never thought there would be someone who could quietly approach them, without them being aware of it.

The human figure sat crossed-legged on the ground. He wore a simple sackcloth, his long blonde hair draped over his shoulder. On his fair handsome face, there were three red marks on his brow.

As Hannet saw the three red marks, he could roughly guess the identity of the man.

"Lord of Black Swamp Palace Garen. I never thought you would sneak into the house of others, like a thief."

"Those are just titles." The other party laughed. Behind that handsome face, he gave people a dangerous and dazzling feeling. "As long as I like, I’ll do it. It will be too tiring to consider so many things."

Hannet and his companion were facing a great enemy. At the Ancestral God Grounds, he didn't know who this young man was and what was his identity. It was only after his uncle pointed out that Hannet knew how dangerous this man was. To be able to kill thousands of people and feel nothing, even if he wasn't the strongest, he would at least be a generational overlord.

Although Hannet saw Garen blocking the Cthulhu Kings attack through the air, he hadn't experienced it firsthand. He totally had no idea how powerful Garen was.

Until now. The opponent before him slowly emitted a needle-like murderous intent. Only now did he understand that his previous evaluation of this man was too low.

"Lord Garen coming to find me, this poor fellow, what would you have us do?" Hannet cooled down. The tough experiences of his past and his awakened memories of his past life allowed him to quickly steady himself.

Looking at Hannet and his companion, Garen blinked his narrow eyes.

"I say, little brat. Have you forgotten our initial appointment? You are the one who gave me this address."

"That was me." The middle-aged man on the side suddenly spoke. His forehead was full of cold sweat. Under the effect of Garen’s aura, both of his legs were shaking, seemingly unable to hold his weight.

"It was me who passed you the address."

The middle-aged man psyched himself up.

"Lord Garen, we have a common enemy in the Cthulhuism Society. As the saying goes, the enemy of my enemy is my friend…"

His voice came to an abrupt halt.

Once the middle-aged man saw Garen looking at him, his body instantly fell into limbo. It was as if a great fear was overwhelming him from the inside. Both of his legs gave way, and he bowed to the ground. His eyes were blurry and his body was covered with sweat. He could no longer speak.

He was different from Hannet. He was just a first form totem user and his core totem had only one ability, stealth. Under the pressure of Garen’s aura, his courage instantly disappeared. He was on the brink of collapsing.

Garen snorted. A delusional, small, ant thought he could be on par with him. A giant dragon would not associate itself with trash that couldn't even be considered food. Both of them were clearly not contributing on the same level. Only Hannet, the last Thunder God, someone with special attributes, could capture his attention.

"Uncle!" A sense of anger flashed through his eyes.

"Don't worry. I'm just letting him quiet down for a moment." Garen said without bothering. This experienced old man was much harder to appease than the last Thunder God. It would be better to keep him silent.

"What are you trying to do?!" Hannet stood still on the ground and didn't dare to move. As he faced the opponent’s pressure, only then he realized the terror of this man. The air around him seemed to have a huge pressure which was constantly pressing on him. The blood throughout his body was boiling. It flowed faster and faster, becoming hotter and hotter. He was indeed more courageous than a normal person. He stood still to face Garen.

Garen finally let out a smile.

"What I want to do is simple." He flipped over his hand and showed a fist size crystal sphere. The transparent crystal sphere was incredibly beautiful. This sphere itself most likely could be sold for tens of thousands of Rumbs in the market.

But Hannet’s gaze was attracted by the dead matter within the sphere.

"Cthulhu's Origin!!??" He couldn't hold in his shock.

"Oh? You recognize it." Garen let out a satisfied smile. "The true form of the Thunder God is an inhibitive substance, a purification substance. I’m sure you now know what I want you to do for me?"

Hannet’s face turned pale.

"You're crazy! To purify Cthulhu's Origin, one needs to completely defeat the will of the Cthulhu King! No one can do it! No one!" In his mind, he suddenly remembered his past self being forced by the Cthulhu King. Eventually, he had no place to go and died a terrible death. That blood red blur is an undefeatable nightmare. Even now, he would dream of that horrifying figure from time to time. His pressure was almost suffocating.

"You just have to do it." The smiling intent in Garen's eyes instantly disappeared. A huge, terrifying pressure was instantly released. It pressured Hannet's body.

Hanner held on to his knees, not allowing himself to bow. Under the two forces, his knees started to crack.

"I saved your life the last time. As basic integrity, shouldn't you repay me?" Garen's mouth was still smiling but his gaze was incredibly cold. It gave off a terrifying, paradoxical feeling.

Hannet’s sweat was like a stream, flowing down from both his temples. The sweat gathered beneath his chin, and continuously fell to the ground.

"Remember, I’m passing this Cthulhu’s Origin to you. How long do you need to prepare?"

"Three...three days!" Hannet knew that if he didn't accept, both he and his uncle would die here today. He bit his teeth and struggled to squeeze out a few words.

"Three days later, I will come to look for you." Before he finished speaking, the figure in the house disappeared in a flash.

The pressure seemed to be just a dream, and disappeared instantly.

Puff!

Hannet sat on the ground. His whole body and even his underwear was wet. It was as if he had just come out from water.

"Three days from now, Beckstone and the rest would be here. That time, they definitely would be able to handle this guy." The more he thought of it, the more afraid he became. Only that bloody red figure had this kind of oppression. Moreover, Garen could already comprehend it at fourth form.

This discovery made him tremble from the bottom of his heart. As someone who doesn't like to rely on his companions, for the first time, he strongly hoped for Beckstone’s quick arrival.

As the Terraflor Society’s first generation pride, Beckstone's talent was his terrifying speed of evolution. He definitely would be able to counter the opponent’s pressure.

　　**********

On a deserted corner outside the house, Garen lazily laid beneath the shade of a huge tree. He layered his two hands behind his head and used them as his pillow. The midday sun shined on his body, providing gentle warmth.

As the gentle breeze blew by, it brought the gentle fragrance of the flora nearby. From time to time, butterflies and bees would pass by him.

He lifted his head. Through the gap in the leaves, he could see the blue sky. It was like premium sapphire.

How long was it since he had such a comfortable feeling?

Garen was counting his mind. He could not remember when was the last time he could relax like this.

These three days were periods of rare rest for him. Every day, other than that three hours needed to fuse the dragon heads, he was completely free for the rest of the time. He could completely relax his body, to adjust his body condition for the upcoming battle.

He was displeased with the last time Hannet ran away on his own. This time he wanted to show him who was boss. Aura pressure and totem pressure were two completely different concepts.

Analyzing the difference in grade, aura pressure is from a person’s heart. When a higher grade aura pressures a lower grade aura, it could completely overwhelm the opponent.

Furthermore, aura encompasses the will, which is a combination of spirit, soul and body. The effects are even more obvious when applying aura on someone that didn't have an aura. Like the oppression between a tiger and a rabbit, this was a natural oppression on one’s

subconscious. Even seeing it would make the person tremble and overwhelmed by fear.

Resistance was impossible.

Most of the time, the body's natural defense mechanism towards danger is beneficial. But when facing aura, the effects were negative. It would numb the body of the being, disabling its movement. The whole body would be in an extremely panicked state. Because the expenditure of energy was too overwhelming, the opponent wouldn't even need to do anything to shock the other person to death. Even elites who could withstand it would also break down due to the body’s huge loss of energy.

This was the terror of aura. It was a dangerous technique created based on natural body instinct.

After Garen's body started to have the combination of power from blood flow and totem light, his aura could be used once again. It was also far stronger than his previous peak.

This kind of aura could bypass the defense of totem light, directly affecting to the body. Garen was delighted. Although he had predicted it, but truly obtaining such a beneficial change would definitely bring joy.

Chapter 493: Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The change of aura originated from his body’s new power. This was Garen’s biggest achievement. If it were before he surpassed his totem light, the blood-colored aura looked strong, but in fact, couldn't be directly used on totem users. Its capabilities were to be a supplement to corrosive poison to corrode the other party’s totem light, and it was a large, area of effect ability. And now, it had returned to its original purpose.

Other than the aura, the other thing was the Cthulhu’s Origin.

The Cthulhu’s Origin was a treasure that allowed the Obscuro Society's marshalls to reach peak fifth form. It's effects were definitely supernatural.

However, to use the Cthulhu's Origin, one has to remove the Cthulhu King’s will. To do this, one has to first use Hannet’s purification abilities to draw itn out, then destroy it with an external force. Only then could the Cthulhu’s Origin be used properly.

As he lay underneath the shade, Garen got more and more relaxed, as if he was about to enter a dream.

Time passed by slowly.

In the afternoon, Garen woke up from his deep slumber. After training the Black Water True Technique for a moment, he sat crossed-legged on the ground to set up his communication rings.

He had three communication rings. They were for Scylla, Black Swamp Palace and the Secret Service each.

He hadn’t been using the Secret Society ring much after the director and the rest moved away. Most likely, they have settled on the fringes of the world fissures, which was a remote area in between Kovitan and the Artic Circle.There was a majestic, giant castle in that area, which was a fortress to defend against monsters on the ground. Most of the people who left Kovitan had headed there. They tried to go underground from there to obtain protection from the Elder Council, and although some of them returned, most of them had already entered the mountain city and will never be back. The conditions of the kingdom did not allow them to return.

He took off the Secret Service’s ring and crushed it in his palm. Next, it was the ring given by Scylla.

He turned it lightly. A faint rustle came from the ring. After studying it for a while, Garen noticed that the principle usage of this ring was about the same as a radio. The only difference was that user could enjoy sole usage of an encrypted channel for communication. He patched into it, but there was no one on the other end to receive his company.

He closed this ring. After thinking for a moment, Garen activated the Black Swamp Palace’s ring.

This time, after a moment, a clap came from the other party. They had connected to each other.

"Is there anything?" It was Ivycius’ voice. His tone had a slight difference through the communication signal, but it was still as cold as usual.

"How are you recently? What’s your condition?" Since he was connected to Ivycius, Garen asked casually.

"Very good. Give me half a year more. I should be able to pass the fusion phase and enter fifth form." Ivycius answered faintly. "You are also in the fusion phase. Why did you run out anxiously?"

"Naturally, I have my own plans. How is the situation in the palace?" Garen continued asking.

"It’s alright. The only thing was that Blizzard and Angel of the Night fought the other day, destroying a small portion of the outer palace. Now it is still under repairs."

"Blizzard and Angel of the Night?" Garen’s head started to hurt. "Aren’t they together? Why did they fight?"

"For the laws you set. Elders have the authority to choose one disciple to be his own in the palace. Both of them set eyes on a newly recruited brat. Once they couldn’t decide who would get him, they started to fight." Ivycius also sounded helpless.

"Oh? A young brat? His talent is so high that two peak fourth forms would fight for him?" Garen was surprised.

"He is a child from a peasant background, not more than fifteen years of age. But in his foundational training of the Black Water True Technique, he only used three days to breakthrough level one, entering into level two." Ivycius answered faintly.

"Oh? That’s impressive!" Garem was instantly interested. As the one who created the Black Water True Technique, naturally he was the one who best understood the difficulty of this martial art. Even with terrifying talent, it was not probable for someone to be able to enter level two in such a short time. There must be a huge secret regarding this child.

When he did his recruitment, he didn’t care about background, but only ability. In the name of non-discrimination, he had his eyes on the genius peasant children. These children did not lack talent. All they lack was a string that they could hold on to climb upwards.

"What is special about him?"

Ivycius paused for a moment. "I can’t place it specifically. However, this kid has terrifying attributes. He has a steady will and strong spirit!"

"Strong spirit!?" Garen’s interest grew. For someone as proud and critical as White Rose Sword Sage, Ivycius to praise his spirit, he must have been abnormally special.

"Tell me. What did he do that made you feel that his spirit is strong?"

There was a pause on the other side. He didn’t answer immediately. After a while, he slowly opened his mouth.

"On the first day he entered the palace, he more than doubled the training of his fellow geniuses."

"Oh?" The corner of Garen’s mouth curved. This genius training camp was where the selected geniuses trained. It was also the place with the most challengers and pursuers for the positions of core disciples and Four Directions Sky Warriors.

"On the second day, he broke through level one. The speed of increment of his attributes were twice that of his peers. Only three others could be compared to him. Moreover." A hint of laughter escaped from Ivycius’ voice. "Moreover, he would meditate in front of your statue every day."

"Meditate?" Garen grew more and more interested. He knew that as the first Lord of Black Swamp Palace, there was a statue of him.

"Out of curiosity, I asked him as I passed by. I asked why did he come here to meditate. Guess his answer?" There was a hint of admiration in Ivycius’ voice as well.

"What did he say?"

"He said. The Lord of Black Swamp Place who gave grace to peasants was the first one to reinvent the world. And he himself, would be the second one who will control the world! He admires you, but it is mere admiration."

"Madness!" Garen couldn’t help but started laughing.

Mere admiration and not reverence. That meant he would one day surpass the other party. By meditating in front of Garen’s statue, it meant two things. One one hand, it meant respect. On the other hand, it meant that Garen was his target.

"What is the situation now? How long has he been in the palace?" Garen asked again. If he didn’t have to purify the Cthulhu’s Origin, he would have rushed back to meet this mad little brat.

"He has been in the palace for half a month. He is currently entering level three of the Black Water True Technique."

Hissss.. Garen sucked in some cold air. Before he left, he already passed on the first four levels of the martial arts to Ivycius.The first four levels were the key parts for a normal human to experience breakthrough.

Even his three most-favored disciples were only on level two currently.

Although this young brat had just entered the palace for half a month, he could actually reach the level three! He must be extremely compatible with the Black Water True Technique to have such frightening progress?

Garen suddenly realized that maybe, he had underestimated the people of the world. Among the peasants there were many terrifying geniuses. The only thing was they never had an opportunity to show it. Now with this rare opportunity, this power that was suppressed by nobles with totems for many years broke through all obstacles and surpassed all limits.

Garen put his hands on his knees. Suddenly he had a feeling. By creating the Black Swamp Palace, he was rewriting a new chapter in history.

Ivycius’ voice continued on.

"After you left, the palace functioned according to your orders. We continued to recruit students from all over the region; three batches of twenty four students each. The elders discussed and decided to segment the students into nine grades, based on the Nine-Headed Hydra. The levels are from one head to nine heads, with nine heads being the strongest. The Black Water True Technique can develop one’s potential. The young brat, being the first one to enter level three has started to have signs of developing totem power. So both elders fought because of him."

According to the agreement, elders were also qualified to acquire disciples. However, they were mere teachers of the path of the totem, not martial arts. The young brat was already highly sought after before he had even completed developing totem power. It was evident that he had outstanding talent.

Although Garen was almost at the peak of the continent, he felt the change of an era was coming when he heard of this news.

Mankind was failing, totem users were suffering heavy losses, but yet geniuses are everywhere. Is this a return to glory or the beginning of hell? No one knew the answer to this question.

"I’ll return as soon as I can." Garen gave his last reminders. He closed the ring and spiraled into deep thought.

Generation after generation, every era wouldn’t be lacking of outstanding people. Who knows whether this young brat would be the next Hellgate. He could be shockingly brilliant, eventually reigning the earth.

"For the Black Water True Technique that should at least take years, he actually entered level three in half a month. This talent….Even I wasn’t that fast when I was training in the Giant Statue Technique."

He thought of all the overlords in the world gathering together, using this world as their stage.

Unconsciously, a sense of pride gushed forward from his chest.

As he slowly stood up, the passion that was slowly depleting over the years started to burn again. The Black Water True Technique surged through his heart as it was operating faster and faster.

The hint of fear towards the Cthulhu King completely disappeared in that instance.

"The heart does not bow under power. Out of all the things in the world, only the heart can restrict a person. As long as the heart is not restricted…" Garen seemed to have an epiphany.

That student’s actions gave him a huge shock. He didn’t stop because of his current weakness. Instead, he made the highest point he could see as his target. That was his huge ambition. As long as he kept up his spirit, in addition to his talent, he would definitely be an outstanding person in the future.

Since the martial art world reached the level of king of the century, there seemed to be some changes.

Garen closed his eyes, carefully experiencing the minute feelings. It was as if everything had passed in a flash and he couldn't grasp it.

In fact, by going through time and space to another world, and experiencing growth from a weakling again by walking step by step and seeing so many different parts of history, he had already long reached the brink of breakthrough.

In a trance, he seemed to be able to see something in the distance. Hawk King Goth was strangled to death by a black net. Flower King Earnest was bound by red string, while Dragon King Alyson was frozen in an ice prison.

And also himself.

He bowed his head and looked at his body. There was a black volcanic ash-like substance on his body. It was doubt, fear, failure, distress...

Unconsciously, Garen’s mind got clearer and clearer. His worries and fear for Hellgate all these while, disappeared in a flash.

The black ash over his body gradually fell off, quickly revealing a set of clean clothes beneath.

Suddenly, he laughed towards the sky.

"Never thought it would be a young brat who gives me the warning."

At that moment, the level of the King of the Century faintly increased towards an unknown extent.

Chapter 494: Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As the Black Water True Technique in Garen’s body was churning crazily, the Nine-Headed Hydra roared towards the sky in the black space. His strong aura was almost tangible blood, constantly rolling around like boiling magma.

In that instant, Garen’s spirit seemed to have completely fused with the Nine-Headed Hydra’s spirit, combining into one entity. In the dark, the Nine-Headed Hydra let out a series of roars. It danced in joy and for the first time, it voluntarily coordinated with the Black Water True Technique, increasing the speed of fusion.

The sixth dragon head quickly fused into Garen's body. The strong dragon heart provided large amounts of fresh blood to nourish the newly fused flesh and bones.

The Nine-Headed Hydra did not reject this at all. It was as if Garen was a close relative. A sense of submission and respect came from the Nine-Headed Hydra, and at that point, it was as if Garen was the true Lord of the Swamp during ancient times.

With the voluntary cooperation of the Nine-Headed Hydra, the fusion became faster and faster. Garen didn’t need to exert energy at all. The Nine-Headed Hydra was like a passionate fanatic, voluntarily breaking down its own flesh. It fused into the Black Water True Technique’s cycle, digesting over and over as the fusion process continued, quickly becoming Garen’s own strength.

Garen stood silently under the shade. His heart was in peace, but there was a faint tyrannical will, creeping up within him.

He understood that this was the tyrannical will that was in the ancient Nine-Headed Hydra’s genome. Because the will was fitting for him, it allowed his core totem, the Nine-Headed Hydra to submit. It was completely willing to fuse into his body.

In ancient times, even the birds in the sky would fall to the ground under the roar of the Lord of the Swamp. This tyrannical, fearless will dominated everything. It was the pride of being one of the strongest living things in ancient times.

The incomplete core totem was still just a copy of the Nine-Headed Hydra. Facing the actual will of its ancestor, it chose to submit.

The villagers from a village far away seemed to hear the cry. There were footsteps heading his way.

Garen smiled and became a cloud of black smoke, then disappeared into the sides of the forest.

Now, with the Nine-Headed Hydra’s voluntary cooperation, the fusion of the dragon heads was no longer an issue. The time required was greatly reduced. Most likely, he needed no more than two days to completely fuse with the Nine-Headed Hydra, stepping into fifth form. Moreover, operating the Black Water True Technique required time, and couldn’t be rushed.

The ancient Nine-Headed Hydra’s tyrannical will was an unexpected fit with him. It actually had a faint intent of fusing with his spirit.

However, these were not major issues. The key thing was, the level of a peak fifth form was in his sights.

Phiroth. Cthulhu King. Both of them had already reached the level of peak fifth form. Their accumulation of power over the years was immense. But Garen could feel that Phiroth’s aura was stronger than the Cthulhu King.~

As the strongest king of Daniela in history, his will had long been at the level that Garen had just entered.

While the Cthulhu King had to rely on his countless years of accumulation to barely be on par with Phiroth.

Garen didn’t know how to describe this level. In Earth terms, it would be someone who was clear of his own heart, able to explore his innermost nature. His heart would be crystal clear, unable to be affected by anything external.

This realm allows one to finally unleash his greatest power. The state of body will not be affected by any external things. Under the shift of the will, one could even unleash powers like never before. He will not be threatened or cumbered. Whether he fights or retreats, there will be no hesitation.

At this level, the heart was like a bright pearl that could be separated into multiple layers. The outer layer will never be able to affect the inner layer.

"Never thought that there are people that can exceed the level of the King of the Century in this world.." Garen lamented. If Phiroth was already so strong, how about Hellgate, who was stronger?

Suddenly he felt thankful, thankful that he came to such a great era, thankful that he could compete with the strongest of this era to pursue what each wants.

　　********************

Three days later.

Under the dim light in the hut.

Hannet was crouching on the ground, drawing the final lines of the tactic formation.

On the floor of the hut, an extremely complex, round tactic formation could be clearly seen in front of another person in the hut.

This tactic formation seemed to be formed by layering more than ten other tactic formations on top of each other. Its diameter was only four meters, but there were more than ten thousand symbols in it. They were crammed together, like countless white bugs climbing on top of each other.

As the light flickered, it shined on Hannet’s sweaty forehead, reflecting a hint of grease.

"Finally, it is complete." Hannet slowly finished his carving and got up from the floor. "I just have to wait for a thunderstorm to connect to the electromagnetic field in the sky. Together with my body attributes, the Cthulhu’s Origin can be purified, drawing out the will of the Cthulhu King."

"What do we do after it is drawn out? None of us can withstand the Cthulhu King’s Will. Even just a glimmer of his will would be able to defeat all of us!" The middle-aged man on the side muttered.

"At that point, it would be up to that man." Hannet shook his head. "We are only responsible for drawing of the Cthulhu King’s will. The rest of it has nothing to do with us."

"Should we go and inform him now?" The middle-aged man asked.

Hannet nodded his head and sat on the ground. He looked exhausted. His eyes were full of bloodlines, showing an obvious lack of rest.

The middle-aged man stood up and came to pick him up.

"Unfortunately I can’t help much."

"No problem. Have Beckstone and the rest arrived?" Hannet closed his eyes and massaged his temples.

"I’ve told them of the urgency. They should be arriving today."

"That’s good."

"Since everything is prepared, shall we begin?" Suddenly, there was another voice in the hut.

The two of them were caught by surprise. Although they were mentally prepared, they were still shocked by the voice who suddenly appeared beside them.

"Lord Garen, are you sure you want to begin?"

Hannet quickly steadied himself and spoke.

"Definitely. How is the preparation of the Cthulhu’s Origin?" Garen was dressed in the same sackcloth clothes as two days ago. He had a smile on his face, looking gentle.

"The preparation is complete." Hannet bowed his head, trying to avoid the other party’s dark red pupils. It had only been a few days since he had seen the other party, but his aura had become more concentrated by a fair bit.

"Let’s begin." Garen nodded.

Hearing the signal, Hannet stepped into the tactic formation. He placed the bright Cthulhu’s Origin in the middle. Then, he sat crossed-legged in the formation. He placed his two palms on the ground on the only two empty areas in the formation.

Buzzz….

A wave of blue, luminous light came from the tactic formation. All the internal lines in the formation glowed in blue. Currents of electric flowed from Hannet’s body into the formation below.

The Cthulhu’s Origin was placed right in the middle. With a cracking sound, the crystal ball suddenly cracked. The white sticky liquid slowly flowed out from within, emitting white luminous light.

As the blue light and white light mixed together, the blue light slowly surrounded the white light and started spinning.

Seconds and minutes went by. With the white light as the center, the blue lightning arcs slowly formed a vortex with a two-meter diameter.

Crack!!

A flash of lightning flashed across the vortex. In the middle of the vortex, a full-blue shadow of a bird appeared.

The blue bird was like a peacock. Its tail had nine, long, lightning feathers. The feathers and blue light were combined together and couldn’t be differentiated.

Crack!

As another lightning arc flashed by, a human-faced bird shadow rose up from the formation. The Human-Faced Bird was fully blue. There was no expression on its face, far different from the Nine-Tailed Bird.

The Nine-Tailed Bird and Human-Faced Bird caught the white Cthulhu’s Origin in between them. As the two palm-sized blurs suspended in the blue and white light, the lightning arcs in the blue light increased in number, becoming denser and denser.

The white liquid in the middle also had signs of becoming clear.

As the buzzing grew louder, the whole hut seemed to start shaking.

"Success!!" Hannet let out an expression of joy. "As the Origin starts to become clear, it is a sign that the purification process is a success!" He said loudly.

Garen, who was standing outside the formation, let out a smile.

Suddenly, there was a series of hurried footsteps coming from outside the house. As the footsteps got nearer, it got more hurried.

Bang!

The door was knocked open. A tall, silver-eyed young man rushed in suddenly.

"Beckstone wait!!" A girl’s urgent cry came from behind him.

Hannet and uncle were overjoyed. It was as if they had let go of a huge burden. They felt much more relieved.

Beckstone, a fourth form and the genius of the Terraflor Society, can definitely scare the Lord of the Black Swamp Palace.

Entering fourth form before he hit thirty, in addition to the strong Terraflor Society behind him, even the arrogant Black Swamp Palace wouldn’t take him lightly. He wouldn’t ignore the giant Terraflor Society.

He met Beckstone during a totem forum in the past. At that time, himself, Tina, Beckstone and another companion stood up simultaneously against a group of bullies. That was how they met.

After that, they realized the chemistry between their totem abilities and so happen could form a small group. Hence, they did so and completed multiple tasks in the Luminarist Guilds. They even set up a small mercenary squad.

After multiple afflictions, their bond grew stronger. Many times, they sacrificed their lives for each other and could be considered friends for life.

This time, when Hannet heard that Beckstone was rushing over, although he said that he didn’t want to rely on others, but in fact he felt warm. The Beckstone now was no longer a normal person like before. His words and actions represented the Terraflor Society. He was a major figure and a genius of the next generation, almost on par with the Three Great Heroes.

In fact, the fame of the Three Great Heroes was built on the three major regions. They used their natural strong forces to protect many peasants and nobles. However in an individual battle, Hannet believed that they might not as skilled as Beckstone.

As both of them lifted their head to looked at Beckstone and his companion, they realized that Beckstone’s and Tina’s expressions were abnormally strange.

"Ga...Garen!!" Beckstone slowly called out the name of the man before him with a low voice.

Before Hannet and his uncle could smile, their mood gradually sunk, together with Beckstone’s low voice. They could evidently see Beckstone’s face turning white. His gaze looked extremely anxious. Together with Tina behind him, both of them seemed...seemed to be in fear.

Hannet’s heart sank.

"My teacher, how is he?" Garen turned to look at the two people. He smiled as he asked.

"Mr. Emin is doing very well." Beckstone bowed slightly. Glimmers of golden totem light were swiftly flowing around him, as if his strong fourth form aura could explode anytime.

He hadn’t forgotten the past two humiliating battles. The man before him had completely become his nightmare. He kept on trying his best to improve himself. But every time he thought of that defeat, his heart would grow cold.

As the white light in the hut grew brighter and sharper, a strange aura slowly flowed out from the white Origin.

Chapter 495: Battle 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Not purifying the Origin on a stormy day would originally be considered inadequate. But since the Cthulhu King's will had voluntarily came out, it was an entirely different story.

Under the blue and white light, Garen did not have any intentions of taking action. He merely stood still and turned his head to continue looking at the Origin in the tactic formation.

Beckstone and Tina watched Garen with extreme caution. They didn't dare to get too close, hence they stayed close to the wall while walking towards Hannet and his uncle.

The hut was terrifyingly quiet. Only the crackling sounds from the blue lightning arcs could be heard from time to time.

As the blue light glowed on Garen's face, it seemed to reflect a hint of coldness.

As the strange aura of the Cthulhu's Origin became denser, some white gas was slowly diffusing out. The gas seemed intangible, appearing and then disappearing again.

Crash!!

Garen's hands suddenly tremored. He threw the remaining Cthulhu's Origins accurately into the middle of the tactic formation.

Crack!!

Suddenly, there was a roll of thunder in the sky outside the house.

All the people from the village raised their head in shock. The weather was originally clear, but large amounts of clouds suddenly gathered together quickly.

"What are those!!?" Someone cried out.

All the villagers were stunned. They dropped whatever they held in their hands. Those that were in their houses ran out. Some of them were carrying their children.

Everyone stared at the sky.

The sky was originally clear, without any clouds. As they watched, more and more clouds gathered.

"No! Those are not clouds!" The village chief who was holding a staff raised his head and spoke.

At that moment, it was as if the huge white clouds instantly became red, as if they had been doused in red ink.

In the hut

There was a passionate smile on Garen's face. He raised one of his hands and grasped at the sky.

The whole roof was corroded silently, like melting candles or snow. There was a large round hole within a few minutes.

Chiiii!!!!!

From the middle of the tactic formation, a red light beam suddenly shot towards the sky. Sharp cries came endlessly. The whole hut disintegrated instantly. Like the roof, the four walls quietly melted into oblivion.

Hannet and the rest had to escape from the hut. Beckstone protected everyone, forming a hemisphere of golden totem light. The crowd looked at the beam from afar in horror.

As the blood-red beam broke through the red clouds in the sky, numerous air streams surrounded it and rotated under high speed.

Garen stood in front of the beam and lifted his head towards the sky, as though the sharp cries and giant tremors did not affect him at all.

In the sky above, numerous blood-colored clouds gathered quickly, forming the shape of a giant face.

The blood-colored face was like a thin mask. There was a silver-faced, red-robed man standing out its right pupil.

From above, the red-robed man glanced down, meeting Garen's gaze.

The wind was howling and the blood-colored clouds were rolling. The whole sky became dark as the sun was completely blocked by the plentiful blood-colored clouds. Only the gigantic blood-colored face and the silver-faced, red-robed man on its left pupil remained.

"You shouldn't have lured me out." The Cthulhu King's voice was metrosexual, unable to determine his gender.

"Have a battle with me." Garen smacked his lips. There was a glimmer of excitement in his eyes. "I tried my best to use the will in the Origin as bait, luring your true self. It wasn't to have a casual chat with you."

The two eyes under the Cthulhu King's mask glowed in red and gave Garen a glance.

"You are not my opponent. Enough strong men have died at my hands."

Before the voice ended, he lifted his hand and pressed downwards.

Suddenly, a beam of red light fell from the sky like thunder.

Bang!!

The pillar descended and shot towards Garen's location at an amazing speed.

Bang!

Garen lifted his hands to block it. Numerous red light arcs passed by his two sides like water. He was fiercely pressured, almost into the ground. The black totem light around him also changed its shape due to the pressure.

"Fragile." The Cthulhu King's scornful voice came from the sky above. Suddenly, the red glow in his eyes dimmed. "Yes? I'll let you go this time. The next time, you won't be so fortunate."

Before he finished his words, the face in the sky dissipated, forming numerous red clouds which eventually disappeared. The Cthulhu King himself also disappeared.

The giant red light slowly disappeared after a few seconds.

Majority of Garen's body had been completely pressured into the ground. Even totem light couldn't withstand such a terrifying attack.

The giant beam pressured him and left him speechless.

After the red light completely dispersed, Garen stood on the ground in rage. The Cthulhu King's explosiveness was far stronger than he had imagined. But it didn't mean he couldn't defend against it. It was just that he didn't adapt in time. As he was about to counter-attack, he never thought the Cthulhu King would flee!

The explosiveness of the Cthulhu King's martial arts was far stronger than the Black Water True Technique. Its power was also abnormally terrifying. It wasn't as dense as the Black Water True Technique, but its power was far superior. However, with that incident, it meant that he'd been left speechless by a casual attack from the Cthulhu King. This caused the ancient Nine-Headed Hydra's ego to be severely provoked.

The environment around was quiet. No one dared to speak for fear of attracting Garen's rage. The villagers had already retreated from the village under the leadership of the experienced chief. They were watching from the outer forest.

Hannet, Beckstone and the rest under the protection of the golden hemisphere also looked at the scene in fear. In a battle of fifth forms, even the aftermath left Beckstone's golden protection hemisphere full of cracks. A bit more power would completely shatter it.

Garen was suppressing his rage when he saw Beckstone's group from afar. He suddenly waved his hand.

Roar!!

Poisonous gas in the shape of a black dragon rushed over and collided with the golden protection hemisphere.

After collided on the hemisphere with a crack, it fiercely lashed at Beckstone's body.

Bang!

As if being punched from a close distance by someone, Beckstone and the rest were blown away, colliding fiercely with the wall behind.

"What are you doing!!" Tina wasn't severely hurt as most of the force was blocked by Beckstone. "Can't defeat the Cthulhu King then take us as punching bags!? Now I know that the Lord of Black Swamp Palace is a villain. I used to think you were an incredibly strong master! I was wrong!" She got to her feet and shouted loudly.

"Stop talking Tina!" Beckstone caught hold of Tina and stood in front of her. Blood was flowing from the edges of his mouth.

Hannet also got on his feet. His face was pale. He helped his uncle up, whose head was covered in blood. His expression was full of rage.

Garen had a strange sense of guilt on his face instead. The rage on his face disappeared instantly. It was as if he was performing a face-changing act. His expression quickly became calm.

"I'm sorry. I was impulsive in the moment. Hannet lured out the Cthulhu King for me and helped me so much. Yet I attacked you. It's my fault."

He had no expression at that point in time. Tina who had a strong intuition could easily see if one was sincere. At that time, she actually felt that Garen was sincerely apologizing.

"It's my fault this time. I should've killed you today Beckstone. Unfortunately…." Garen let out a sigh of regret, then became a black cloud and disappeared on the spot.

The surroundings were quiet without any other noises. Only the sound of the wind blowing above the village could be heard.

In a wooden hut behind Beckstone.

Two white-robed men and women looked at each other and laughed. The shining green seeds in their hands slowly dimmed.

"He sensed our presence." The man spoke softly.

"What about that? With the Seed of Light, we only have to chant the spell to bring Beckstone away. Even if he attacked it won't be beneficial for him." The girl smiled. "We have troubled you this time."

"Why do you mention this between us?" The guy shook his head. "Sisley, what do you plan to do next?"

"We don't have much time. The Nine-Headed Hydra should have entered the separation stage. It is troublesome. He is on the same level as Phiroth, very troublesome. To fuse the totem's blood vessels and will into the body to achieve complete fusion in spirit, not only the man would affect the totem, the totem will also affect the man. However, he can independently use the totem's mode, to form a perfect totem fusion power for battle. Not many can surpass him in actual strength."

"This guy is so young, yet had already entered this level.." The guy said in regret. "Let's not bother about him. Once Hellgate awakens, he will also be one of our greatest helpers. Let's consider how to handle the Clash of Clans."

"I've already contacted the kings of the three regions. This time we can't go, or…." The girl whispered but the man held her hand tightly. Warmth came from the man's hand.

"Don't worry. I will always be by your side."

The girl lifted her face and revealed a young, gentle face. She leaned into the man's embrace.

Two of them turned and instantly became green light, then disappeared.

　　*****************

Garen was traveling at high speeds in the forest. He was a like a black line on a green carpet, incredibly evident.

As the warm sun shone from above, his shadow wasn't left behind.

After running for some time, he came to a sudden halt. He closed his eyes and sensed his surroundings. The Cthulhuism Society's major rendezvous point wasn't far away.

After being defeated by the Cthulhu King, the ancient Nine-Headed Hydra's will was displeased. Garen decided to look for a group of Cthulhus that could be easily found.

Moreover in a head to head battle, not to mention himself, even the stronger Phiroth couldn't take on the Cthulhu King plus the other eighteen Cthulhus together. Immortality was the terrifying point of the Cthulhus. Even by grinding, they could wear out a majority of elites.

He could sense the aura and voice of a Cthulhuism Society stronghold from afar.

Garen leaped onto a large tree branch and crouched on it.

"It's getting more and more exciting." He mumbled and looked at the Cthulhuism Society stronghold in the distance. It was shaped like a red bucket.

As he was about to attack Beckstone, he suddenly sensed an unknown teleportation power surrounding Beckstone and the rest. This power was very difficult to sense as it kept appearing and disappearing. There were also two strong auras around that were incredibly in sync.

The intense vitality in the aura made him think of the Terraflor Society. Only plant totems would have that kind of aura.

Terraflor Society was always under the radar, but Garen knew about the original history. He didn't forget one bit. After Hellgate's awakening, Sisley, the Terraflor's leader, one of the elites that could take on Hellgate in the East Continent will also be awakened. The battle between was even recorded extensively in the history of the universe.

All this while, the Terraflor Society had been led by the elders. Their leaders could not be found and their tracks were uncertain. However, after Hellgate's awakening, they were forced to appear to avoid the total destruction of the Terraflor Society.

Sisley was actually a woman. However, her husband has to be included in her abilities. In other words, the Terraflor Society's strongest force was actually this couple combined. Both of their core totems were a plant totem called Dual-Love Flower. The nature of this plant was one pair for a lifetime. They were connected like lovers, staying with each other in life and death. With the combined strength of the two of them, they managed to fight Hellgate. Of course, there were other factors, but they managed to hold Hellgate off for a substantial period of time.

Garen was organizing the original history in his mind. He roughly calculated the upcoming situation. After his latest upgrade, his core totem was in a unique state. It was in a state of the ancestral Nine-Headed Hydra's will, which allowed him to unleash the strongest battle ability.

The Black Water True Technique stabilized at the thirteenth level. He forced each level with each of his dragon heads.

Garen recorded the changes of every level, so the students in the Black Swamp Palace could master it as well. Since they didn't have the Nine-Headed Hydra's blood, they could never be as strong as Garen. However, if they trained it to the peak, they would at least be far stronger than a normal fourth form. If they were fortunate to find a core totem that fit well with the Black Water True Technique, they might have an opportunity to enter the fifth form.

Chapter 496: Battle 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Gathering his thoughts, Garen suppressed the Totem Light force field before removing a Cthulhu’s Origin crystal ball from his belt.

The three Cthulhu’s Origins inside were rotating around one another, forming a beautiful ring.

Light God’s Origin, Time God’s Origin, War God’s Origin.

The white, black and red halos rotated constantly, endlessly. The Cthulhu’s Will inside had already been removed completely, removed by the Cthulhu King to locate its coordinates.

Currently, these three Cthulhu’s Origins had become absorbable powerful treasures.

Despite this, Garen was unsure of how to absorb this to receive the Origin’s effect; different resources required different absorption methods, while medicine could even become poisonous.

It was the same as using external medicine internally. Not only would there be no benefits, it might even prove dangerous.

"The only one who truly knows how to use it is the historical, unnamed Obscuro Marshall." Garen thought about everything that happened at the Ancestral God Grounds, and quickly focused on the masked female Obscuro Marshall.

"I’ll go see the Cthulhuism Society first, if that doesn’t work, go find the female Obscuro Society Marshall!" he instructed himself in his mind.

The figure turned into a shroud of black smoke instantly and silently shot towards the Cthulhuism Society’s bloody wooden fortress.

Boom!!

The main door of the wooden fortress cracked open instantly and split inwards, violently smashing into a few followers who were guarding the place.

"Enemy attack!!"

A loud roar echoed from within the fortress.

Garen stood in front of the wooden main door, watching as the Cthulhuism Society’s followers clad in red leather clothes rushed out, each of them holding glowing red long spears as they charged towards him. A few Totem Users stood at the back, while both of their hands drew Tactics quickly. Layers of Tactical Formations slowly illuminated with white light in their surroundings. At the same time, many Totem beasts also pounced out from all four corners.

The corners of his mouth curled into a sneer, and without any movement, the Black Water True Technique began to rotate slowly.

Garen stepped on the ground.

A cloud of black Poison Mist was released suddenly, before it filled the surroundings.

Desperate cries rang out without cease, while a large group of Totem beasts that were caught in between wailed loudly.

With Garen as the center, all of the Cthulhuism Society’s followers prostrated on the ground and rolled around screaming. The flesh melted off their bodies instantly like a candle, until only their skeletons were left.

Soon, only white bones were left inside the entire fortress.

The strongest Cthulhuism Society Totem User was only Form 3 and had not even achieved Spiritualization yet. He had only resisted for little while longer in the Poison Mist.

Looking at the entire bloody fortress from a far, there were clouds of black Poison Mist that surrounded the fortress closely. They had taken on the shape of a dragon as it drifted past.

"Is there not even one person of substance here? What about the Cthulhus?" Garen furrowed his eyebrows and scanned his surroundings, noticing that within a short span of two minutes, this place had completely transformed into a dead city.

The hundreds of people inside had all become nutrients for the Black Water True Technique, fusing into the Poison Mist.

"This place is a great distance from the Ancestral God Grounds. Perhaps the Cthulhus have all returned to their respective stations," he furrowed his eyebrows and guessed. "However, I just need to destroy a few more of Cthulhuism Society’s bases, and the Cthulhus will probably appear by then."

**********************

Half a month later

Ender in the East Continent

Somewhere on the long coastline, blue-white waves crashed against the shore before receding, leaving dark water marks that disappeared almost instantly.

Two slender silhouettes walked side-by-side across the beach, strolling. Rays of light from the sunset bathed both of them, casting them in a layer of gold and red and causing two narrow shadows to form behind them.

"You’ve really made up your mind?" One of the silhouettes belonged to a young man clad in long black robes with dark gold lace trimmings. His chest was unclothed, exposing white bandages that were wrapped around his bare upper body and waist. Faint traces of blood on top lined the top.

"For the sake of this goal, how many years of hard work have we endured already? Just when we’re about to succeed, you decide to withdraw from seclusion?"

The other person was a woman who reached her hand out to comb her hair messed up by the sea breeze. Like the man, she also wore a long robe with dark gold lace trimmings, except that she also had a tight-fitting white T-shirt inside, while a black ring hung down in front of her ample chest.

The woman turned to the side and glanced at the unending seaside scenery, while a confused look appeared on her pale, average-looking face.

"You wouldn’t understand. It’s not the life I want." The white crescent-shaped earrings that hung from her ears shook slightly, adding some colour.

"Then what kind of life do you want?" asked the man faintly. "When we first joined Obscuro together, we decided that we would join and leave with each other, but now, I get out and the first thing I find out is that you want to retreat, don’t tell me there are people in the West Continent that dared to bully you?"

"To you, will I only ever be that little girl that gets bullied by everyone?" The woman could not help but smile. She kicked the pebbles on the beach while her head was lowered. "I’m just tired, my heart is tired."

The woman’s voice became softer.

"This life that is filled with nothing but chasing the unknown, it’s so tiring…"

"You promised me…"

"Don’t force me, okay?" The woman interrupted the man. "Have you not noticed? That I’m becoming less like myself?"

The man suddenly fell silent.

"How many years has it been since we strolled on the beach like this? Even though you and I both command a continent, and even if we stand any higher, or our powers become any stronger, what use would it be? A person would always feel exhausted in the end."

"So your trip to Daniela this time, was to obtain Love God’s Origin? And then retreat after it fused? Did you ever think of my feelings?" The man’s emotions began to bubble up. "I worked hard to become stronger, and made commanding a continent my only goal, for what exactly?"

He paused. "In the beginning, you said that once I achieved Spiritualization, you would consider marrying me. Then, I entered Spiritualization. Next, you said that because of your older brother, you couldn’t be selfish, so I needed to achieve Form 4 and help Big Bro before we could get married. And after that, I entered Form 4."

The woman bowed her head, lacking any rebuttal.

"Finally, you said that because of your brother, you had to head towards the West Continent, while being in charge of a military department." The man inhaled deeply. "For your sake, I determinedly immersed myself in your matters, and did unscrupulous things, before finally, becoming the head of the military in the whole continent. And now, you’re telling me that you’re prepared to retreat?!"

"I let you down…" The woman lowered her head.

"Hahaha…" The man laughed softly. "How many years has it been, don’t tell me these are the words you think I’ve been waiting for all these years?" His smile disappeared suddenly. He stared at the woman in front of him.

"Aixi, can I hold you, properly, one last time?"

The woman stayed silent, but her body inched closer to the man nonetheless.

The man suddenly took the woman in her arms tightly, as if he were holding the most valuable piece of treasure in the entire world. The unconcealable look of greed and desire appeared on his face and gaze, all hidden from an angle invisible to the woman.

"Let me hold you for a moment, just a moment… Alright?" he begged.

Perhaps it was because she felt guilty; the woman’s body stiffened slightly, but finally relaxed again, allowing the man to hold her tightly.

However, still out of the sight of the woman, the back of his palm faintly lit up with line after line of black symbols, The countless symbols soon crawled off the back of his right hand, like ants, quietly climbing onto the woman’s back.

"Aixi… You will always be mine, forever…"

The man murmured softly.

The woman suddenly realised something was wrong.

"God Cloud, let go of me!" She began to struggle, but it was useless. Her entire body had turned limp, as if she had no strength left. A burning sensation began to creep across the skin on her back.

"God Cloud! What are you doing?!"

"How pitiful…" Suddenly, a sympathetic male voice echoed out from nearby the two people.

"Who is it?!" God Cloud raised his head suddenly.

There was a crashing noise before a black chain exploded out from beneath the legs of the intruder, forming a hole. The chains disappeared instantly, forming a shadow.

Not far from the two people, stood a slender, well-built golden-haired man, whose tassel-like bright long hair was being blowing in the wind, a mocking expression plastered on his handsome face. He looked at the two people embracing one another.

"Didn’t think that I’d see such a romantic scene the moment I rushed over. Tch tch… Who would have thought the two Marshalls of Obscuro’s main military departments had this kind of.. confidential information."

"Black Swamp Palace Master Garen?" God Cloud loosened his grip on Aixi, holding her by the waist with one hand, propping her up against his own body. "Why are you here? If you’re here to get revenge after your breakthrough, I can accompany you anytime."

A look of faux surprise flashed across Garen’s face.

"I’ve always thought that you only liked men, I never expected that you would choose not not give up on women, too…"

"Damn you!"

God Cloud’s face suddenly contorted in rage.

Innumerable black chains shot out of the ground and flew towards Garen, before intertwining with one another and enveloping him, wrapping him into a metal ball in the blink of an eye.

However, strangely enough, all of the chains merely wrapped around air, and Garen appeared appeared in a different position from before. His hand reached out to pressed onto the surface of the chain ball gently.

Silently, the chain ball melted quickly into a black gooey liquid that fell onto the sandy beach.

"After spending such a long time in Kovitan as the concubine, don’t tell me you’ve forgotten the daily love and care His Majesty Avic showed you, God Cloud? Tch tch… That’s really brutal," said Garen with a sympathetic look on his face.

The expression on God Cloud’s face became even more contorted, while violent strength seemed to be bursting out of him like an exploding volcano, like a dam about to burst.

Unfortunately, to protect one person while confronting the newly peaked Form 5 in front of him was beyond his abilities, even for someone like himself. Moreover, the Distorted Beads were not with him anymore, and in order to control Aixi, he had used up half of his Totem Light, causing him to be in his weakest state right now.

God Cloud’s gaze flashed, while black chains slowly arranged themselves in Tactical Formations throughout his surroundings in midair. The chains seemed to be dispersed in a chaotic manner, but within the chaos possessed hidden, ordered movements.

Garen sneered, snapping his fingers lightly.

Bang!

A circle of black mist formed a ring and dispersed itself. It rushed straight for the black chain, quickly melting it into the same black viscous liquid before dropping onto the ground.

Within a range of a hundred meters around the three people, all of the living creatures were melted by the Poison Mist. Even the sea water turned slightly black.

"Trying to escape? I picked this timing on purpose, so why would I let you run away so easily?" Garen smiled. "To control your lover, you picked this location specially, and even arranged everything in advance. With such good timing, do you really think I would let you off so easily? Now, tell me about the fusion methods of the Cthulhu’s Origins."

Chapter 497: Venus 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Fusion methods of the Cthulhu’s Origin?"

God Cloud’s mind relaxed; as long as his opponent still had demands, this would be easy.

A puzzled expression was currently plastered on Aixi’s face while she was being propped up by God Cloud with one hand. Even though a large amount of black symbols were crawling up her back slowly, she felt nothing, but even so, pain seemed apparent in her eyes.

Looking at Garen, who was not far away, her mouth moved to speak but no sound came out. Even her right to speak was being controlled by God Cloud.

Lowering her head, Aixi stopped moving. Regarding God Cloud’s minor movements, she was no longer worried. She was just being held, gently, by him, while both her eyes were half shut.

"You want to fuse the Cthulhu’s Origin?"

God Cloud did not notice Aixi’s current expression because he was glaring at the man opposite him instead.

Black Swamp Palace Master Garen Trejons. He had a breakthrough not long ago and entered lower Form 5, but his battle skills rivaled peak Form 5 in reality. He had slaughtered countless Cthulhuism Society bases consecutively and defeat many Cthulhu alliances, before finally disappearing suddenly. No one had expected him to suddenly appear here.

"To hand it over or not, that is your own choice." Black Poison Mist permeated out from below Garen’s feet continuously, surrounding a range of more than hundreds of meters around him, enveloping around God Cloud and the woman tightly as well.

Within the black mist, black chains began floating out of midair in the surroundings of the two people. It resisted the corrosion of the Poison Mist.

God Cloud’s eyes flashed; the current situation between him and his enemy was undesirable.

"I can give you the methods, but who can assure me that you won’t make another move after I give it to you?"

"This will depend on your luck." Garen laughed, he had noticed Aixi a long time ago, but she was always exiting the Obscuro professionals’ base, and thus he had no opportunities, and could only keep following closely behind her and wait for his chance.

He never expected that Aixi would leave the base alone this time, and when he found out that the person she was meeting was actually God Cloud, Garen prepared to retreat quietly, but never thought that God Cloud would make a move first.

When he grasped the key moment when the two Marshalls would be at their weakest, Garen appeared instantly.

Both of the Marshalls would surely have Crystal Derivators, but with professionals of their level, Totems that were controlled by something like that would only be useful to delay time. The true determinant of victory or defeat depended on one’s own strength.

"Alright, I can give the Origin fusion method to you. But this method requires a longer time to be explained verbally…" God Cloud hesitated slightly, opening his mouth suddenly.

"It doesn’t matter, we have more than enough time." Garen’s mouth stretched into a smile, exposing his pearly white teeth, but strangely enough, his current teeth had become slightly sharper, and resembled a saw, unlike human teeth.

"For plotting against President Hellgate’s blood-related younger sister, the West Continent military department Marshall, your future days will not be good, God Cloud… Do you want to consider leaving Obscuro Society to join my Black Swamp Palace instead?"

"You don’t have to worry about that anymore." Aixi opened her mouth suddenly. White light flashed throughout her whole body before she escaped from God Cloud’s arms at once and stood on his side quietly. It was obvious that God Cloud had given up his control of her, allowing her to escape.

"Big Brother God Cloud did not do anything to me, your eyes have fooled you."

Garen’s expression remained unchanged, he was now sure that Aixi was the historical Marshall that had broke through using the Cthulhu’s Origin, but at this moment it was obvious that she had not broken through yet, and did not need to be feared. Meanwhile God Cloud had had a burden removed from him, and could relax during this battle. Victory and defeat would be harder to determine now. However, it was fortunate that the Tactics from earlier had left a large impact on his remaining strength.

A somber expression flashed past God Cloud’s face, but he opened his mouth calmly, before he started to explain the methods and conditions of absorbing the Cthulhu’s Origin.

"The Cthulhu’s Origin is evil and manic, most people should not even think of absorbing it, merely approaching it could cause someone to be bewitched by the strength of the Origin. Once the mind is completely immersed in it for eternity, they will be unable to free themselves. They must be of a high level, and their will must be extremely strong, before they are able to absorb it without being influenced completely. We at Obscuro and the Obscuro Society have been researching it carefully to find the easiest method of absorption, and although there is a certain amount of risk attached, the dangers have been reduced significantly. This method of absorbing the Origin has two conditions."

He paused. "First, the Cthulhu King’s will must be removed, and I’ve heard that you’ve already reached this step, so I won’t talk about that. Meanwhile, the second condition is that you need to use proper, fitting Ancient Endor Secret Techniques and adjust them."

"Adjust Ancient Endor Secret Techniques?" Garen raised his eyebrows slightly.

"That’s right, the Cthulhu’s Origin possesses a nature that is extremely violent and tempting. Without a method of adjustment, even if you were to get stronger, you would only destroy it and would not be able to absorb it for your own use," said God Cloud indifferently. "If that wasn’t the case, why do you think that Aixi would be the only one in Obscuro Society that would be able to absorb it?"

"Then Scylla and the others…"

"There will be certain short term benefits, but it will become a hurdle that will obstruct them in the future. The longer it drags on, the stronger this hindrance will become, causing them to deteriorate in the end." A mocking expression appeared on God Cloud’s face. He was truly shrewd, as he could remain calm even after Garen ridiculed him earlier, while being able to explain everything to him clearly.

"Then which Origins are to be used with which Secret Techniques?" Garen continued asking.

"The Secret Techniques that can be matched with the Origins have always been in the hands of the Cthulhu King, and Aixi had coincidentally found out that her own Secret Technique which the Love God's Origin hadn’t rejected too much. This was how she absorbed it. I heard that you obtained different types of Origins from the Cthulhu King, and to remove the Cthulhu King’s will, you almost had a full-on battle with him. Unfortunately, the Cthulhu King’s Secret Technique is the only way to match all of the various Cthulhu’s Origins, and if you want to absorb all of the Origins, the only method is for you to obtain the Cthulhu King’s Secret Techniques on your own," God Cloud sneered. "Don’t assume that this is a trick, there are many people that know about this method, and some people from the Hidden World school of thought are also aware of it, but no one has been able to reach this point."

Garen furrowed his eyebrows.

If all of this was true, this would be an overt plan, and it seemed that God Cloud had already correctly guessed that he could not afford not to confront the Cthulhu King.

Suddenly, he smiled faintly. He outstretched his right hand, while his index finger pointed upwards.

Hiss!

A shroud of black mist shaped like a snake was released from his fingertip. It twisted and coiled around, just like a living creature, it let out snake-like hissing noises.

"I know the methods already, but since I came all the way here, I should return what I owe you from the battle at Snowy Peak."

Before he finished speaking, Garen suddenly released the black snake on his head.

The black snake rushed out, and grew larger in midair, and suddenly transformed from the thickness of a finger into a terrifyingly large snake that had a diameter of a few meters. It opened its large mouth and rushed towards God Cloud.

Countless clouds of black Poison Mist rolled around as the black snake let out silent howls while charging directly towards God Cloud. The incomparably toxic corrosive smoke permeated throughout the surroundings as the sand on the beach was corroded into puddles of black water, while the nearby seawater turned black as well, and a rotten stench filled the air.

"Lock!!" God Cloud’s eyes widened as he placed both of his hands together quickly. Countless black chains burst out of the ground around him, forming a black cylinder, protecting him inside.

Pfoo!!

Throughout the whole beach, black chains burst out towards the sky like fountains in an extremely obtrusive manner.

The chain cylinder collided with the black snake while rays of black light burst out silently between them suddenly. Aixi stood wide-eyed on the sidelines, witnessing this peak Form 5 battle. Most Totem Users had never been given the chance to see something like this in their lifetimes.

The black light dispersed like a bomb that had exploded, and only remained for an instant before vanishing.

On the burnt yellow beach where explosion followed explosion, faint lights ignited from within and only a dull banging noise could be heard.

The figures of God Cloud and Garen violently crashed into one another repeatedly.

Both of them stuck close together, their four limbs a chaotic, overlapping flurry. The black chains and black Poison Mist in their surroundings intertwined with one another, while black melted liquid flowed downwards constantly.

Garen brought his palms together and brought them downwards, while all ten of his fingers were pressed against each other. He hit God Cloud’s arm with overwhelming violence from above, his whole body floating in midair, both of his eyes pitch-black, devilish slits.

God Cloud raised both of his arms to deflect the powerful hit from above, while the chains popped out from beside him periodically.

Boom!!

A large round pit split open beneath God Cloud’s feet, and a crater replaced what was a ten-meter diameter hemisphere of beach sand below.

"Wheel!!" A black hole appeared on God Cloud’s chest suddenly, and a ray of black light shot out of the hole, transforming into a slow rotating, complex round wheel.

The black wheel was filled with moving black chains and Tactic runes. Crisp wind noises could be heard in midair slowly, as if they were drifting over from a faraway place.

A similarly magnified black wheel appeared in the air beside Garen silently. A strong, locking attraction locked it in place, while everything inside the wheel, such as sand, sea water, and air, were all tightly held in place by the strong chain powers.

God Cloud had no intention of letting his guard down. He took a few steps backwards hastily, while the black wheel on his chest broke open, and a pitch-black arm stretched out of the black hole suddenly.

The five fingers on the hand all had sharp nails, while a ferocious face grew out of the palm. It appeared, it rushed towards Garen without pause, its claws pointed its target. A ripping noise could be heard at that moment, and five pitch-black cracks appeared. Apparently, it could even rip through thin air!

Within the black wheel, both of Garen’s eyes were devoid of pupils, leaving only darkness. The red marks on his forehead had disappeared completely long ago, and had slowly transformed into a narrow, black crack.

"Locked Wheel, huh?" He moved his body suddenly, while a crisp cracking noise could suddenly be heard throughout the air, as if porcelain had cracked or glass had broken.

"Black Water Traction!!"

Garen outstretched his right hand. Countless black snakes coiled around his arm, rushing towards the Pitch-black Demon Arm directly.

A crisp cracking noise rang across the beach.

The Pitch-black Demon Arm and Garen’s right arm collided against each other with crushing force, and at almost the exact same moment, both of them collapsed.

The Demon Arm broke into tiny pieces of flesh before turning into black light and disappearing, while a painful howl echoed out of the darkness.

Garen’s right arm broke off instantly as well, and turned into countless bloodied flesh pieces that flew everywhere, before instantly melting into the surrounding Poison Mist.

A bout of intense pain shot through his right arm, but Garen ignored it. The shadow of a dragon shrouded his face before a guttural roar rang out. His right leg rose into the sky, and countless tufts of black smoke amassed. His leg expanded and reached more than ten meters as a large column of black smoke appeared suddenly.

Bang!!

The two black figures separated at the same time, and flew towards opposite directions.

Blood flowed out of the bandages around God Cloud’s waist continuously, but soon stopped. His figure appeared half-kneeling on the ground, his expression unchanged while he took a deep breath before standing up.

On the opposite side of the sea, Garen’s figure had already gibbed into flesh chunks, and after the collision earlier, after he and God Cloud compared their physical strengths, he realized that ten points of Vitality could still allow anti-shock abilities to shatter his whole body.

The black Poison Mist quickly enveloped him into a mist ball, and in the blink of an eye, the mist had disappeared, and Garen’s healthy body had appeared once again.

His upper body was bare, while his lower body was covered by the Poison Mist. He was floating above the sea, as if he had not been injured at all.

"The Nine-Life Talent?" God Cloud raised his eyebrows slightly, he had just finished speaking, before the shadow of a black wheel appeared above his right shoulder in midair suddenly, it was only the size of a palm, but it emitted crisp, empty wind noises again in midair.

Bang!!

Garen’s body that he had just solidified suddenly exploded with a ‘bang’.

Chapter 498: Venus 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen, who was smiling at first, now had a different expression on his face. The darkness in his eyes that resembled the deep ocean had faded, while the black crack in his forehead had disappeared instantly, exposing an alarming color. His entire body, excluding his neck, was constantly exploding below, and it had only been a moment before his recently fixed body had exploded into many pieces.

The black mist lingered around him, and after a moment, his body returned to its original state, but the painful throbbing from earlier left a sense of fear in Garen’s heart. He controlled the black mist and moved it more than ten meters backwards, while looking at God Cloud who stood on the shore from afar.

He was no longer a rookie, unlike during the first battle with Ivycius. He had read and memorized a large amount of knowledge from the secret library in the palace, allowing him to understand God Cloud better.

God Cloud practiced the strangest Locked Wheel Secret Technique. It was rumored that there were nine realms of this Secret Technique, and that God Cloud had achieved the highest realm more than ten years ago. However, from his records, he had never heard of that untraceable ability from earlier.

God Cloud’s face remained unchanged. The black wheel on his right shoulder moved again, letting out crisp bell noises.

Bang!!

Garen’s body that had just been restored exploded again.

"Back!!" Without hesitating, Garen gathered the black mist and suddenly turned it into a ray of black light, allowing it to fly past. Within a blink of an eye, it disappeared deeper into the sea. The surrounding Poison Mist also quickly disappeared completely.

"Everyone assumed that there were only nine levels of the Locked Wheel, unfortunately, I exhausted my efforts, and finally pushed it to its unprecedented tenth level." God Cloud’s expression remained indifferent while he stood in his original position, looking at the direction in which Garen was leaving.

Suddenly, his left hand clawed against the beach floor.

A black light flashed, and a dull banging noise could be heard before a large cloud of Poison Mist exploded on the beach. Black light shot out of the Poison Mist and flew towards Garen like arrows.

"This is indeed worthy of God Cloud!" Garen’s voice echoed out of the black light faintly.

Aixi, who stood on the side, finally sighed in relief, as she walked over to stand beside God Cloud.

"Is he really leaving?"

God Cloud nodded.

Bang bang bang bang!!!

In a blink of an eye, countless bloody wounds exploded throughout his body, and large amounts of black blood gushed out, while the occasional Totem Light chains that circled his body broke as well.

"Go!" God Cloud struggled to spit the word out before he fainted.

Aixi, shocked beyond words, and waved her hand frantically. A piece of white satin flew out from her sleeve wrapping round the both of them then loosening, before both persons within the satin disappeared completely.

The white satin flew inland, and within the blink of an eye had apparently traveled more than a hundred meters, quickly disappearing on the horizon.

The moment both of them left, a shroud of black mist suddenly drifted over the surface of the sea, and within the mist, Garen’s figure appeared clearly. Both of his eyes scanned his surroundings. His nose twitched slightly before a stern gaze flashed in his eyes suddenly.

"Apparently I’ve been fooled as well! Fine fine fine!"

His figure turned, before Garen’s entire body turned into black mist once again and disappeared.

*************************

Within the borders of Daniela

Woo~~~~~~!!

The bleak and distant sound of a horn echoed from the top of the vast forest.

On the edge of an unusually tall white cliff, a large hand with cast-iron like muscles held a two-meter long black horn, raised toward the sky, its clear sound ringing continuously.

Boom!!

On the ground far away, a blood red air pillar shot into the sky suddenly, piercing through the clouds, dyeing the vast blue sky into red. The surrounding clouds gathered around the blood pillar and formed around it quickly, rotating around it.

"Welcome, God King!!!" The giant threw the horn down, before kneeling on the ground, and prostrating in worship.

"Welcome, God King!!!" Countless ear-piercing roars echoed from the bottom of the forest.

Within the green forest, hoards of bloodied Cthulhuism Society followers appeared, raising both of their hands as they prostrated in the direction of the blood pillar.

Countless faint chirping noises could be heard. Suddenly, countless Cthulhu silhouettes flashed in the sky.

It was the Water God, Light God, and Thunder God.

The three of them walked towards the blood pillar and bowed with a single hand pressed against their chests.

"May the wounds of the God King heal!"

Three different voices announced in unison, and their voices sounded through the empty space clearly, echoing far and wide, not fading out in the slightest.

"Even if your King’s wounds heal, we must still collect an abundance of Glittering Water, and get our hands on all of the Glittering Ponds beyond." A cold voice that was indistinguishable as male or female echoed from afar. "This water source will be a great help for our Secret Technique magic powers."

"Yes!" replied the three Cthulhus respectfully, as their Origin Cores were already within the Cthulhu King’s hands, making them unable to object.

"I can already clearly feel, the fated son of destruction that will endanger myself is none other than Hannet Thunderstorm," Cthulhu King said softly. "Go, all of you together, and bring him to me. I want to hang him from the top of Steele Cathedral."

The three middle-level Cthulhus did not hesitate at all, and quickly left in various directions.

*******************

Within the large open area between Kovitan’s Ultimate Protection and Ender.

White snow covered the rolling hills, and within the layers of snowy peaks was a secluded hilltop in a shaded area.

Dark grey stone ruins stood alone on one of the lower snow covered hill tops.

Most of these ruins were once dark grey stone buildings. Most of them had collapsed completely, but the most eye-catching one was a dark grey cathedral.

The sharp roof of the cathedral pierced through the sky, and the entire cathedral was shaped like a mountain. However it had more than just three sharp points, instead they seemed like sharp spears that had been piled together, and together had more than ten points, all of different heights.

The cathedral had a single dome-shaped protrusion, twenty meters tall, as wide as a football field. It was paved neatly with large black bricks, smooth, and unusually clean.

Within the dome contained the main hall, and was surrounded by twenty meter tall white stone columns that resembled human fingers. Hard and straight, the fingers supported the entire roof of the cathedral.

Cold mountain air blew past, whistling endlessly. Torches with blue fire stuck to each of the pillars and illuminated the hall in blue and white, making it bright and clear.

Inside the hall, were many people, some standing and some sitting. These people were either dressed in black, white or red robes. Within the black and white robes were many different shades, with robes of all colors. Most of the groups were led by elders, while the younger people occupied a separate section. These people in different colored robes made up at least ten different groups.

There were four groups that contained the most people.

Black, white, green and red. These four groups contained the most people, and had formed a circle, surrounding the center of the hall.

There was a large empty space in the middle of the hall where no one stood, as if for no reason.

The cold winds whistled, and only a few voices could be heard in the hall, although more than a hundred people had gathered in the cathedral, but everyone was focused on something, as if they were waiting for a specific timing.

"It’s almost time." Among the people in black robes, a man who was fully covered in long robes stepped forward slowly and said softly. Although his voice was low and feeble, everyone could still hear his words clearly.

"It should be now." Within the group of people in red robes, an old man with white hair and a bushy beard narrowed his eyes and said.

"It’s an old rule, so you should go first this time," the man in the black robe laughed.

The bushy-bearded old man nodded, and without holding back, stood directly in the center of the empty space.

"Now, all clans, please release your Totems!" he said loudly.

When he stopped speaking, the remaining black, white, and green color groups all took a step forward at the same time. None of them spoke while their whole bodies faintly glowed with Totem Light.

Black, white and green, the lights of all three different colors started off dim and became stronger quickly, before becoming bright, and finally blinding.

The Totem Lights of all three groups of people gathered together, transforming into three balls of light and hanging above their heads.

Among the three Totem Light balls, the black one was a ball of moving black flames. The white one was a complicated but gorgeous white flower. The green one was a large bird that had three pairs of eyes.

The three Totem Light balls flew towards the center of the hall simultaneously.

The red robed, bushy-bearded old man stretched his skinny, wrinkled arms out slowly, and raised them up high.

Tch!!

A blinding ray of light shot out of his fingertip suddenly. Within the red light, a beautiful red lotus bloomed slowly.

Black, white, green and red, these four lights fused with one another, and as if they had collapsed, all of the lights shrunk into one another.

The four rays of Totem Light immediately suppressed themselves and shrunk into a dot the size of a soybean, before hanging in the center of the hall.

The red robed old man looked at his own faction in a flustered manner, before leaving the center.

Boom!!!

Suddenly, the entire hall burst in an explosion of red light. All four lights turned into a sea of red before all of the Totem images disappeared completely.

The floors of the whole building shook violently, as if an earthquake was shaking snowy peak.

The avalanche was accompanied by an incredible amount of snow, shaking the ground violently as it crashed down the mountain.

Strangely, no one had moved from the hall. Everyone’s gazes were fixated on the blooming red light in the center. No matter how much the outside shook, this light remained steadily in place, while its whirlpool-like interior continued to rotate clockwise slowly.

"The fourteenth Clash of Clans begins now," announced the red robed old man hurriedly. "The organizer for this round is the Red Lotus Society!!"

The red robed old man waved a single hand before a faint red light screen suddenly floated on top of the heads of everyone inside the hall. This listed, in more than ten different languages, each clan’s previous rankings.

‘First place: Obscuro Society. Second place: Red Lotus Society. Third place: Terraflor Society. Fourth place: Resonance Tower.’

"It’s an old rule, but only the first four places have the right to enter the Tungus list, and obtain key and the permission to be in charge of opening the Tungus remains." said the old man loudly, while his voice echoed throughout the entire hall, allowing everyone to hear him clearly.

"Obscuro’s representatives please come forward." The old man from Red Lotus Society turned his gaze towards the group of black robed people. "For this contest, which three people would you like to send as representatives?"

"Three people?" The leader of the black robes suddenly smiled faintly.

Caw!!

A pitch-black crow flew into the hall from outside, beat its wings, and landed on the black robed man’s right shoulder at once.

"Go, Gelouse…" The black robed man stretched his hand out and pointed, and the black crow flew down suddenly, before its body became bigger and it grew fiercer. In the blink of an eye, it melted and transformed, before solidifying into a black robed figure wearing a hood.

"Gelouse!!"

At once, astonished voices could be heard, and the old man from the Red Lotus Society turned pale. The faces of the white robed people from Terraflor Society quickly turned serious as well.

"You’re not Obscuro!" yelled the green robed leader of the Resonance Tower.

The pale corners of the black robed man’s mouth curled into a smile, as he reached his hand out to remove the hood on his head.

A pale, bald man suddenly appeared in front of everyone. His skin color was of an unusual kind of paleness. It had dull silver-grey tones, without a hint of rosiness, and resembled smooth hard stone.

He had no eyebrows, no beard, and not a single strand of hair to be seen, not on his entire head.

He had faint wrinkles on his forehead, and both of his eyes were deep and bright, like the clearest blue lakes and gems.

He loosened the black robe on his body, exposing the heavy and complicated black armor underneath.

"The thousand year-long dispute between clans should end today…"

"Looks like you’ve truly broken through, Hellgate…"

Among the people in white robes, two of them stood out slowly, removing their hoods, exposing that themselves as a man and a woman. The man was handsome, while the woman was beautiful, and both of their foreheads were embedded with silver flower head ornaments.

"Sisley, Aud, I’m so glad that you’re still alive," said Hellgate with a sincere smile.

Chapter 499: Intercept and Reward 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black stone pillars stood upright on the ground.

In the center of the gravelly dirt, between the stone pillars, a pitch-black stone city stood quietly. Its hundred-meters-long city walls stood at a height of ten meters, and the top of the wall was armed with archers dressed in various clothes, who were holding bows and arrows and constantly shooting downwards.

The scene below the wall was dark and messy, while groups of men in torn grey clothes held spears, axes and other weapons as they surrounded the main gate of the city walls.

Looking down from the sky, one could see more than a thousand people in the siege army, while there were only ten people barely supporting the city gates. Among the sea of tightly packed heads, blue and red light explosions would occur occasionally, and after each explosion, more than ten people would be sent flying, creating empty spaces. But these inferior troops did not retreat, instead, they remained red-eyed, as if they had lost all reason, and charged towards the city walls mindlessly.

Occasional band noises echoed over faintly, but the siege army did not yell and remained silent while they charged, giving people an eerie vibe.

"Do not let them take the Precious Heirlooms! Or else, no one in this world will be able to stop them anymore!" said a man with a black beard in a low voice, while standing on top of the city walls.

Beside him were a few boys and girls, but none of them possessed any signs of youthful immaturity. Every one of them had resolute expressions on their faces, as they looked at the killing fields below them with no fear at all.

"News has arrived from the King of Osa," said a boy softly. "The monsters on Withdrawal Bridge have increased, so we should be careful."

When the chaos began in Osa, the only means of entry and exit, the Withdrawal Bridge, had been occupied by monsters, making it unusable, before the bridge itself was blown up and broken as well. Osa was a natural valley and cave country situated in the southernmost part of the East Continent, hence it was always somewhat disconnected from the rest of the world, and after its communication got cut off from the outside recently, it had become even more of a lone army, and lost all news of the outside world.

"Our clan has guarded the Demon Phoenix for more than two thousand years already, and I once assumed that with this talented generation of people, we would finally have a hope of ending the thousand-year-old grudge, I never expected that…" Blackbeard touched a scar on his forehead.

"If the Demon Phoenix escapes, then…"

"Tony." Among the boys and girls, a delicate and pretty girl in leather armor reached her hand out and held Blackbeard's right palm gently. ‘Tony' meant ‘father' in the Osa language, meaning that she was obviously this man's daughter.

"Don't say such discouraging things, Big Brother has inherited the Moon Scar, and will definitely not let the Demon Phoenix break the Seal!" The girl's brown armor hugged her figure tightly, showing the curves of her body, while her long black hair was tied in a smooth, high ponytail that flowed straight down but curved slightly, before flowing down again, giving off a heroically spirited vibe.

"That's right, uncle, we've inherited the Moon Scar, and will definitely not let the Demon Phoenix break the Seal!" said the leading boy enthusiastically, before the other boys and girls voiced their agreement as well.

"The source of the Demon Phoenix's strength is Black Gold, but that's not a big deal because once we destroy the Black Gold, we will be able to destroy the curse temporarily." Blackbeard lifted his hands slowly, before raising them up high.

"Charge!!!" "Kill them!!" They yelled loudly, before dull galloping noises could be heard, as more than a hundred horsemen charged out of the city gates. Just like a sharp knife, they began massacring crowds of people while faint yellow halos illuminated their bodies, and they held long swords that cut through their enemies precisely and killed them in one go as if they were slicing through stalks of wheat.

"Ready! If this killing continues, the Demon Cloud Puppets will suffer great losses, and will definitely not last long, so they should be moving out soon…" Blackbeard stared deeply, before turning his attention towards a further area. "Those without the Moon Scar will be unable to fight the Demon, so the rest will depend on all of you."

The crowd of boys and girls nodded solemnly. Dull hums could be heard from their bodies, and after each sound, an additional dark gold glow would appear on their bodies.

This glow resembled an aura that was constantly emitting from their bodies, before these children's figures underwent slight changes, as if they had expanded, becoming much taller and bigger than they were before.

"Leave it to us, uncle." The leading boy grabbed the two large hilts at his waist. "Let's go!"

He turned around and led the others down the city walls.

"Everyone, move back!! Retreat, retreat!!" The leader of the cavalry team roared and led his team back quickly. The Totem Users in the team released Tactic glows constantly, but strangely enough, none of them released any Totems for battle, but just drew Tactics to do battle instead. Even though some of the people in the cavalry team were injured, they still had no plans to release their Totems.

On a tall dark cliff near Black Mountain City

Three figures in purple armor stood beside the cliff quietly, looking at the mountainous city from afar.

"We cannot let the Demon Cloud Puppets suffer great losses, as these are still our Lord's nutrients." A girlish voice echoed from the girl in purple armor in front, and although her voice was curt and cold, it carried faint tones of seriousness, as if two versions of herself were speaking simultaneously.

"After a thousand years of entanglement with one another, we have finally reached the moment where we are separated into victory or defeat," said another person in purple armor, and this time, it was a low male voice. "The Demon Phoenix Peak from a thousand years ago will finally begin again, and this time, no one will be able to obstruct our Lord's majesty and power!"

"Once we kill the last of these Moon Scars, there will no longer be anything standing in the way of Our Lord conquering the world!" The last purple armored man had a shrill voice but harbored a violent air about him.

"Move out." The purple armored girl took a step forward and walked directly off the cliff, before flying downwards.

Shh!!

A pair of large purple flesh wings grew out of her back suddenly, and flapped in the air, flying towards the battlefield not far from there.

The other two people flew off the cliff as well, after a pair of wings grew out of their backs, while they followed the girl closely.

Behind the three people, on top of the black cliff, at the center of the mountain, a large Lone Eye blinked open.

The bloodied Lone Eye seemed to be made up of mountain rocks but actually consisted of countless stones, plants, and trees that had twisted together, forming the shape of a large eye. It looked towards the black mountainous city from afar.

The Lone Eye's gaze seemed to pass through empty spaces, and reached the city wall of the mountain city, looking directly at the two eyes of the delicate girl beside Blackbeard.

The girl felt dizzy before a white pale blue crescent-shaped scar silently floated up on the right side of her face.

"We meet again, young Osaka." A cold, female voice could be heard throughout the sky above the whole city.

The girl shivered, while pale blue auras were released from her body constantly, as she tried to resist the large pressure from its gaze.

"I won't let you get away so easily!!" The girl ground her teeth determinedly, while her body continued to shiver uncontrollably, but after awhile, cold sweat had soaked through her inner protective cotton armor completely.

Blackbeard was uncomfortable as well, even more so than his own daughter, as his entire body was surrounded by purple light, and his face was stiff, making it impossible for him to retaliate while he was half-kneeling on the ground.

"I can feel the air of fate…" the woman's cold voice lamented. "Everything that happened today is fate allowing me to escape, and the world will finally be changed because of me… Boom!!!"

Before she finished speaking, a light pillar consisting of translucent black chains fell from the sky, suddenly crashing into the center of the battlefield. The light pillar possessed a diameter of a few meters and resembled a large tree, and remained on the ground for more than ten seconds, with strong ripples of power that resembled hurricanes, that sent the surrounding people flying at once, like dusty ants that had been blown away by fierce winds.

Endless humming noises interrupted and masked the Lone Eye's voice, making it impossible to hear the rest of her speech.

"God Cloud, you can't escape anymore," said a man's voice from high above in the sky.

The chain light pillar dispersed slowly, before a ray of white light shot out suddenly, towards the direction of the Lone Eye in the black mountain wall.

"No!! That's the Demon Phoenix Seal's land!!" The father and daughter looked downwards, before their pupils widened suddenly, while the three people in purple armor who were going up against the Moon Scar youths earlier, opened their mouths in shock as well.

"That's the way! That's the way! Hahaha! I'm finally going to break the seal!! A thousand years! A thousand years of…" An insanely ecstatic expression appeared on the Lone Eye's face suddenly, as its unsuppressible noises of joy echoed throughout the entire sky.

Tch!

Throughout the sky, black clouds gathered, forming a tall man in a black robe. His golden hair flew in the wind, and a proud expression beamed in his eyes contemptuously, like a cat that had caught a mouse.

He raised a single hand up high, before pressing it down suddenly.

Countless black clouds gathered, and formed a large black hand instantly, before violently clawing at the white light that God Cloud had created.

"This is fate! You cannot obstruct fate!!" The Demon Phoenix's voice grew more high-pitched.

"Deep Demon Arm!!" God Cloud's voice echoed throughout the white light suddenly.

Instantly, everyone felt the black light flash, before their eyesight became blurry, and within the white light, a sharp, pitch-black hand stretched outwards slowly. It moved directly towards the large black cloud hand that came swinging at it.

Boom!!

A large mushroom-like black cloud exploded suddenly, and the white light was refracted into shards by the explosion, before crashing into the Lone Eye in the mountain wall.

"Die!!" The voice of the black-clothed man echoed throughout the sky suddenly.

The crowd of people on the battlefield merely heard the crackling of electricity.

A black lightning bolt shot towards the ground violently.

"Oh, ~~~ Oh~~~ It's coming! It's coming!! Coming…" After that, only the noise of crashing thunder could be heard.

"Hahaha!!! I have finally come out… Ah!!" Before the Demon Phoenix finished speaking, a painful cry could be heard, stopping it instantly.

At this moment, the Moon Scar youths, Black City cavalry Totem Users that were fighting, and the three purple armored, winged people, all looked at each other, as their minds had become dull as if everything had become a sticky mess.

"The grudge between you and me finally ends today!!" The black-clothed man's voice echoed from afar.

"Black Swamp Palace Master! Don't force us to go overboard!!" echoed another girl's voice angrily.

"Hehe!!"

The three purple armored people stopped in mid-air while looking at the land of the Seal from afar, where the Lone Eye was positioned.

Two separate rays of black and white light intertwined and fought there constantly, while ripples of power that almost seemed physical permeated around, and everything that came in contact with the ripples melted and decomposed, turning into puddles of black goo.

Chapter 500: Intercept and Reward 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At this moment, bright red and gold light flew around and filled the sky, and half of the sky was dyed in gold and red hues.

Countless rays of red and gold light twisted and weaved themselves around in the sky, before solidifying into a tall silver-faced man in a long red robe. Without saying a word, he raised his hand and pointed downwards.

Red thunderbolts appeared in the sky instantly, solidifying into a thunder pillar, before crashing down suddenly.

"Cthulhu King!!" An angry, violent voice echoed from the black and white intertwined lights.

A black figure flashed, evading the thunder pillar, before moving ten meters backward and suspending itself mid-air.

Garen's incomparably furious face appeared within everyone's vision clearly.

He took a deep breath, raising his chest up high before black cloud whirlpools with diameters of over ten meters gathered behind him quickly. The shadow of a black and red colored Nine-Headed Hydra floated out behind him slowly, and the gigantic ten-meter tall shadow made it seem like a demon.

Roar!!!

Garen raised his head suddenly, and the Nine-Headed Hydra raised its nine heads towards the sky and roared angrily at the same time.

The Black Water True Technique fueled the Hydra's powerful roar, and this was the first time Garen used all of his power to release the Hydra's roar since he entered Form 5.

A circle of black ripples surrounded him while he remained in the center before it spread towards its surroundings rapidly. The ripples resembled the sharpest razors that sliced through the cliff instantly, before more than a hundred meters of the top half of the cliff slid down suddenly. Instantly, a large round pit appeared in a section of the ground that was cleared up, and the black stone pillars inside quickly broke off into tiny pieces of sand and dust.

The ripples collided into God Cloud and Aixi, and as both of them could not react in time, they could only groan in pain as they were sent flying backward before they crashed into the ground and were embedded in an unknown depth.

The man clad in a bloody robe in the sky remained indifferent.

"Idiotic struggle," he waved his hand and pointed again.

A red pillar of red light gathered in the sky, before crashing down suddenly.

Boom!!

The red light pillar collided with the black ripples, stiffening for a moment, before piercing through the ripples suddenly, and crashing into Garen's body violently.

Before he could even groan, Garen crashed into the ground at once, and with himself as the center, a gigantic, hundred meters wide stone pit formed once again, as dust and rubble flew upwards, forming a grey cloud. The stormy winds blew, causing the dust to be blown everywhere, while the sky became grey and blurry.

Roar!!!

After the Hydra roared, Garen turned into a ray of black light again, and shot off the ground, before flying into the sky towards Cthulhu King.

"God's Sacrifice!" Cthulhu King turned around, and evaded a collision with the black light perfectly, while at the same time, a red semi-circular light flashed across one side of his body, coincidentally blocking Garen's black light.

Bang! Crash!!

Garen's entire body was blown up into countless clouds of bloody mist, and once it solidified, it crashed towards the ground due to the powerful rebound strength.

But a faint look of surprise appeared on Cthulhu King's face suddenly.

He stretched out a finger, gently stroking the right side of his face, where a bloody red scar had formed there faintly.

"Ahhh!!!" Garen's incomparably furious howls echoed from below.

Inside the deep pit, Garen lay face up, while countless red lightning bolts flooded his surroundings, like countless ropes that tied him down tightly.

"I let you go the last time, thinking that you would learn your lesson, but I never expected that you would be such a brainless idiot," said Cthulhu King while he looked down at him contemptuously.

He waved a single hand, before another ray of red light fell from the sky, and crashed violently into the pit where Garen lay.

Boom!!

The red light was blinding, and he could not see anything clearly for a moment, except that the deep pit in the ground had expanded, becoming much deeper.

Dust flew about, impairing his line of vision.

God Cloud and Aixi flew out of the pit and landed on the ground gently, although their faces were as white as paper, without the slightest hint of rosiness.

After being pursued by Garen for more than ten thousand kilometers, and after running through an unknown number of countries and territories, they had become exhausted long ago. It was fortunate that Cthulhuism Society and Obscuro Society were allies. When they required assistance during dire times, their lives would be secured.

"Has it ended?" Aixi supported God Cloud and looked on while Cthulhu King floated down slowly.

"Luke, I owe you one," nodded God Cloud while he looked at Cthulhu King with a bitter smile.

Cthulhu King nodded and began to speak before his expression changed suddenly.

Faintly, from the deep pit where Garen lay, shrouds of pitch-black smoke wafted out slowly and spread out towards its surroundings like a living creature.

Within the smoke, poisonous mist soon turned into little black snakes that slithered around, making soft hissing noises.

Cthulhu King's expression became serious. Unlike the heavily injured God Cloud and Aixi, if the previous strength was too insignificant to threaten him, these current ripples of power, were enough to kill him.

Suddenly, a ray of black light shot out of the deep pit, soared through the sky, before falling down slowly, and unlike the previous chaotic manner, the current black light was calm and unhurried, and naturally steady.

Plop!

Two feet landed on the ground inside the deep pit.

Garen's figure appeared in front of the three people once again.

Unlike his previous hot-tempered manner, his current expression was gentle, and black mist circled his body, quickly solidifying into a simple long black robe on his body.

"I need to thank Cthulhu King for helping me digest the ancient Nine-Headed Hydra's will. I never thought that being in a state of separation would be so difficult to solve," said Garen with a smile on his face.

Suddenly, the three other people saw another expression morphing on his face, and this new face was filled with anger, dissatisfaction, and was howling. But this was merely a translucent state, that was layered on top of Garen's own face.

Instantly, the angry face and the smiling face seemed to be substituting constantly, giving off a strange vibe.

Cthulhu King's eyes narrowed, and a red light flashed across his hands that hung downwards before a pair of red metal gloves appeared there.

"Interesting…" He smiled faintly, and instantly, both of his hands appeared in front of his chest, before turning into fists and striking the area in front of him.

Bang!!

Garen appeared in front of him suddenly, and both of their four limbs were used to exchange blows before exploding a circular area with a dull hum. All this was done without any Totem Light splashes, revealing their extremely terrifying power and control.

Garen's fist was deflected, and his arm twisted before his elbow was illuminated with black light as he threw it forward furiously, striking Cthulhu King's left cheek directly.

The palm of his other hand was straightened into a knife-like shape, before he disappeared from his original position, and struck the back of Cthulhu King's head out of thin air.

Clap!

His elbow was deflected and was struck by a ray of red light that had shot out suddenly.

The first that struck the back of Cthulhu King's head was deflected by a red semicircle instantly which shattered into pieces. Cthulhu King's expression remained unchanged while he opened his mouth and aimed it directly at Garen, as red light glowed out of his mouth. However, a ray of black light struck his cheek lightly again before he fell out of the sky; Garen had gained the upper hand.

Both of them were entangled beside the deep pit and fought there, and their limbs could not be seen from their figures, as the only things that could be seen were black and red lights that were intertwining and colliding with one another.

With a ‘bang', Cthulhu King stepped back suddenly, and stood at a distance of more than a hundred meters away, while his face flushed red, and under the immense pressure, gold-red blood started flowing out of his right ear involuntarily.

But Garen on the opposite side was slightly worse off, as one arm hung from his body limply, as the result of heavy injuries from two losses.

However, both of them were characters that possessed powerful Recovery abilities, and after standing still for a while, their wounds had almost recovered completely, and they were back to charging at each other.

The banging noises that resulted from the collisions could be heard constantly and compared to earlier, the current battle was not as elegant as before, but the thick Totem Powers that could be seen from their bodies were still strangely powerful.

Garen could constantly use the Nine-Life Talent together with his Potential Points to repair his body, while Cthulhu King also had similar measures, showing that the Cthulhus undying and indestructible characteristics were apparent here. All wounds would be completely healed within a few breaths.

The people on top of the city wall had turned numb completely. Blackbeard stood in front of his daughter and shielded her after all of their army forces had been withdrawn.

A group of people had gathered beside him, and all of them were the major and minor heads and representatives of the city. Currently, they were all looking on with wide eyes and opened mouths at the disastrous and terrifying battle happening outside.

"What about the Demon Phoenix…" asked someone, as this monster that the household had guarded for a thousand years was obviously where everyone's greatest concerns lied.

"Over there!!" Someone had noticed its tracks and was pointing towards a faraway distance.

The crowd looked over at that direction, but could only see a figure that was fully dressed in black clothes that were leading three tiptoeing purple-armored people towards a faraway place.

The crowd was suddenly speechless.

They once thought that the terrifying thing in Osa was the Demon Phoenix, and that it was the greatest strength in the world, and that once they released her, misery would befall their lives, and the world would fall into chaos.

They never expected…

This gap was indeed a little too wide.

"City Master… What do we do now?" a newly recruited soldier asked Blackbeard softly.

"We…" Blackbeard opened and closed his mouth, but even from his vision, he could clearly see that the Demon Phoenix's face was currently astonished, and was worried that some of the fighters would notice her expression.

A Demon Phoenix like this… He truly did not know what to say now.

"Perhaps… Perhaps we were cut off from the world for too long…" he smiled bitterly.

"Without a mission, what else can we do?" He was slightly confused, but he was not the only one, as the faces of everyone here were also filled with confused looks.

The Demon Cloud Puppets outside had been injured and killed long ago because of the aftermath of the fighting, and most of them could not even survive the aftermath, and this was an incredible feat. Not only the Puppets, but the three purple armored leaders suffered a similar fate as well, as one of them had been flung aside by the red light pillar, losing half of their body at once, while the other had been struck on the face by a flying rock, and was now crying…

If it wasn't for their strong Life Forces, they would have probably been destroyed completely after the fight.

At this point, no one cared about the mission or the Demon Phoenix anymore. In the eyes of the group of people, the Demon Phoenix was merely a child that had passed by, a mere feeble thing.

Blackbeard's mind was a chaotic mess, and at this moment, the two faraway people had separated again.

The black and red figures flew around, and the black figure leaped a few times, flashing past the tops of the heads of the four Demon Phoenixes, and the four Demon Phoenixes cried out in pain before they were caught by the black mist.

The two people were in terribly bad states, as the head and bodies of the one in red clothes had been separated, before he used both of his hands to press his head back in place again, allowing the large amounts of flesh at his neck to connect back. It looked incomparably normal.

Meanwhile, the man in black had a large hole with a diameter of half a meter in the center of his chest, exposing all of his internal organs clearly, but he continued to move like normal as if it did not affect him at all.

"How is he still living..?" yelled some people with uncontrollably shocked looks on their faces.

"They've stolen the Demon Phoenix!!" Blackbeard's daughter yelled. "Tony, what should we do? The Demon Phoenix has been stolen, we…"

The group of people looked at each other in despair, completely devoid of any goals. They had painstakingly guarded this enemy for many years, only to have it stolen helplessly by someone, and from the looks of it, it seemed as easy as stealing a few chicks. This was unbearable for the hidden school that had guarded it for a thousand years...

Chapter 501: Root 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Blackbeard's mind was a mess. However, after seeing everyone's gaze fixated on him, he tried hard to clear his mind and clarify a few key points.

"Without Demon Phoenix, there is no point for us to be on guard here. Looks like we have to think of a way to escape to the outside world….How long has it been since we were in touch with the outside world?"

"I always thought that we were protecting the world from the ferocious Demon Phoenix. We were fighting for true peace. I never thought…We have indeed overestimated ourselves." Blackbeard sighed.

"Uncle." The young leader with a crescent mark suddenly voiced out. He lowered his head and spoke with a low voice. However, there was a sense of immovable determination to it. "We have to go and see the outside world."

The people around were quiet for a moment, then immediately started talking.

"How about the withdrawn bridge? That's the only exit."

"No one can leave Osa without breaking through the Six-Horned Bull."

"How did those people enter? We must be able to exit that way!"

"They are so strong, we…" "Maybe the Six-Horned Bull has already been handled by them?"

"Let's go have a look!" "Yes, have a look, in case…" "Let's go have a look!"

Within a while, arguments due to different opinions became a united voice, to go and have a look. At that moment, everyone's gaze fixated on two people, the young man with a crescent mark and Blackbeard. These were the two men with authority in the small village.

"Our responsibility is to guard the Demon Phoenix to prevent it from creating trouble. Since the Demon Phoenix has been kidnapped, we have to find out what is that person's true purpose." Blackbeard thought for a moment. Finally, he managed to find a reason to appease himself.

Since all of them were soldiers, they could leave anytime.

"After all it is our thousand-year duty," Blackbeard said surely. "Let's go to look for the black-robed man! Let's find the Demon Phoenix, and also...also see the world!"

"Tony...According to what I heard just now, the people fighting called the black-robed man Lord of Black Swamp Palace. There was also Cthulhu King. They were speaking in a strange Ender language." Blackbeard's daughter who had the most talent in linguistics spoke. She was the legendary sage Osaka's reincarnation after a thousand years. Osaka had been the great sage that had sealed the Demon Phoenix. Her position among the crowd was very special.

"A person as strong of this is definitely not an unknown figure. As long as we find a civilization, we definitely would be able to find out." Blackbeard nodded. He looked at the devastated battlefield below. Without the power of the Demon Phoenix, those puppets fell to the ground, each returning to the state of a corpse.

"Let's leave the city!" He shouted at last.

　　**********************

Ten days later...

He took a deep breath.

Garen sat crossed-legged on the floor, healing his body. From time to time, he would spit out blood. He was severely injured.

It was a black barren plain. The surroundings were quiet. Some distance away, a few white wolves were being corroded by black acid into corpses.

The Demon Phoenix and three others were being cautious on the side. They were watching Garen closing his eyes, meditating. The four of them exchanged gazes and quietly walked away. A faint purple light surrounded the four people, completely blocking off the noise from their footsteps.

From their point of view, there was a large, round hole on his chest. His body was almost split into two. With injuries like that, it would be considered extremely severe even for themselves, what more for a human. The man before them was definitely drained, without much energy remaining.

However, thinking of the terrifying wave and aftermath in the battle just now, four of them shuddered. Their first thoughts weren't to fight back, but a strong intent to escape.

As they took slow steps, minutes and seconds passed by.

Garen's aura stabilized. His eyes didn't seem to open, as if he had fallen asleep.

As they finally retreated towards behind a stone pillar, Demon Phoenix and the rest heaved sighs of relief.

"Where are you all heading to?"

Suddenly, a calm male voice came from behind.

The four of them were shocked. Their bodies became numb and stood still. Only then did they notice that black gas was slowly coming from the ground beneath their feet. The black gas gathered into small snake-like shapes. Their glowing black eyes stared at the four of them coldly.

"Stay here and don't run around." Garen opened his eyes to look at the remaining potential points on his attribute pane. There were only ten plus points left, totally insufficient. In the battle with the Cthulhu King, he'd recklessly used his points during the battle. Hundreds of points that he had accumulated had been drained to maintain the full nine lives of his nine-life talent. Because of that, he'd used up too many potential points. Twenty potential points could be used to replenish a life. Normally, it wouldn't seem like much, but at this point where he was only left with ten points...

Garen spat out some air. The taste of blood was incredibly strong. His ears moved slightly. As he stood up, black gas suddenly appeared beneath his feet. With a swoosh, he disappeared into a ray of black light, which shot out into the distance.

Demon Phoenix and the rest heaved sighs of relief.

"My Lord, what should we do now?" The purple-armored girl, who was quietly beside Demon Phoenix asked.

"Do not panic...We do not know why he captured us. But since he didn't kill us after capturing us, he must have his reason. Let's not panic." The helmet on the Demon Phoenix's head had been corroded into black water after being surrounded by the black gas. It revealed a pretty girl's face beneath.

The girl had a healthy tan. She had a blue eye and a purple eye, while her two ears were a little pointy. She didn't look like a human. Her purple-black long hair was like feathers, and she was faintly releasing a strong strange aura.

"Never thought that I, Demon Phoenix, whom no one could restrict for thousands of years. But now, surprisingly…" Demon Phoenix stood up in negativity. She looked towards the sky with deep, complex emotions.

Bang!

It was the sound of a heavy object falling to the ground.

"Why you are you standing over there foolishly! Come over and prepare a meal!"

Garen's voice came from a close distance.

"Oh…" Demon Phoenix looked stunned. She hurried over to drag the ten-meter long corpse of a giant yellow bear on the ground. The three others also rushed over to help her.

For the past few days, Garen had been going to hunt and bringing back raw materials for Demon Phoenix and the rest to process, making all kinds of dishes. Garen never thought that the dishes that they made were actually decent. Hence, he would rather pass on this task fully to them.

However, today seemed different.

As they were processing the giant bear's corpse, a black ray of light landed not far away from them, forming Garen's figure. The difference this time was, there were a large group of more than ten yellow bears following him behind.

This bear species had a white horn on its chest. The horn faced the sky and could increase gravitational force by three times. These ten plus giant Gravity Bears were obviously chased here by Garen.

They gathered together and didn't dare to move at all. Numerous small black snakes suspended in the air around them. These snakes were formed purely by black gas. It was a huge oppression by a peak fifth form. Even Demon Phoenix and the rest also felt the air and didn't dare to go close, what more these Gravity Bears..

Very quickly, a purple bonfire came to life again. With one hand, Demon Phoenix was controlling the Demon Cloud Power, which emitted the purple flames. On her other hand, she was grabbing the hind leg of a giant bear, while the other purple-armored girl was carrying the bear's head.

The two of them set up the whole bear and barbequed it over the fire. The skinless bear turned red. As its blood continuously dripped, it quickly produced crackling sounds in the purple fire below. There was also a faint smell of meat flavor.

From time to time, purple-black smoke rushed into their faces, causing their faces to be smoked and blackened.

After finishing their barbeque of the giant bear, the two of them were covered in smoke, ruining their images.

The other two males had been responsible for skinning, draining the blood, removing the internal organs and other dirty tasks.

For the five of them, Demon Phoenix, her three companions, and Garen, who once again closed his eyes to rest on one side, this was their small, temporary campsite.

The four of them were busy with their own tasks. All of them were now Garen's captives. The original difference of statuses was also gone. Whether it was Demon Phoenix or her three underlings, they cooperated to cook up a meal. None of them considered any other things.

After the meat was done, the seasoning was passed on to the purple-armored female chef. Demon Phoenix went around to find edible vegetables and plants.

According to Garen, it wasn't appropriate to only eat meat. It has to be paired with some vegetables to be healthy. After a few deep thoughts and physical lessons, Demon Phoenix would naturally go around to find vegetables with decent texture. After all, no one would love to be severely beaten fifteen times in an hour...

She couldn't wander too far to obtain the vegetables. Fortunately, Garen had a good appetite. His strong body allowed him to only care about the taste and texture. He didn't have to consider whether it was poisonous or not.

Demon Phoenix walked for hundreds of meters. She had previously thought to escape. But unfortunately, the few small black snakes around her body made her dismiss the idea.

With the power of a fifth form, finding plants was extremely easy. Regardless of whether they were on the ground or underground, they couldn't escape Demon Phoenix's discerning eyes.

When she returned, the bear meat was already seasoned. Fresh green vegetables with golden-yellow bear meat, it looked appetizing indeed.

Under the salivating gaze of the rest of them, Garen was gobbling down the bear meat in big bites. The rich aroma was all around the area. But they didn't dare to move. They were only qualified to eat after Garen had finished eating.

Very quickly, after half an hour or so, Garen threw away the femur in his hand. The purple-armored female hurriedly served a napkin that was just cleaned. After wiping his mouth, Garen nodded in satisfaction.

"Look after these small things. I'm heading out first." He ordered.

"Yes." Demon Phoenix and the rest answered quickly.

"Alright." Garen stood up. He had almost fully recovered from the injuries on his body. With a bang, he exploded, becoming a black cloud that shot towards the distance.

Very quickly, a thunderous bang came from afar. A black giant stone pillar slowly broke down and collapsed. Roaring sounds could faintly be heard.

"Needless to say, they are fighting again." Demon Phoenix and the rest looked into the distance. They could only see the black cloud and red light interweaving in the dusty sky. They couldn't see anything else.

The terrifying tremor could be heard even from tens of kilometres away.

When they'd arrived on these plains, it had been a flourishing land.

Various strong creatures could be found everywhere fighting for territories. Desolate beast cries could be heard every evening. However, since those two people arrived, the whole plains had become silent…..

Chapter 502: Root 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Within the remains of a black cathedral on a snowy peak

Disciples from various associations had gathered together. There were hundreds of them, donning robes of different colors. All of them were the strongest elites in the East Continent's associations.

At that instant, everyone could feel that the atmosphere was heavy like never before.

In the center region of the crowd, there were four camps of different colors.

Black. White. Green. Red. The four robe colors represented the four strongest associations in the East Continent. It wasn't just their power that was the strongest. It was also their research abilities, potential, knowledge, and others. It was a comprehensive comparison.

There was a circle of black, stone, high-back seats in the middle of the crowd. On top, all of them were inlaid with fine, purple gemstones. The gemstones were like eyes.

The masters of the various associations stood in a circle with a red ball at the center. Their gaze landed in the middle of the hall, which was the empty area below the red ball.

The giant red ball was suspended in the air like a fireball. It was hung high above, illuminating the area beneath in red. Two figures stood confronting each other. One was an old man while the other was a middle-aged man.

The old man's right hand was shaking slightly. The swordfish totem suspended behind was slowly breaking down, releasing countless black dots.

"East Britain Lord. Please." The opposing middle-aged man was panting. He was resisting the intense pain in his abdomen as he muttered.

"The fourth battle match, Green Island Society wins!" The announcer on one side said loudly.

The old man shrugged, turned around and walked down. He returned to his seat in the midst of the blue-robed crowd.

"Fifth match! Green Island Society versus St. Lange School!"

The master of St. Lange School leaped into the sky. Light blue colored bird shadows appeared below his feet. Leveraging on them, he lightly landed in the middle of the arena.

"In this clash to unite all, only the Obscuro Society's master is someone worthy for me to follow! Out of all the East Continent associations, only the Obscuro Society's master can achieve true greatness."

"The Clash of Clans has been happening for a thousand years. No one can disrupt a thousand-year tradition." The master of the Green Island Society said in a low voice.

"Talk less nonsense. Let's begin!" The other party didn't want to say much. As he grabbed with his right palm, large amounts of light blue bird shadows appeared in the air around him. A wave-like black dagger appeared on his right hand, which he quietly thrust towards the direction of his opponent.

The Green Island Society master stomped his feet. His arms suddenly became two green, giant bird wings. He then leaped towards his opponents.

Hellgate was smiling in his seat, while the Sisley couple on the opposite looked solemn. Together with their supporters behind them, these two parties were two clearly distinct sides.

Hellgate's intent was obvious. He wanted to completely unite all the associations, ending the competition in the East Continent. No one wanted their inheritance to be cut off. No association could tolerate giving up their independence and becoming a pawn of the Obscuro Society.

Battle after battle, numerous masters came and left. Among them, there were also new geniuses and elites that appeared. However, it made people more and more disheartened. Winners from the Obscuro's camp grew more and more. Now, other than the Terraflor Society, the Green Island Society was the next strongest one. If they lost….

Everyone's faces grew grim.

Complex, true, fourth form elites or even the unique totems of fifth form masters flashed passed Hellgate's eyes. They were like the windows to the world, but they left no impression.

Before people knew it, the final four seeding battles had finally arrived.

At that point, Hellgate stood up with a smile.

Likewise, the opposing Sisley couple also stood up slowly. They smiled at each other, then held hands as they walked into the arena.

"Hellgate...Master." Sisley held her husband's hand tightly. In her heart, there was peace and serenity like never before. "The Terraflor Society challenges the Obscuro Society, in a battle to the death."

Hellgate walked into the arena to face the two people. Even he himself had a sense of admiration in his eyes.

"The grudges two hundred years should come to a complete end today."

There was an uproar in the crowd. No one thought that the Terraflor Society masters would challenge the Obscuro Society to a battle to the death.

Hellgate let out a smile. Beneath his pitch black armor, was a mountain-like body. The pressure from him almost caused the people around to be out of breath.

Pat.

He suddenly took the first step.

Buzzzz…..A low tremor spread out.

Beneath his feet, the ground slowly cracked. It was like a scar on the ground. Black lava silently gushed out. The lava emitted large amounts of white gas, passing by countless distraught faces.

The hall started to shake. The sky instantly changed as countless black clouds gathered. The whole sky instantly darkened.

Ming~~~

As they were standing in the hall, a ferocious wind was blowing from the outside. The blue torch on the stone pillar kept shaking, almost extinguishing.

"Hellgate, you really want to do this?" The master of the Red Lotus Society got up and slowly stood on the side of the Sisley couple.

Crack.

As lightning flashed across, the faces of the crowd instantly turned pale. A heavy, shapeless pressure completely surrounded the people. Everyone could only hear the heartbeat and breathing.

"Let's begin. This meaningless game should come to an end." The wrinkles on Hellgate's forehead deepened. He slowly opened his arms, as if he was about to hug something. Suddenly there was a tremor.

Bang!!

All the pillars in the cathedral instantly exploded and broke down. The people around were instantly overwhelmed by the ferocious force. At the same time, various associations formed light spheres of different sizes. However, they were all broken and cracked in the blink of an eye. Before the numerous totems that were just summoned could let out cries, they were already completely annihilated. The crowd was overwhelmed as if they were pressured by an unknown force to bow.

"Sisley, you can also see the door?" Surprisingly, that particular set of words came into Hellgate's mind.

"The gate in the sky….It's the door that leads the dead into the heavenly kingdom."

In a trance, everything seemed to overlap with her childhood.

Sisley tugged at her own hand, running on the shore. The evening sun revealing two shadows.

"You have gone crazy…." There was suddenly a long white-silver sword in Sisley's hand. The tip of the sword was surrounded by a circle of glittering diamond light.

"Return to my side," Hellgate whispered. "Don't you see it? The door is opening."

Her memory kept on overlapping with reality. She couldn't differentiate who was real and who was just an illusion.

"Everything is caused by you. The appearance of the black hole, the mutation of the earth." Sisley held her husband's hand tightly. Both of them held the long white-silver sword together.

"The cause of chaos!" The master of the Red Lotus Society looked solemn. There was rage simmering in his eyes. Two red flames slowly lit up on his shoulders and a flaming-red, lotus-like crown appeared on the air above his head. "The world fell into chaos because of you people pursuing the gates of heaven!!"

Hellgate looked as if he did not understand.

"I am not crazy….I just want to open that door, to see what is inside…"

　　*******************

On the Black Plains

Garen's fights with the Cthulhu King had become more and more frequent.

Initially, it had been once every few days. Very quickly, the tempo had sped up to once a day. Now after a month, it has become three times in one day.

Whoosh!!

A black giant living elephant was thrown through the air into the mouth of a black giant dragon.

The dragon mouth was formed of black smoke. There was not even a bubble after the ten-meter long black elephant was thrown into it. With a grunt, the black dragon instantly swallowed it.

Sitting crossed-legged beneath, Garen's lower body was completely gone. Visible to the naked eye, a new body was quickly forming.

Originally, Demon Phoenix and the rest had to barbecue and season the meat for Garen to eat. Now they didn't even have enough time. He ate the meat raw, without even barbecuing. They were even chasing a group of black giant elephants as livestock. These mutated beings were shivering at one side.

After swallowing more than 10 black giant elephants, the pitch blackness in Garen's eyes slowly subsided. His injuries were also completely healed.

Without saying a word, he stood up, becoming a black light again, shooting into the distance.

After a moment, the red lightning and black air interweaved in the sky in the distance. Needless to guess, both of them were fighting again.

The chaos lasted for more than an hour before it quietened down.

Garen's arms were completely gone. He flew back from afar. As he landed, he immediately grabbed a few elephants. The black gas became a large mouth, which swallowed an elephant in one gulp.

Moo!!

The elephant let out pitiful cries, but there was absolutely no way to struggle or escape.

As his injuries slowly improved, Garen's two hands also grew back.

At this stage, totem light was already completely fused into the body. There was no longer the saying where breaking through totem light would be equal to severe totem damage. As his body's strength increased at an insane speed, the lethality of his kicks and punches also dramatically increased. After the fusion process, the power in his body could absolutely oppress any lower level totem power.

With the Nine-Headed Hydra's terrifying regenerative abilities, plus the accumulation of potential points by hunting non-stop in this period of time, it allowed him to barely maintain this state of balance.

Through the daily battles with the Cthulhu King, both parties were already familiar with the other party's techniques.

The Cthulhu King was trained in a demonic martial art called the Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel. It is rumored to be able to draw energy from the sun to battle. However, it has to continuously suck and gather the "yin" essence of others, to balance the incredibly "yang" energy of the sun.

The terrifying part of this martial art was its uncomparable lethality and explosiveness. In an instant, it could unleash its greatest power without any indication.

Garen has heard of information about this demonic art in the Kovitan's Library. But he never thought that the Cthulhu King was trained in this martial art.

His lethality and explosiveness were far from the Cthulhu King. Although the Black Water True Technique allowed humans to enter into a supernatural realm, in terms of growth of strength, it was not even close to the Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel.

Fortunately, Garen could rely on his nine life talent plus the usage of potential points to fight a lose-lose battle. With that, he managed to maintain the state of a draw.

Of course, Garen's purpose wasn't just to understand the other party's martial art.

　　*********************

Puff!

The Cthulhu King sat on the ground. His face as pale as paper. One of his thighs was completely gone. This was the result of carelessly allowing Garen to get near. Now although he only could cross one leg as he sat, he was able to barely stabilize.

God Cloud and Aixi were already gone. He was the only one on the black plains. All the communication devices had been destroyed in the battle. There was nothing remaining.

Even his clothes were imitations created by totem power.

In over a month, his opponent grew from an easy one into a difficult one. Right now, if the Cthulhu King wasn't careful, he could be severely injured by his opponent.

The opponents speed of growth was incredibly fast. Even after living hundreds of years, he had never seen such a terrifying talent for martial arts. It was impossible for even the last Cthulhu King to have such terrifying and obvious growth.

But this wasn't the most worrisome thing for the Cthulhu King. It was the fact that the other party has been slowly understanding the paths and principles of his Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel.

The Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel was a terrifying demonic martial art invented by the last Cthulhu King before his death. Its complexity far surpassed a normal martial art by at least ten times.

But even so, that Garen already showed signs of understanding parts of the Sun-Sealing Demonic Wheel.

This caused the easy-going Cthulhu King to panic.

Initially, he didn't want to get entangled in this and planned to return directly to the Cthulhuism Society's headquarters. However, he had changed his mind. He wanted to make Garen stay, then think of a way to completely destroy this menace.

With such terrifying growth, if he was given more time….

If he directly returned to the Cthulhuism Society's headquarters, or he killed himself and allowed the Origin to revive in the headquarters, he would escape this entanglement. The other party wouldn't foolishly pursue him to the headquarters. It would be difficult to find a chance to destroy the opponent.

He had to think of a way...